{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Sullivan?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Aspiration pneumonia", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Big Moe?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Arsenic poisoning", "Chronic renal failure", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Sims?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Respiratory arrest", "Ovarian cancer", "Muscular dystrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Derrick Shepard?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Cardiomegaly", "Pyaemia", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Henri Matisse?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Marfan syndrome", "Exhaustion", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of T-Bone Wolk?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Myocardial infarction", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Glioblastoma multiforme"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Guy Williams?", "answers": ["Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Lobar pneumonia", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marty Feldman?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Melanoma", "Bright's disease", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rudolph Valentino?", "answers": ["Peritonitis", "Influenza", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rudolph Valentino?", "answers": ["Hepatitis A", "Embolism", "Pleurisy", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Hughes?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Myocardial infarction", "Synovial sarcoma", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pepsi Tate?", "answers": ["Falling", "Pancreatic cancer", "Respiratory Infection", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pat Garrett?", "answers": ["Poison", "Morphine", "Skin cancer", "Ballistic trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Horatio Spafford?", "answers": ["Endometrial cancer", "Malaria", "Coronary thrombosis", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paula O'Hara?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Smoke inhalation", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rick Danko?", "answers": ["Pernicious anemia", "Myocardial infarction", "Renal failure", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony Wilson?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Pulmonary embolism", "Cirrhosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hern\u00e1n Cort\u00e9s?", "answers": ["Pleurisy", "Renal failure", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert B. Parker?", "answers": ["Physical abuse", "Myocardial infarction", "Lobar pneumonia", "Skin cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Groucho Marx?", "answers": ["Tongue Cancer", "Cyanide poisoning", "Pneumonia", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ken Kesey?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Meningitis", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Traumatic brain injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Keith Haring?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "AIDS", "Dementia", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brian Jacques?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lillian Wald?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Viral pneumonia", "Parkinson's disease", "Endometrial cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Howard Carter?", "answers": ["Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Physical abuse", "Lymphoma", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Boyd?", "answers": ["Viral pneumonia", "Toxoplasmosis", "Gigantism", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Boyd?", "answers": ["B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Bright's disease", "Liver tumour", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Boyd?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Parkinson's disease", "Cor pulmonale", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andrei Tarkovsky?", "answers": ["Pulmonary aspiration", "Asphyxia", "Emphysema", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jonathan Ferrell?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Dementia", "Ballistic trauma", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lane Smith?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Motor neuron disease", "Heart cancer", "Iatrogenesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Al Davis?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Heart failure", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of M. S. Subbulakshmi?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Bronchitis", "Pleurisy", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gene McFadden?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Puerperal fever", "Anal cancer", "Myelodysplastic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gene McFadden?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Liver tumour", "Infectious disease", "Intestinal Obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Muammar al-Gaddafi?", "answers": ["Skin cancer", "Ballistic trauma", "Edema", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Eddington?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Lymphoma", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Eddington?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Liver disease", "Colon Cancer", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mickey Cohen?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Stomach cancer", "Chronic renal failure", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Thomas Wolfe?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Meningitis", "Cancer", "Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Conrad?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Spinal tumor", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Doyle?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Myocardial infarction", "Coronary artery disease", "Pernicious anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of H\u00e9ctor Camacho?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Ballistic trauma", "Alcohol intoxication", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hulda Regehr Clark?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Gigantism", "Multiple myeloma", "Celiac disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gustav Klimt?", "answers": ["Multiple myeloma", "Post-polio syndrome", "Pneumonia", "Dementia pugilistica"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gustav Klimt?", "answers": ["Anorexia nervosa", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rosalind Russell?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Thyroid cancer", "Breast cancer", "Multiple myeloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Thorpe?", "answers": ["Testicular cancer", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Myocardial infarction", "Acute renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miguel Pi\u00f1ero?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Cirrhosis", "Brain tumor", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Conway Twitty?", "answers": ["Pulmonary aspiration", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Epidural hematoma", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mark Abrahamian?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Myocardial infarction", "Spinal tumor", "Acute renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Kaufman?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Cancer", "Congenital heart defect", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Kaufman?", "answers": ["Cor pulmonale", "Fever", "Throat cancer", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Keith Floyd?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Septic shock", "Spinal tumor", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mike Evans?", "answers": ["Cancer of the larynx", "Smoke inhalation", "Throat cancer", "Cholangiocarcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Salvador Dal\u00ed?", "answers": ["Pulmonary aspiration", "Multiple sclerosis", "Heart failure", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Salvador Dal\u00ed?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Pneumonia", "Cervical cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stephen Ambrose?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Aplastic anemia", "Gallbladder cancer", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Geeta Bali?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Cervical cancer", "Smallpox", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rita Hayworth?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Anemia", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Morgan?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Diarrhea", "Testicular cancer", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Hartnell?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Typhoid fever", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Hartnell?", "answers": ["Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Choking", "Heart failure", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Hartnell?", "answers": ["Acute renal failure", "Wound", "Cardiovascular disease", "Smallpox"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of L. S. Lowry?", "answers": ["Bubonic plague", "Morphine", "Pneumonia", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Gotti?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Liver cancer", "Arteriosclerosis", "Tongue Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Samuel Beckett?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Barbiturate overdose", "Heart cancer", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris Mims?", "answers": ["Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Respiratory failure", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Les Paul?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Uterine cancer", "Physical abuse", "Pernicious anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ron Silver?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Alcoholism", "Fever", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Curt Flood?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Anal cancer", "Throat cancer", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nellie Fox?", "answers": ["Skin cancer", "Kidney Disease", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Glenn Gould?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Aplastic anemia", "Stroke", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Nelson Reilly?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Pneumonia", "Aortic dissection", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jimmie Dodd?", "answers": ["Burn", "Acute pancreatitis", "Cancer", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Flannery O'Connor?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Brain tumor", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rituparno Ghosh?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Cardiac arrest", "Cerebral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David McLetchie?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Malnutrition", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Alcohol intoxication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Moana Pozzi?", "answers": ["B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Drug overdose", "Liver tumour", "Iatrogenesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Reeves?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "Diarrhea", "Ballistic trauma", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kirk Urso?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Viral pneumonia", "Congenital heart defect", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ralph Abernathy?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Endometrial cancer", "Infection", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Graham Kennedy?", "answers": ["Epilepsy", "Dementia pugilistica", "Celiac disease", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Domino Harvey?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Diarrhea", "Congenital heart defect", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gypsy Rose Lee?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Kidney Disease", "Infectious disease", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Jordan?", "answers": ["Arthritis", "Pneumonia", "Post-polio syndrome", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rupert Brooke?", "answers": ["Metastatic Melanoma", "Polycythemia", "Pneumonia", "Aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rupert Brooke?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Hypothermia", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Raj Kapoor?", "answers": ["Cardiac surgery", "Typhoid fever", "Heart failure", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Raj Kapoor?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Renal failure", "Cirrhosis", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Raj Kapoor?", "answers": ["Pulmonary aspiration", "Asthma", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eddy Duchin?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Smallpox", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Epidemic typhus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Phil Harris?", "answers": ["Intracranial aneurysm", "Cerebral edema", "Myocardial infarction", "Colon Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Phil Harris?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Melanoma", "Stroke", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barbara Britton?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Atherosclerosis", "Stomach cancer", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Donat?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Asthma", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ren\u00e9 L\u00e9vesque?", "answers": ["Crohn's disease", "Cardiac arrest", "Liver failure", "Encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ren\u00e9 L\u00e9vesque?", "answers": ["Testicular cancer", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Heart cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harry S. Truman?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Tetanus", "Pneumonia", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Diane Cilento?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Nephropathy", "Cancer", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fats Waller?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Uremia", "Coronary thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fats Waller?", "answers": ["Cardiac surgery", "Uremia", "Pneumonia", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Quorthon?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Asthma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dack Rambo?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Acute pancreatitis", "Leukemia", "Marfan syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward Smith?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Cardiomyopathy", "Multiple myeloma", "Ischaemic heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brad Armstrong?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Mesothelioma", "Stroke", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Randy Vanwarmer?", "answers": ["Epidemic typhus", "Leukemia", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bud Abbott?", "answers": ["Hepatitis C", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Prostate cancer", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bud Abbott?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Breast cancer", "Cervical cancer", "Hepatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carroll O'Connor?", "answers": ["Intracranial aneurysm", "Diabetes mellitus", "Congenital heart defect", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carroll O'Connor?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Sepsis", "Myocardial infarction", "Celiac disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Poston?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Septic shock", "Oral cancer", "Cyanide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Adam Faith?", "answers": ["Smoke inhalation", "Gallbladder cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Timmy Everett?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Arsenic poisoning", "Myocardial infarction", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johnny Carson?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Morphine", "Emphysema", "Epidemic typhus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Long?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Fever", "Myocardial infarction", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wesley Willis?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Malaria", "Gallbladder cancer", "Liver tumour"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Timothy J. Russert?", "answers": ["Endometrial cancer", "Peritonitis", "Myocardial infarction", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carlos Castaneda?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Liver tumour", "Head and neck cancer", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Margaret Lockwood?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Bronchopneumonia", "Accidental Fire", "Ischaemic heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nick Adams?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Cardiomegaly", "Cancer of the larynx", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Billy Fury?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Cystic fibrosis", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Francis Crick?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Colorectal cancer", "Dementia pugilistica"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Josh Weston?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Yellow fever", "Alcoholism", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William S. Burroughs?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Brain Cancer", "Hyperthermia", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rene Rivkin?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Bubonic plague", "Drug overdose", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alan Ladd?", "answers": ["Kidney cancer", "Pancreatic cancer", "Drug overdose", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carl Betz?", "answers": ["Testicular cancer", "Lung cancer", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ram\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Cerebral edema", "Respiratory Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ram\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Stomach cancer", "Thrombus", "Intestinal Obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kitty Foxx?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Septic shock", "Crohn's disease", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dennis Cleveland Stewart?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Dysentery", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Audrey Williams?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Myocardial infarction", "Heart failure", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Ho?", "answers": ["Aortic aneurysm", "Heart failure", "Pleurisy", "Cholangiocarcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Ho?", "answers": ["Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Cardiovascular disease", "Anorexia nervosa", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bela Lugosi?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Aortic dissection", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Juliet Prowse?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Pancreatic cancer", "Schistosomiasis", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Bessell?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Drug overdose", "Aortic aneurysm", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Toy Caldwell?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Injury", "Myocardial infarction", "Influenza"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lee Atwater?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Brain tumor", "Poisoning", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Beverley Cross?", "answers": ["Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Aneurysm", "Insulinoma", "Iatrogenesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Laurence Dunbar?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Spinal tumor", "Tuberculosis", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yokozuna?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Pulmonary edema", "Cardiac surgery", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Lawford?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Epilepsy", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Lawford?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Wound", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Adams?", "answers": ["Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Coronary artery disease", "Seizure", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Adams?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Paraquat", "Tongue Cancer", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Adams?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Arteriosclerosis", "Anorexia nervosa", "Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rick Majerus?", "answers": ["Cardiomyopathy", "Injury", "Heart failure", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Avalanna Routh?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Cyanide poisoning", "Thrombus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brian Piccolo?", "answers": ["Shock", "Perforated ulcer", "Acute renal failure", "Testicular cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brian Piccolo?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Lung cancer", "Appendix cancer", "Physical abuse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bubba Smith?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Cystic fibrosis", "Drug overdose", "Skin cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Floyd Cramer?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Aortic aneurysm", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rob Grill?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Chest pain", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anthony Shadid?", "answers": ["Asthma", "Dementia", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chill Wills?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Appendix cancer", "Accidental Fire", "Tongue Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris Whitley?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Lung cancer", "Cardiomegaly", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anthony Burger?", "answers": ["Tetanus", "Alcoholism", "Thrombosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shemp Howard?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Cardiomegaly", "Myocardial infarction", "Huntington's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Holmes?", "answers": ["Edema", "AIDS", "Alcoholism", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ron O'Neal?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Pancreatic cancer", "Huntington's disease", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jos\u00e9 Alfredo Jim\u00e9nez?", "answers": ["Atherosclerosis", "Hyperthermia", "Binge drinking", "Hepatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Niels Henrik David Bohr?", "answers": ["Fournier gangrene", "Choking", "Rheumatic fever", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aeschylus?", "answers": ["Traumatic brain injury", "Brain damage", "Smallpox", "Septic shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tim Richmond?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Bubonic plague", "Infectious disease", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tim Richmond?", "answers": ["Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Cerebral edema", "Exhaustion", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Trevor Goddard?", "answers": ["Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Typhoid fever", "Drug overdose", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Craig Jones?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rod Steiger?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Debility", "Encephalitis", "Tongue Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tim McIntire?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Pulmonary edema", "Aneurysm", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rudolf Nureyev?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Head and neck cancer", "AIDS", "Lobar pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sally Hayfron?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Renal failure", "Encephalitis", "Iatrogenesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lyndon B. Johnson?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Paraquat", "Hyperthermia", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Babe Ruth?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Cirrhosis", "Esophageal cancer", "Accidental Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenneth Williams?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Epidemic typhus", "Malaria", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenneth Williams?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Kidney cancer", "Coronary artery disease", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Gleason?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Stroke", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mark Belanger?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Accidental Fire", "Cervical cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of August Schellenberg?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Acute renal failure", "Myocardial infarction", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shirley Hemphill?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Arteriosclerosis", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rue McClanahan?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Muscular dystrophy", "Morphine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rue McClanahan?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Cardiac surgery", "Stroke", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rue McClanahan?", "answers": ["Physical abuse", "Bleeding", "Lymphoma", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Northern Calloway?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Heart failure", "Poison", "Injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Estelle Getty?", "answers": ["Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Colon Cancer", "Nephropathy", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ann Sothern?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Burn", "Spinal tumor", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Peel?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Malnutrition", "Myocardial infarction", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Feroz Khan?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Skin cancer", "Lung cancer", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Feroz Khan?", "answers": ["Peritonitis", "Cardiac surgery", "Alzheimer's disease", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Patrice O'Neal?", "answers": ["Edema", "Ballistic trauma", "Systemic scleroderma", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eileen Brennan?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Tongue Cancer", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Hodgkin's lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Smedley Butler?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "Cystic fibrosis", "Cancer", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Elizabeth of York?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Childbirth", "Alcohol intoxication", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jean-Dominique Bauby?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Thrombus", "Hyperthermia", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jean-Dominique Bauby?", "answers": ["Tetanus", "Motor neuron disease", "Pneumonia", "Poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jake Adam York?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Septic shock", "Cardiac arrest", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Kroc?", "answers": ["Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Heart failure", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Kroc?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Alcohol intoxication", "Dengue fever", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Virginia Woolf?", "answers": ["Encephalopathy", "Drowning", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Howard Ashman?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "AIDS", "Colon Cancer", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Graf?", "answers": ["Choking", "Myocardial infarction", "Dementia pugilistica", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Stack?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Arthritis", "Brain damage", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bernard Bresslaw?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Hyperthermia", "Anaphylaxis", "Aplastic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sotigui Kouyat\u00e9?", "answers": ["Insulinoma", "Respiratory disease", "Smoke inhalation", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Demme?", "answers": ["Appendix cancer", "Drug overdose", "Insulinoma", "Myasthenia gravis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Demme?", "answers": ["Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Myocardial infarction", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stan Rogers?", "answers": ["Renal Cancer", "Smoke inhalation", "Meningitis", "Aplastic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Heather O'Rourke?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Hypothermia", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Heather O'Rourke?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Dysentery", "Cardiac arrest", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Heather O'Rourke?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "Aneurysm", "Anaphylaxis", "Septic shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Heather O'Rourke?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Iatrogenesis", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Whale?", "answers": ["Crohn's disease", "Drowning", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony Gubba?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Leukemia", "Aortic dissection", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James A. Garfield?", "answers": ["Skin cancer", "Spinal tumor", "Cervical cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James A. Garfield?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Cardiovascular disease", "Arsenic poisoning", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James A. Garfield?", "answers": ["Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Pneumonia", "Asthma", "Accidental Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Brodie?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "Multiple myeloma", "Bone cancer", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jill Ireland?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Surgery", "Breast cancer", "Pneumothorax"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Douglas Engelbart?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Wild?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sid James?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Congenital heart defect", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Sellers?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Brain damage", "Drowning", "Thrombus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mukesh?", "answers": ["Tetanus", "Myocardial infarction", "Pancreatic cancer", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fernando Lamas?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Pancreatic cancer", "Carbon monoxide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of \"Chris \"\"Mac Daddy\"\" Kelly\"?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Syphilis", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Oral Roberts?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Pneumonia", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Talia Castellano?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Fever", "Ischaemic heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Ginty?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Crohn's disease", "Childbirth", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Abraham Maslow?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Binge drinking", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jesse Pearson?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Melanoma", "Cancer", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Elizabeth Edwards?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Mesothelioma", "Diverticulosis", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lucille Ball?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Aortic dissection", "Smoke inhalation", "Testicular cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Gillen?", "answers": ["Fever", "Liver tumour", "AIDS", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gregory Isaacs?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Multiple myeloma", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Soni Pabla?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Hypertension", "Meningitis", "Polymyalgia rheumatica"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rudolf Diesel?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Drowning", "Respiratory disease", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Frost?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Iatrogenesis", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Audrey Meadows?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Chronic renal failure", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Thaw?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Tuberculosis", "Throat cancer", "Pernicious anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dinah Shore?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Ovarian cancer", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Francis Bacon?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Pneumonia", "Gangrene", "Infectious disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Diosdado Macapagal?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Melanoma", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Diosdado Macapagal?", "answers": ["Post-polio syndrome", "Uremia", "Pneumonia", "Embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kim Perrot?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Lung cancer", "Dysentery", "Multiple myeloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of S. Manivannan?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Motor neuron disease", "Anorexia nervosa", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris Farley?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Epidural hematoma", "Drug overdose", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris Farley?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Arsenic poisoning", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Benjamin Britten?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Mesothelioma", "Pulmonary embolism", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Hunt?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Stroke", "Cardiac surgery", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of The Rev?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Typhoid fever", "Pyaemia", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Ludlum?", "answers": ["Pulmonary aspiration", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Pneumonia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sugar Ray Robinson?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Ovarian cancer", "Anemia", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sugar Ray Robinson?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Blunt trauma", "Alzheimer's disease", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Villard?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "AIDS", "Infection", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Villard?", "answers": ["Crohn's disease", "Pneumonia", "Drug overdose", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rob Hall?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Bacterial pneumonia", "Anorexia nervosa", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ed Bradley?", "answers": ["Kawasaki disease", "Cardiovascular disease", "Leukemia", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vonetta McGee?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Rheumatic fever", "Cardiac arrest", "Rheumatic fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Billie Thomas?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Trichinosis", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony Beckley?", "answers": ["Meningitis", "Polycythemia", "Cancer", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Geoffrey Hutchings?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Head and neck cancer", "Meningitis", "Epilepsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nate Dogg?", "answers": ["Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Gigantism", "Myocardial infarction", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jawaharlal Nehru?", "answers": ["Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Cirrhosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Thrombus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jawaharlal Nehru?", "answers": ["Endometrial cancer", "Tetanus", "Binge drinking", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of A. A. Allen?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Alcoholism", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of A. A. Allen?", "answers": ["Poison", "Crohn's disease", "Liver failure", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Gandolfini?", "answers": ["Meningitis", "Myocardial infarction", "Aortic aneurysm", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harry Reems?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Epidemic typhus", "Pancreatic cancer", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Kelly?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Head and neck cancer", "Multiple myeloma", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Coburn?", "answers": ["Synovial sarcoma", "Chest pain", "Cardiomyopathy", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Howard Taft?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Pancreatitis", "Cardiovascular disease", "Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Rakoff?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Cancer", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Malcolm X?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Throat cancer", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ibn al-Khattab?", "answers": ["Suffocation", "Poison", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Starvation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ibn al-Khattab?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Congenital heart defect", "Head and neck cancer", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Norman Fell?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Skin cancer", "Cancer", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jacqueline du Pr\u00e9?", "answers": ["Cardiomyopathy", "Barbiturate overdose", "Pneumothorax", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Percy Bysshe Shelley?", "answers": ["Epilepsy", "Drowning", "Diarrhea", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Cazale?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Exhaustion", "Starvation", "Cancer of the larynx"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Cazale?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Embolism", "Lung cancer", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Cazale?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Cancer", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenny Rankin?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Lung cancer", "Hepatitis", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Caron Keating?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Blunt trauma", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Euell Gibbons?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Diverticulosis", "Congenital heart defect", "Wound"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Cahill?", "answers": ["Traumatic brain injury", "Respiratory failure", "Internal bleeding", "Marfan syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kim Peek?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Skin cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kim Peek?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Pyaemia", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vivian Vance?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Systemic scleroderma", "Exhaustion", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vivian Vance?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "Bone cancer", "Pancreatitis", "Accidental Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vivian Vance?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Breast cancer", "Renal failure", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eddie Gilbert?", "answers": ["Leiomyosarcoma", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris LeDoux?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Mesothelioma", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lawrence Welk?", "answers": ["Arsenic poisoning", "Pneumonia", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Hegyes?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Bladder cancer", "Brain Cancer", "Viral pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Deborah Walley?", "answers": ["Debility", "Esophageal cancer", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Anal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Luther Perkins?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Meningitis", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alvin Smith?", "answers": ["Poison", "Accidental Fire", "Pleurisy", "Cholera"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Darrell Porter?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Bronchitis", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Hunter?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Multiple sclerosis", "Cancer", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Hunter?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Stomach cancer", "Seizure", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne of Cleves?", "answers": ["Burn", "Cancer", "Liver disease", "Syphilis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Dolby?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Renal failure", "Heart cancer", "Coronary thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Monroe?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Encephalopathy", "Respiratory arrest", "Acute renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Monroe?", "answers": ["Alcoholism", "Fever", "Heart failure", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Anning?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Liver disease", "Uremia", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jade Goody?", "answers": ["Respiratory Infection", "Cervical cancer", "Exhaustion", "Multiple myeloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Austin Box?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Drug overdose", "Coronary artery disease", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenneth Mars?", "answers": ["Lupus erythematosus", "Drug overdose", "Pancreatic cancer", "Embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Booker?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Pulmonary edema", "B-cell lymphoma", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hernando de Soto?", "answers": ["Fever", "Spinal tumor", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dana Key?", "answers": ["Cor pulmonale", "Thrombus", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nico?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Alcoholism", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Morgan?", "answers": ["Nephritis", "Morphine", "Myocardial infarction", "Hepatitis A"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barry White?", "answers": ["Paraquat", "Barbiturate overdose", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Soupy Sales?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Typhoid fever", "Morphine", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wayland Flowers?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "AIDS", "Leukemia", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wayland Flowers?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Encephalitis", "Cancer", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Larsen?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Drug overdose", "Anorexia nervosa", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Frazier?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Liver cancer", "Cerebral edema", "Trichinosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dara Singh?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Viral pneumonia", "Myocardial infarction", "Tetanus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aleister Crowley?", "answers": ["Cor pulmonale", "Respiratory Infection", "Heart cancer", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Josephine Cohan?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Cardiovascular disease", "Gangrene", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Red Sovine?", "answers": ["Aneurysm", "Lymphoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Coretta Scott King?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Poisoning", "Diverticulosis", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Allen Ginsberg?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Malnutrition", "Cancer of the larynx", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Allen Ginsberg?", "answers": ["Intracranial aneurysm", "Cystic fibrosis", "Hepatitis", "Dementia pugilistica"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Constance Bennett?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Bright's disease", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Henry Gibson?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Cancer", "Barbiturate overdose", "Rheumatic fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Shelley?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Bronchitis", "Brain tumor", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Grigori Rasputin?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Brain tumor", "Lobar pneumonia", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Grigori Rasputin?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Grigori Rasputin?", "answers": ["Poison", "Seizure", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Denver?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Epilepsy", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Pyaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Denver?", "answers": ["Hepatitis C", "Post-polio syndrome", "Pneumonia", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Henry Fonda?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Cardiovascular disease", "Septic shock", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Adam Yauch?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Colon Cancer", "Multiple sclerosis", "Systemic lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Tyler?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Stroke", "Kidney Disease", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barry Cowsill?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Drowning", "Smallpox", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Annabel Tollman?", "answers": ["Coronary artery disease", "Thrombosis", "Smoke inhalation", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vivian Stanshall?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Accidental Fire", "Ballistic trauma", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kevin Carter?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Respiratory Infection", "Carbon monoxide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frankie Gaye?", "answers": ["Choking", "Suffocation", "Gigantism", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jenny Likens?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Aneurysm", "Renal Cancer", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dick Clark?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Paraquat", "Cardiomyopathy", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kathy Lutz?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Emphysema", "Starvation", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dennis Hopper?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Surgery", "Coronary artery disease", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lefty Frizzell?", "answers": ["Mesothelioma", "Thyroid cancer", "Stroke", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Zelmo Beaty?", "answers": ["Lupus erythematosus", "Pancreatitis", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shelby Grant?", "answers": ["Pneumothorax", "Alcohol intoxication", "Kidney cancer", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Elisa Bridges?", "answers": ["Coronary thrombosis", "Cardiomegaly", "Drug overdose", "Trichinosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Rennie?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Aortic aneurysm", "Bleeding", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Knight?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Colorectal cancer", "Ovarian cancer", "Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Knight?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Hypertension", "Cancer", "Viral pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pete McCarthy?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Childbirth", "Pancreatic cancer", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Patrick Saint-Eloi?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Congenital heart defect", "Hepatitis A"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gracie Allen?", "answers": ["Cancer of the larynx", "Myocardial infarction", "Cystic fibrosis", "Starvation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Rheumatic fever", "Seizure", "Drug overdose", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of June Allyson?", "answers": ["Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Brain damage", "Respiratory failure", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of June Allyson?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Epidemic typhus", "Dementia pugilistica", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Morrison?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Cystic fibrosis", "Respiratory arrest", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Morrison?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Pancreatitis", "Rheumatic fever", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chester McGlockton?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Falling", "Myocardial infarction", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cole Porter?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Renal failure", "Smallpox", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nick Drake?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Sleep apnea", "Drug overdose", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rodney Harvey?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Suffocation", "Puerperal fever", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Ingle?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Cancer", "Malaria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Kennedy Toole?", "answers": ["Lupus erythematosus", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Head and neck cancer", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Laura Nyro?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Ovarian cancer", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wes Montgomery?", "answers": ["Multiple myeloma", "Myocardial infarction", "Edema", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alberta Nelson?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Pneumonia", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fred Sonic Smith?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Smallpox", "Cyanide poisoning", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony De Vit?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Polycythemia", "Myasthenia gravis", "Encephalitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Candy?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Poisoning", "Atherosclerosis", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Levi Stubbs?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Cirrhosis", "Stroke", "Hepatitis C"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Levi Stubbs?", "answers": ["Thrombus", "Cancer", "Kidney Disease", "Pyaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Merle Oberon?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Congenital heart defect", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Benjamin Orr?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Pancreatic cancer", "Heart cancer", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Flynn?", "answers": ["Bacterial pneumonia", "Drowning", "Pulmonary embolism", "Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Flynn?", "answers": ["Choking", "Aortic dissection", "Myocardial infarction", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fernando Pessoa?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Cyanide poisoning", "Cirrhosis", "Hepatocellular carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Floyd Collins?", "answers": ["Edema", "Cystic fibrosis", "Hypothermia", "Starvation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Frann?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Diabetes mellitus", "Myocardial infarction", "Cor pulmonale"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Patty Donahue?", "answers": ["Craniocerebral Trauma", "Burn", "Muscular dystrophy", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Murphy?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Pleurisy", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pablo Vitar?", "answers": ["Pernicious anemia", "Injury", "Colorectal cancer", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Douglas Adams?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Asthma", "Asphyxia", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Walter Burley Griffin?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Pancreatic cancer", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Peritonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Flip Wilson?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Anorexia nervosa", "Toxoplasmosis", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hamnet Shakespeare?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Fever", "Dementia pugilistica", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shirley Jackson?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Emphysema", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Osama bin Laden?", "answers": ["Cardiomyopathy", "Ballistic trauma", "Aortic dissection", "Carbon monoxide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nabal?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Myocardial infarction", "Bleeding", "Dementia with Lewy bodies"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Snow?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Stroke", "Hepatitis C", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Jamerson?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Pneumonia", "Childbirth", "Intestinal Obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Jamerson?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Pneumothorax", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenneth E. Hagin?", "answers": ["Wound", "Polycythemia", "Injury", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenneth E. Hagin?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Congenital heart defect", "Drowning", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chrissy Amphlett?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Insulinoma", "Encephalitis", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Burton?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Liver tumour", "Liver cancer", "Starvation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Duke Kahanamoku?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Burn", "Thrombosis", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jane Addams?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Prostate cancer", "Cancer", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nathanael Greene?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Respiratory arrest", "Smallpox", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ashley Nwosu?", "answers": ["Arsenic poisoning", "Alcoholism", "Liver disease", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Keenan Milton?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Cancer of the larynx", "Sepsis", "Acral lentiginous melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robbin Crosby?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Uremia", "Colorectal cancer", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robbin Crosby?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Sleep apnea", "Lupus erythematosus", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Denis Forest?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Hepatitis A", "Liver failure", "Myelodysplastic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Kelly?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Starvation", "Smallpox", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeremy Brett?", "answers": ["Aplastic anemia", "Heart cancer", "Heart failure", "Aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeremy Brett?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Tongue Cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ronnie Barker?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Trichinosis", "Respiratory Infection", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ronnie Barker?", "answers": ["Nephritis", "Cardiovascular disease", "Infection", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris Hallam?", "answers": ["Cardiomyopathy", "Cancer", "Hepatitis A", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Audrey Mestre?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Bronchitis", "Drowning", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vilasrao Deshmukh?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Renal Cancer", "Sleep apnea", "Accidental Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Van McCoy?", "answers": ["Multiple myeloma", "Viral pneumonia", "Myocardial infarction", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Ripley?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Respiratory arrest", "Epilepsy", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Mees?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Hitchens?", "answers": ["Smoke inhalation", "Esophageal cancer", "Kawasaki disease", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rodel Naval?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "AIDS", "Muscular dystrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nicole DeHuff?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Kidney Disease", "Pneumonia", "Glioblastoma multiforme"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johnny Unitas?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Throat cancer", "Diabetes mellitus", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nikki Sudden?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Sleep apnea", "Myocardial infarction", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Waylon Jennings?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Diabetes mellitus", "Binge drinking", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Claude Rains?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Alzheimer's disease", "Pulmonary embolism", "Acral lentiginous melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vinod Mehra?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Oral cancer", "Asthma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stieg Larsson?", "answers": ["Blunt trauma", "Bronchopneumonia", "Epilepsy", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Penn?", "answers": ["Dengue fever", "Viral pneumonia", "Stroke", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sabu Dastagir?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Asthma", "Celiac disease", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Washington Vanderbilt II?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Asphyxia", "Dehydration", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pamela Courson?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Aneurysm", "Bright's disease", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roc\u00edo D\u00farcal?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Thyroid cancer", "Uterine cancer", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joseph Cotten?", "answers": ["Ruptured Aneurysm", "Throat cancer", "Barbiturate overdose", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joseph Cotten?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Encephalitis", "Liver cancer", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Ihnat?", "answers": ["Trichinosis", "Meningitis", "Myocardial infarction", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of R. J. Mitchell?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Colorectal cancer", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of R. J. Mitchell?", "answers": ["Multiple myeloma", "Celiac disease", "Paraquat", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Claudette Colbert?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Emphysema", "Stroke", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eric Liddell?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Brain tumor", "Diabetes mellitus", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pro Hart?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Peritonitis", "Suffocation", "Liver disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sylvia Plath?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Cholera", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Carbon monoxide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lynden David Hall?", "answers": ["Smoke inhalation", "Meningitis", "Uremia", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Conrad Bain?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Arsenic poisoning", "Bladder cancer", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carlos Hathcock?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Pleurisy", "Pleurisy", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dudley Moore?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Asthma", "Pneumonia", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dudley Moore?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Myasthenia gravis", "Skin cancer", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rainer Werner Fassbinder?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "B-cell lymphoma", "Anal cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rainer Werner Fassbinder?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Cardiac surgery", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cantinflas?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Skull fracture", "Esophageal cancer", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Jennings?", "answers": ["Burn", "Lung cancer", "Pulmonary edema", "Systemic lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Simon MacCorkindale?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Sepsis", "Cardiovascular disease", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Simon MacCorkindale?", "answers": ["Fever", "Colorectal cancer", "Starvation", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jonathan Edwards?", "answers": ["Smallpox", "Head and neck cancer", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of \"\"\"Dr. Death\"\" Steve Williams\"?", "answers": ["Poison", "Cancer", "Throat cancer", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mobutu Sese Seko?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Poison", "Prostate cancer", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yash Chopra?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Septic shock", "Ballistic trauma", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yash Chopra?", "answers": ["Celiac disease", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Woodrow Wilson?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Stroke", "Alcoholism", "Trichinosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ross Clifton?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Drowning", "Respiratory Infection", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Raghuvaran?", "answers": ["Smallpox", "Cardiac arrest", "Muscular dystrophy", "Lobar pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of P. V. Narasimha Rao?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Respiratory disease", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Napoleon II?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Influenza", "Tuberculosis", "Kidney cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Wallace Lincoln?", "answers": ["Cardiac surgery", "Typhoid fever", "Bleeding", "Binge drinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chuck Muncie?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Suffocation", "Nephropathy", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Romy Schneider?", "answers": ["Physical abuse", "Myocardial infarction", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ernest Borgnine?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Chronic renal failure", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eddie Kendricks?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Cancer", "Lung cancer", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chat Silayan?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Spinal tumor", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Bindon?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Pancreatic cancer", "Drug overdose", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Bindon?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Tongue Cancer", "Anal cancer", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joseph Kearns?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Binge drinking", "Injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Henry Lawson?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Barbiturate", "Head and neck cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Shearston?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Anorexia nervosa", "Malaria", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Haley?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Myocardial infarction", "Shock", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Megna?", "answers": ["Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Prostate cancer", "Epilepsy", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Persis Khambatta?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Bronchitis", "Myocardial infarction", "Hepatocellular carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sonja Henie?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Influenza", "Leukemia", "Renal Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Shenar?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Bright's disease", "Fever", "Insulinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Thelonious Monk?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Bubonic plague", "B-cell lymphoma", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rory Calhoun?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Smoke inhalation", "Dysentery", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rory Calhoun?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Esophageal cancer", "Dementia pugilistica", "Embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pierre Trudeau?", "answers": ["Heart cancer", "Childbirth", "Atherosclerosis", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lynda Wiesmeier?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Physical abuse", "Brain Cancer", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Charles?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Hepatitis", "Alcohol intoxication", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Wollstonecraft?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Colon Cancer", "Multiple sclerosis", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Wollstonecraft?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Peritonitis", "Appendix cancer", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Greg Morris?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Pancreatitis", "Brain Cancer", "Cyanide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wangari Maathai?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Diverticulosis", "Huntington's disease", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bonnie Franklin?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Throat cancer", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fred MacMurray?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Brain Cancer", "Barbiturate", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fred MacMurray?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Asthma", "Leukemia", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Louis Braille?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Epidural hematoma", "Tuberculosis", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Laura Ingalls Wilder?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Diabetes mellitus", "Cystic fibrosis", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Peritonitis", "Mesothelioma", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jean-Jacques Rousseau?", "answers": ["Huntington's disease", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Bleeding", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Louis Stevenson?", "answers": ["Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Diane Elizabeth MacMillan?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Cancer", "Diabetes mellitus", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shari Lewis?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Viral pneumonia", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shari Lewis?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Injury", "Uterine cancer", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shari Lewis?", "answers": ["Craniocerebral Trauma", "Lymphoma", "Accidental Fire", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sylvia Kristel?", "answers": ["Intracranial aneurysm", "Renal failure", "Stomach cancer", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sylvia Kristel?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Esophageal cancer", "Drug overdose", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Les Dawson?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Stomach cancer", "Encephalitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Powell?", "answers": ["Kidney Disease", "Pyaemia", "Kawasaki disease", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tim Hetherington?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Trichinosis", "Ballistic trauma", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Benny Goodman?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Arteriosclerosis", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ken Curtis?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cass Elliot?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Chest pain", "Aplastic anemia", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Soumaya Domit Gemayel?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Cancer", "Injury", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bill W.?", "answers": ["Aortic aneurysm", "Ovarian cancer", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Jordan?", "answers": ["Encephalitis", "Pneumothorax", "Brain tumor", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary I of England?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Bleeding", "Celiac disease", "Cholera"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Randy Pausch?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Cancer of the larynx", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mick Lally?", "answers": ["B-cell lymphoma", "Emphysema", "Kidney cancer", "Pernicious anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dorothy Parker?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Cardiomyopathy", "Infectious disease", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harry Kalas?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Cholera", "Myocardial infarction", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Audrey Hepburn?", "answers": ["Physical abuse", "Appendix cancer", "Gigantism", "Ischaemic heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hugh Beaumont?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Dengue fever", "Myocardial infarction", "Gallbladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cleavon Little?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Oral cancer", "Thyroid cancer", "Traumatic brain injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Billy MacKenzie?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Drug overdose", "Renal Cancer", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mother Teresa?", "answers": ["Kidney Disease", "Trichinosis", "Cardiac arrest", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sparky Anderson?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Infectious disease", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gregor Mendel?", "answers": ["Iatrogenesis", "Exhaustion", "Liver cancer", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Katharine Graham?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Trauma", "Cholera", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buck Owens?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Dehydration", "Lupus erythematosus", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alexander the Great?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Insulinoma", "Fever", "Kawasaki disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Warhol?", "answers": ["Coronary occlusion", "Dementia pugilistica", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Orson Welles?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Dementia pugilistica", "Myocardial infarction", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nancy Walker?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "Injury", "Lung cancer", "Myelodysplastic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marti Caine?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Head and neck cancer", "Cancer", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marti Caine?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Diabetes mellitus", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Iatrogenesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Li Bai?", "answers": ["Bright's disease", "Brain tumor", "Cancer", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Layton?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Throat cancer", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Parveen Babi?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Huntington's disease", "Gangrene", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Augustus Pablo?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Myasthenia gravis", "Coronary occlusion", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kevin Feeney?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Brain Cancer", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eva Cassidy?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Ovarian cancer", "Cancer", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eva Cassidy?", "answers": ["Head and neck cancer", "Tongue Cancer", "Skin cancer", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gilda Radner?", "answers": ["Testicular cancer", "Brain Cancer", "Ovarian cancer", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ofra Haza?", "answers": ["Crohn's disease", "Lobar pneumonia", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vince Edwards?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Colon Cancer", "Kawasaki disease", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tommy Bolin?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Drug overdose", "Cervical cancer", "Seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sue Randall?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Drug overdose", "Lung cancer", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Blaise Alexander?", "answers": ["Craniocerebral Trauma", "Post-polio syndrome", "Throat cancer", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeanne Crain?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Diarrhea", "Myocardial infarction", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Geraldine Ferraro?", "answers": ["Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Multiple myeloma", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Schistosomiasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buddy Ebsen?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Arteriosclerosis", "Appendix cancer", "Skin cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jos\u00e9 Lim\u00f3n?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Acute renal failure", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Cor pulmonale"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harvey Korman?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Blunt trauma", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Joe Hill?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Tetanus", "Insulinoma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bill Cowsill?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Shock", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alex Karras?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Renal failure", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Princess Charlotte of Wales?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Esophageal cancer", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Thompson Oliha?", "answers": ["Head and neck cancer", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Malaria", "Viral pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carter Stanley?", "answers": ["Aplastic anemia", "Cirrhosis", "Nephropathy", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mario Lanza?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Anorexia nervosa", "Testicular cancer", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mario Lanza?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Pulmonary embolism", "Throat cancer", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Carter?", "answers": ["Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Childbirth", "Brain Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wilt Chamberlain?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Insulinoma", "Appendix cancer", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Bront\u00eb?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Tuberculosis", "Dysentery", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alfred Wegener?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Heart failure", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Stone?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Myocardial infarction", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joseph Stalin?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Melanoma", "Stroke", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bernard Manning?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Kawasaki disease", "Renal failure", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Glasser?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Respiratory failure", "Acute renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marie Curie?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Myasthenia gravis", "Trauma", "Aplastic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Erik Friborg?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Debility", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Solveig Dommartin?", "answers": ["Endometrial cancer", "Respiratory failure", "Multiple myeloma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Hickenlooper?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Acute pancreatitis", "Drug overdose", "Uremia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward VIII of the United Kingdom?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Arteriosclerosis", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Louis XIV of France?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Diarrhea", "Pneumonia", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hoke Howell?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Influenza", "Alzheimer's disease", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Ritter?", "answers": ["Aortic dissection", "Epidemic typhus", "Trauma", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Ritter?", "answers": ["Septic shock", "Pleurisy", "Cardiovascular disease", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Liberace?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "AIDS", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Simone de Beauvoir?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Stomach cancer", "Coronary occlusion", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of \u00c9variste Galois?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Embolism", "Yellow fever", "Peritonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Victor Wong?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Surgery", "Heart failure", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of J. Michael Riva?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Physical abuse", "Infection", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of M. Scott Peck?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Bone cancer", "Cirrhosis", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of M. Scott Peck?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Choking", "Pancreatitis", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of M. Scott Peck?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Parkinson's disease", "Respiratory Infection", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Benny?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Lymphoma", "Arthritis", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Billy Powell?", "answers": ["Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Cancer", "Post-polio syndrome", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Virginia Weidler?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Cardiomyopathy", "Hypothermia", "Cervical cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Garrincha?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Cor pulmonale", "Hepatitis A", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Korey Stringer?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Binge drinking", "Hyperthermia", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Clerk Maxwell?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Trauma", "Iatrogenesis", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Clerk Maxwell?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Nephritis", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Khalil Gibran?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Polycythemia", "Hepatitis", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Khalil Gibran?", "answers": ["Aortic aneurysm", "Respiratory Infection", "Tuberculosis", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Johnson?", "answers": ["Cardiac surgery", "Encephalitis", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Baudelaire?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Toxoplasmosis", "Bright's disease", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wong Ming Yang?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Acute pancreatitis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don LaFontaine?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Iatrogenesis", "Pneumothorax", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jackie Wilson?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Myocardial infarction", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jackie Wilson?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Pneumonia", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Pernicious anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Todd Bennett?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Physical abuse", "Arteriosclerosis", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alfred Nobel?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Gigantism", "Lobar pneumonia", "Cor pulmonale"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robin Nedwell?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Sleep apnea", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Coronary thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jean Arthur?", "answers": ["Pleurisy", "Cardiovascular disease", "Schistosomiasis", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Levon Helm?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Gangrene", "Anal cancer", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Levon Helm?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Cancer", "Cholera", "Wound"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tennessee Williams?", "answers": ["Choking", "Hepatitis", "Pneumothorax", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Henry V of England?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Fever", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Humayun Ahmed?", "answers": ["Cholangiocarcinoma", "Cystic fibrosis", "Cor pulmonale", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ty Cobb?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Prostate cancer", "Hypertensive heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Huddie William Ledbetter?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Viral pneumonia", "Wound", "Poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Victor Hugo?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Cerebral edema", "Falling", "Myelodysplastic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wilson Pickett?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Myocardial infarction", "Hepatitis C", "Coronary thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Carlin?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Nephritis", "Myocardial infarction", "Syphilis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Carlin?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Liver disease", "Kidney cancer", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Carlin?", "answers": ["Lupus erythematosus", "Cor pulmonale", "Heart failure", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Entwistle?", "answers": ["Atherosclerosis", "Drug overdose", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Entwistle?", "answers": ["Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Myocardial infarction", "Pulmonary aspiration", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mazhar Khan?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Traumatic brain injury", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wolfman Jack?", "answers": ["Fever", "Choking", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Grover Cleveland?", "answers": ["Smallpox", "Syphilis", "Myocardial infarction", "Acral lentiginous melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy Lichtenstein?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Rheumatic fever", "Aneurysm", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Baxter?", "answers": ["Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Anorexia nervosa", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shel Silverstein?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Iatrogenesis", "Hyperthermia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerome Robbins?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Systemic scleroderma", "Iatrogenesis", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Thomas Hobbes?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Stroke", "Paraquat", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kevin DuBrow?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Dementia pugilistica", "Drug overdose", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony Randall?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Pneumonia", "Cancer of the larynx", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Darwin?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michal Friedman?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Aspiration pneumonia", "Childbirth", "Bright's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Bennett?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "AIDS", "Stroke", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alec Guinness?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Bronchopneumonia", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alec Guinness?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Cervical cancer", "Liver tumour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alec Guinness?", "answers": ["Malnutrition", "Liver cancer", "Diarrhea", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pablo Neruda?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Prostate cancer", "Fournier gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pablo Neruda?", "answers": ["Shock", "Coronary occlusion", "Aortic aneurysm", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris Antley?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Chronic renal failure", "Drug overdose", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cochin Haneefa?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Drug overdose", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stanley Sandler?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Leukemia", "Smoke inhalation", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lee Van Cleef?", "answers": ["Exhaustion", "Pyaemia", "Myocardial infarction", "Epidemic typhus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ada Lovelace?", "answers": ["Uterine cancer", "Mesothelioma", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Rheumatic fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Jobs?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Insulinoma", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Polycythemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Rose?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Nephritis", "Lymphoma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pier Angeli?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Drug overdose", "Toxoplasmosis", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Whitney Blake?", "answers": ["Binge drinking", "Cancer", "Huntington's disease", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Whitney Blake?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Cyanide poisoning", "Falling", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sim\u00f3n Bol\u00edvar?", "answers": ["Coronary artery disease", "Pneumothorax", "Pneumonia", "Encephalitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dan Rowan?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Diarrhea", "Rheumatic fever", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Le Corbusier?", "answers": ["Pernicious anemia", "Motor neuron disease", "Dengue fever", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Walter Hawkins?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Diverticulosis", "Myasthenia gravis", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of LaWanda Page?", "answers": ["Cystic fibrosis", "Diabetes mellitus", "Renal Cancer", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Colin Winkelmann?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Renal Cancer", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ingrid Bergman?", "answers": ["Appendix cancer", "Lymphoma", "Renal Cancer", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ingrid Bergman?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Breast cancer", "Asthma", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dan James White?", "answers": ["Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Skin cancer", "Cardiac arrest", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Healy?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Trichinosis", "Post-polio syndrome", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peggy Lee?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peggy Lee?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Cardiovascular disease", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Encephalitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peggy Lee?", "answers": ["B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Hepatitis C", "Cervical cancer", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bruce Lee?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Malnutrition", "Cerebral edema", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joey Ramone?", "answers": ["Respiratory Infection", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Thrombus", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anselmo Feleppa?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Polycythemia", "Kidney cancer", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dolphy?", "answers": ["Peritonitis", "Pneumothorax", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Muir?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Renal Cancer", "Lung cancer", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Majel Barrett?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Motor neuron disease", "Leukemia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mikey Welsh?", "answers": ["B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Enteritis", "Lung cancer", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Colonel Sanders?", "answers": ["Epilepsy", "Pneumonia", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Colonel Sanders?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Anal cancer", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Milburn Stone?", "answers": ["Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Muscular dystrophy", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Oodgeroo Noonuccal?", "answers": ["B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Liver failure", "Cancer", "Marfan syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Maureen Starkey Tigrett?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Diarrhea", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lester Bangs?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Kidney cancer", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Motor neuron disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Huo Yuanjia?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Pancreatitis", "Infection", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tim Buckley?", "answers": ["Pulmonary aspiration", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Drug overdose", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wade Nichols?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Encephalitis", "Burn", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Allen Lanier?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Cervical cancer", "Atherosclerosis", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dana Reeve?", "answers": ["Melanoma", "Coronary thrombosis", "Lung cancer", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barry Roberts?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Encephalitis", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Shaw?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Asphyxia", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Simon Cadell?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Bladder cancer", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Adam Petty?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Starvation", "Diverticulosis", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jean-Baptiste Lully?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Aplastic anemia", "Gangrene", "Thyroid cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leslie Nielsen?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Pneumonia", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Syphilis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alexander Litvinenko?", "answers": ["Poison", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Brain tumor", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Brain Cancer", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hu Yaobang?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Bubonic plague", "Myocardial infarction", "Tongue Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Malcolm McClaren?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Yellow fever", "Mesothelioma", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Malcolm McClaren?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Thrombus", "Crohn's disease", "Hodgkin's lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harry Nilsson?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Aortic aneurysm", "Myocardial infarction", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aimee Semple McPherson?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Atherosclerosis", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aimee Semple McPherson?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Liver disease", "Bright's disease", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Oliver?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Lung cancer", "Bone cancer", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Buckley?", "answers": ["Choking", "Respiratory failure", "Myasthenia gravis", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James K. Polk?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Cholera", "Paraquat", "Cervical cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hugh O'Connor?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Drug overdose", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alex Taylor?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Henson?", "answers": ["Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Bacterial pneumonia", "Multiple sclerosis", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Henson?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Cardiovascular disease", "Testicular cancer", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Henson?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Sepsis", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Renal Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Meredith MacRae?", "answers": ["Accidental Fire", "Meningitis", "Brain tumor", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy Scheider?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Brain tumor", "Multiple myeloma", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Montgomery?", "answers": ["Pleurisy", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Cancer", "Poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jon Lord?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Esophageal cancer", "Gigantism", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jon Lord?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Bladder cancer", "Burn", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Allen?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Barbiturate overdose", "Myocardial infarction", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Montesquieu?", "answers": ["Poison", "Respiratory failure", "Fever", "Muscular dystrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Linda Jones?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Septic shock", "Esophageal cancer", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Egon von F\u00fcrstenberg?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "AIDS", "Lupus erythematosus", "Hepatitis A"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Egon von F\u00fcrstenberg?", "answers": ["Encephalopathy", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Paraquat", "Liver tumour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eva Hesse?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Blunt trauma", "Brain tumor", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of \"Johnny \"\"Guitar\"\" Watson\"?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Toxoplasmosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Buchanan?", "answers": ["Binge drinking", "Respiratory failure", "Diarrhea", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Lane?", "answers": ["Heart cancer", "Alcoholism", "Malaria", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Mitchell?", "answers": ["Poison", "Cor pulmonale", "Stomach cancer", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Mitchell?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Cancer", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Willem de Kooning?", "answers": ["Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Liver disease", "Asphyxia", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jason Miller?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Bubonic plague", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fireball Roberts?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Pneumonia", "Cancer of the larynx"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fireball Roberts?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Chronic renal failure", "Cardiac arrest", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hiram Bullock?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Throat cancer", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Katherine Mansfield?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Myasthenia gravis", "Colorectal cancer", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Clive Burr?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Uterine cancer", "Surgery", "Marfan syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vince Flynn?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Respiratory failure", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dale Carnegie?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Pyaemia", "Wound", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stanley Kamel?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Asphyxia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charlotte Bront\u00eb?", "answers": ["Epilepsy", "Epidemic typhus", "Kidney cancer", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yootha Joyce?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Hepatitis", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yootha Joyce?", "answers": ["Insulinoma", "Anal cancer", "Alcoholism", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anna May Wong?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Hypertension", "Seizure", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jesse Wayne Swayze?", "answers": ["Alcoholism", "Myocardial infarction", "Crohn's disease", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anna Pavlova?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Pleurisy", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pope Pius XII?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Skin cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Huell Howser?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Toxoplasmosis", "Anaphylaxis", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Urich?", "answers": ["Physical abuse", "Enteritis", "Synovial sarcoma", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Weider?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Post-polio syndrome", "Heart failure", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gloria Stuart?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Hypertension", "Bright's disease", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marianna Komlos?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Choking", "Breast cancer", "Injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gloria Grahame?", "answers": ["Hepatitis A", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Peritonitis", "Encephalitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gloria Grahame?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Epidemic typhus", "Asthma", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gloria Grahame?", "answers": ["Congenital heart defect", "Mesothelioma", "Breast cancer", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Phillip Law?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Alzheimer's disease", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frances Bavier?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Physical abuse", "Tuberculosis", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frances Bavier?", "answers": ["Infectious disease", "Cancer", "Hyperthermia", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Curt Hennig?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Drug overdose", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Trichinosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ed Sullivan?", "answers": ["Bubonic plague", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Respiratory failure", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jackie Gleason?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Influenza", "Dementia pugilistica"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Redd Foxx?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Peritonitis", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Pickford?", "answers": ["Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Lung cancer", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Albert Jacka?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Respiratory disease", "Nephritis", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harry Morgan?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Syphilis", "Barbiturate", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sydney Pollack?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Syphilis", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charlotte MacLeod?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Alzheimer's disease", "Skull fracture", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vespasian?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Diarrhea", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michelle Thomas?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Lobar pneumonia", "Stomach cancer", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jon Mannah?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Smoke inhalation", "Thrombosis", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Allen Ludden?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "B-cell lymphoma", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wilfrid Brambell?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Coronary occlusion", "Starvation", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Beatrix Potter?", "answers": ["Anorexia nervosa", "Pneumonia", "Acute pancreatitis", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Daniel Webster?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Asphyxia", "Myocardial infarction", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Daniel Webster?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Gallbladder cancer", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Septic shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Nathan-Turner?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Bronchopneumonia", "Aortic aneurysm", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Annette Charles?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Trichinosis", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Hallett?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Post-polio syndrome", "Cardiovascular disease", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chloe Jones?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Oral cancer", "Pleurisy", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chloe Jones?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "Hepatitis", "Syphilis", "Viral pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Philip K. Dick?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Stroke", "Tetanus", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tug McGraw?", "answers": ["Aortic dissection", "Brain tumor", "Cholera", "Epidural hematoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Virginia Hill?", "answers": ["Cystic fibrosis", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Drug overdose", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Perry Moore?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Drug overdose", "Poison", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Jacob Astor IV?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Choking", "Syphilis", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jessica Tandy?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Diverticulosis", "Ballistic trauma", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Cooper?", "answers": ["Epilepsy", "Choking", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Cooper?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Aneurysm", "Kawasaki disease", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Conaway?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Gangrene", "Sepsis", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Conaway?", "answers": ["Polycythemia", "Surgery", "Encephalopathy", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Conaway?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Drug overdose", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Conaway?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Pneumonia", "Cardiac arrest", "Poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Neville Chamberlain?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Influenza", "Dementia pugilistica", "Skin cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Glen Buxton?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Multiple sclerosis", "Marfan syndrome", "Cholangiocarcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chet Atkins?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Tongue Cancer", "Heart failure", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barboura Morris?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Stroke", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Bancroft?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Cyanide poisoning", "Crohn's disease", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ayn Rand?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Falling", "Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Riggs?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Respiratory disease", "Prostate cancer", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Crash Holly?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Uterine cancer", "Pulmonary edema", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ivor Dean?", "answers": ["Infectious disease", "Embolism", "Trichinosis", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mohammad Reza Pahlavi?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Cor pulmonale", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jagjit Singh?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Cholera", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christina Onassis?", "answers": ["Aplastic anemia", "Internal bleeding", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christina Onassis?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Atherosclerosis", "Pulmonary edema", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Beatrice Arthur?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Celiac disease", "Fever", "Fournier gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ian Mendez?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Colorectal cancer", "Poison"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Lorre?", "answers": ["Celiac disease", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Stroke", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Denny Dent?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Burn", "Skull fracture", "Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Bearer?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Falling", "Myocardial infarction", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Maxwell?", "answers": ["Myasthenia gravis", "Insulinoma", "Drowning", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Young?", "answers": ["Metastatic Melanoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Bone cancer", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aaron Russo?", "answers": ["Fever", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aaron Russo?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Gangrene", "Uremia", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Laxmikant Berde?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Renal failure", "Respiratory arrest", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stan Getz?", "answers": ["Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Respiratory failure", "Liver tumour", "Intestinal Obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Margaret Thatcher?", "answers": ["Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Alzheimer's disease", "Prostate cancer", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miriam Makeba?", "answers": ["Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Myocardial infarction", "Bubonic plague", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Quintana Roo Dunne?", "answers": ["Cor pulmonale", "Pulmonary embolism", "Acute pancreatitis", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jesse Owens?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Pneumonia", "Lung cancer", "Anaphylaxis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mustafa Kemal Atat\u00fcrk?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Cirrhosis", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Hepatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Elizabeth Montgomery?", "answers": ["Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sacagawea?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Fever", "Hepatitis C", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joseph Merrick?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Suffocation", "Hepatitis", "Kidney Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mahalia Jackson?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Cardiovascular disease", "Cerebral edema", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mahalia Jackson?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Gallbladder cancer", "Liver tumour", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Terence McKenna?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Arthritis", "Spinal tumor", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Koch?", "answers": ["Cor pulmonale", "Cancer", "Hepatitis", "Glioblastoma multiforme"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brad Renfro?", "answers": ["Suffocation", "Tetanus", "Skin cancer", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stuart Sutcliffe?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Binge drinking", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Aplastic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Taylor?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "B-cell lymphoma", "Nephritis", "Acute renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gerry Mulligan?", "answers": ["Hypertensive heart disease", "Surgery", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Liver tumour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Landon?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Diverticulosis", "Gallbladder cancer", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Landon?", "answers": ["Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Multiple myeloma", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dave Williams?", "answers": ["Appendix cancer", "Cardiovascular disease", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Trichinosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Grace Kelly?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Stroke", "Marfan syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dan Seals?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "Suffocation", "Motor neuron disease", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andreas Katsulas?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Systemic scleroderma", "Lung cancer", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John A. Macdonald?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Huntington's disease", "Debility", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Debbie Friedman?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Parkinson's disease", "Epidural hematoma", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Greta Garbo?", "answers": ["Huntington's disease", "Arsenic poisoning", "Pneumonia", "Testicular cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Greta Garbo?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Dehydration", "Oral cancer", "Insulinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shell Kepler?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Emphysema", "Cardiomegaly", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Hayward?", "answers": ["Acute renal failure", "Rheumatic fever", "Systemic scleroderma", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Hayward?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Fournier gangrene", "Epidemic typhus", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Hayward?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Cardiac surgery", "Pneumonia", "Rheumatic fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alfred Kinsey?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "Pneumonia", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Coronary thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerry Orbach?", "answers": ["Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Prostate cancer", "Myelodysplastic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gram Parsons?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Drug overdose", "Alzheimer's disease", "Systemic lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Earl Ray?", "answers": ["Alcoholism", "Hepatitis C", "Brain damage", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Troup?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Yellow fever", "Myocardial infarction", "Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gia Carangi?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "AIDS", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Myasthenia gravis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Leslie?", "answers": ["Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Myocardial infarction", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack MacGowran?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Parkinson's disease", "Trichinosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carrie Snodgress?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Gallbladder cancer", "Multiple myeloma", "Accidental Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Heavy D?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Respiratory disease", "Esophageal cancer", "Hepatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Betty Sue Lynn?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Emphysema", "Aortic aneurysm", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andrew McKelvey?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Peritonitis", "Surgery", "Epilepsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hugo Ch\u00e1vez?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Aneurysm", "Pneumonia", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hugo Ch\u00e1vez?", "answers": ["Blunt trauma", "Cancer", "Drowning", "Pneumothorax"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Huang Wenyong?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Lymphoma", "Pancreatitis", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carolyn Jones?", "answers": ["Endometrial cancer", "Colorectal cancer", "Surgery", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Brecker?", "answers": ["Kidney cancer", "Colorectal cancer", "Leukemia", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dean Martin?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Uterine cancer", "Skin cancer", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dean Martin?", "answers": ["Paraquat", "Accidental Fire", "Coronary thrombosis", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dean Martin?", "answers": ["Infectious disease", "Emphysema", "Alcohol intoxication", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Coronary thrombosis", "Anal cancer", "Wound", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Hepatitis A", "Atherosclerosis", "Drowning", "Pyaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bernadette Lafont?", "answers": ["Accidental Fire", "Cardiac arrest", "Respiratory arrest", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Woody Hayes?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Respiratory arrest", "Heart failure", "Kidney cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alexander Graham Bell?", "answers": ["Blunt trauma", "Brain tumor", "Colon Cancer", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alexander Graham Bell?", "answers": ["Epilepsy", "Pneumonia", "Pernicious anemia", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Claude Akins?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Crohn's disease", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Randy Stone?", "answers": ["Tetanus", "Cardiovascular disease", "Poisoning", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Matt Monro?", "answers": ["Septic shock", "Liver tumour", "Stomach cancer", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Enid Blyton?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Acute renal failure", "Acute renal failure", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lois Hamilton?", "answers": ["Kawasaki disease", "Drug overdose", "Cardiomegaly", "Respiratory Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of C. S. Lewis?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Exhaustion", "Poisoning", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Octavio Paz?", "answers": ["Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Pancreatitis", "Fournier gangrene", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marilyn Chambers?", "answers": ["Aortic dissection", "Chronic renal failure", "Respiratory failure", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marilyn Chambers?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Ballistic trauma", "Malaria", "Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cassandra Harris?", "answers": ["Cardiomegaly", "Ovarian cancer", "Lymphoma", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Cuccione?", "answers": ["Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Endometrial cancer", "Respiratory failure", "Cancer of the larynx"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Cuccione?", "answers": ["Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Bright's disease", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Muhammad Ali Jinnah?", "answers": ["Thrombus", "Pulmonary embolism", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Muhammad Ali Jinnah?", "answers": ["Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Tuberculosis", "Renal failure", "Hodgkin's lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charlie Chaplin?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Hepatitis A", "Stroke", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dennis Farina?", "answers": ["Fever", "Thrombosis", "Liver cancer", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anita Mui?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Endometrial cancer", "Cervical cancer", "Yellow fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sean Sasser?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Mesothelioma", "Fever", "Brain Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jane Seymour?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Morphine", "Childbirth", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerry Finn?", "answers": ["Atherosclerosis", "Renal failure", "Uterine cancer", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leonard Rossiter?", "answers": ["Arsenic poisoning", "Shock", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Acute renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alan Shepard?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Colorectal cancer", "Leukemia", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Beckinsale?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Gallbladder cancer", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Uremia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ann Dunham?", "answers": ["Uterine cancer", "Gangrene", "Seizure", "Gallbladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ann Dunham?", "answers": ["Edema", "Appendix cancer", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ann Dunham?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Ovarian cancer", "Brain damage", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sarah Burke?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Accidental Fire", "Brain damage", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sarah Burke?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Encephalitis", "Injury", "Alcohol intoxication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eric Dolphy?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Myocardial infarction", "Childbirth", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Franklin D. Roosevelt?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Atherosclerosis", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Epidemic typhus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Swigert?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Dehydration", "Typhoid fever", "Endometrial cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Swigert?", "answers": ["Multiple myeloma", "Surgery", "Bone cancer", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Showers?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Respiratory disease", "Drowning", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Victor Mature?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Pleurisy", "Leukemia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Poberezny?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Toxoplasmosis", "Anaphylaxis", "Respiratory Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Babe Didrikson Zaharias?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Fever", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Babe Didrikson Zaharias?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Pleurisy", "Dengue fever", "Cerebral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joan Blondell?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Lobar pneumonia", "Septic shock", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lee Roy Selmon?", "answers": ["Endometrial cancer", "Cyanide poisoning", "Cervical cancer", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy O. Disney?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Hyperthermia", "Esophageal cancer", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Exhaustion", "Epilepsy", "Typhoid fever", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gene Tierney?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Hyperthermia", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sonny Schmidt?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Poisoning", "Anemia", "Traumatic brain injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Levy Mwanawasa?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Typhoid fever", "Stroke", "Colon Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bette Davis?", "answers": ["Pernicious anemia", "Starvation", "Breast cancer", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Road Warrior Hawk?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Cyanide poisoning", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Patrick Bouvier Kennedy?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Septic shock", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ronald Reagan?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Pulmonary embolism", "Alzheimer's disease", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ronald Reagan?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Pneumonia", "Accidental Fire", "Smallpox"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hiroshi Tsuburaya?", "answers": ["Smallpox", "Cystic fibrosis", "Diabetes mellitus", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dmitri Mendeleev?", "answers": ["Arsenic poisoning", "Pneumothorax", "Influenza", "Myasthenia gravis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Thelma Todd?", "answers": ["Injury", "Arteriosclerosis", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Carbon monoxide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Clark Gable?", "answers": ["Coronary thrombosis", "Binge drinking", "Burn", "Schistosomiasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George C. Scott?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Iatrogenesis", "Asthma", "Liver tumour"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Landesberg?", "answers": ["Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Colorectal cancer", "Cardiac arrest", "Pneumocystis pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bernard Edwards?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Gangrene", "Dysentery", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Harvey?", "answers": ["Coronary thrombosis", "Hepatitis C", "Burn", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chuck Schuldiner?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Syphilis", "Brain tumor", "Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Walker?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Anorexia nervosa", "Iatrogenesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Walker?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Aortic aneurysm", "Anaphylaxis", "Schistosomiasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aliki Vougiouklaki?", "answers": ["Intracranial aneurysm", "Pancreatic cancer", "Barbiturate overdose", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Beverly Shea?", "answers": ["Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Syphilis", "Stroke", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Freddy Soto?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Epilepsy", "Leukemia", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Baloff?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Brain tumor", "Head and neck cancer", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Clement?", "answers": ["Bright's disease", "Peritonitis", "Liver cancer", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George McFarland?", "answers": ["Malnutrition", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Appendix cancer", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barbara Stanwyck?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Bronchopneumonia", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barbara Stanwyck?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Tetanus", "Alzheimer's disease", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barbara Stanwyck?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Liver failure", "Testicular cancer", "Anal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Ure?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Traumatic brain injury", "Anemia", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mattie Moss Clark?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Dengue fever", "Wound", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sexy Cora?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Pulmonary embolism", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chuck Traynor?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Coronary occlusion", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cormac McAnallen?", "answers": ["Viral pneumonia", "Cardiovascular disease", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Poison"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Esther Rolle?", "answers": ["B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Pancreatic cancer", "Diabetes mellitus", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aaron Alexis?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Ballistic trauma", "Encephalopathy", "Insulinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Osceola?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Smallpox", "Malaria", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Earl Manigault?", "answers": ["Insulinoma", "Pancreatic cancer", "Cardiovascular disease", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sanjeev Kumar?", "answers": ["Bacterial pneumonia", "Malaria", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Robson?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Hypothermia", "Cancer", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Robson?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Peritonitis", "Lung cancer", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Antonio Puerta?", "answers": ["Atherosclerosis", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Cardiac arrest", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Antonio Puerta?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Cardiovascular disease", "Burn", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Blake Snyder?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Cardiac arrest", "Schistosomiasis", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Strummer?", "answers": ["Thrombus", "Congenital heart defect", "Anaphylaxis", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marcelino S\u00e1nchez?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Anemia", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lou Myers?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Pneumonia", "Alcoholism", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anthony Minghella?", "answers": ["Aortic aneurysm", "Cervical cancer", "Anemia", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anthony Minghella?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Bleeding", "Cyanide poisoning", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anthony Minghella?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Enteritis", "Cancer", "Systemic lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kristi\u0101ns Pel\u0161s?", "answers": ["Renal Cancer", "Drowning", "Pancreatic cancer", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Lansing?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Binge drinking", "Cancer", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Lansing?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Liver failure", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry Linville?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Cancer", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry Linville?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Cervical cancer", "Debility", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry Linville?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Alcoholism", "Lung cancer", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Henry Bromell?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Dengue fever", "Bone cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mark Balelo?", "answers": ["Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Tongue Cancer", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Sand?", "answers": ["Heart cancer", "Bladder cancer", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roxie Roker?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Childbirth", "Brain tumor", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Oliver Reed?", "answers": ["Endometrial cancer", "Renal failure", "Myocardial infarction", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lewis Carroll?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Pneumonia", "Arteriosclerosis", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mia Amber Davis?", "answers": ["Shock", "Liver disease", "Thrombus", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andrew Carnegie?", "answers": ["Aneurysm", "Seizure", "Chest pain", "Bronchopneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Janssen?", "answers": ["Cardiac surgery", "Encephalitis", "Myocardial infarction", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Meyer Lansky?", "answers": ["Spinal tumor", "B-cell lymphoma", "Barbiturate", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joey LaCaze?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Respiratory failure", "Poison", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Ford?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Arsenic poisoning", "Head and neck cancer", "Starvation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Ruby?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Stroke", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Ruby?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Heart cancer", "Bladder cancer", "Polymyalgia rheumatica"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Ruby?", "answers": ["Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Head and neck cancer", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Phyllis Hyman?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Choking", "Traumatic brain injury", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Kossoff?", "answers": ["Injury", "Starvation", "Respiratory failure", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Martin?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Smallpox", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Beryl Burton?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Heart failure", "Septic shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Simon Ward?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Testicular cancer", "Polycythemia", "Hepatocellular carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Clark?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Dementia", "Pernicious anemia", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Atkins?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Renal failure", "Viral pneumonia", "Influenza"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lou Gehrig?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Hyperthermia", "Coronary thrombosis", "Gallbladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lou Gehrig?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alexander Fleming?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Exhaustion", "Bubonic plague", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joshua Nkomo?", "answers": ["Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Prostate cancer", "Pulmonary embolism", "Kidney Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George DiCenzo?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Barbiturate", "Smallpox", "Anal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ahn Sahng-hong?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Stroke", "Hyperthermia", "Gallbladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Crenna?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Pancreatic cancer", "Polycythemia", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Crenna?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Lobar pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charlie Parker?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Shock", "Post-polio syndrome", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charlie Parker?", "answers": ["Respiratory Infection", "Perforated ulcer", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stephen Boyd?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Hepatitis", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jason Richards?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Traumatic brain injury", "Myasthenia gravis", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Updike?", "answers": ["Cardiomyopathy", "Thyroid cancer", "Paraquat", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Walston?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Lupus erythematosus", "Multiple sclerosis", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ginger Rogers?", "answers": ["Hypertensive heart disease", "Dysentery", "Myocardial infarction", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alexander Dale Oen?", "answers": ["Ruptured Aneurysm", "Cardiac arrest", "Emphysema", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of H. P. Lovecraft?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Peritonitis", "Cancer", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of H. P. Lovecraft?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Malnutrition", "Coronary artery disease", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jean-Michel Basquiat?", "answers": ["Blunt trauma", "Drug overdose", "Poison", "Embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leo Tolstoy?", "answers": ["Testicular cancer", "Heart cancer", "Brain damage", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hubert Humphrey?", "answers": ["Falling", "Atherosclerosis", "Cirrhosis", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hubert Humphrey?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Anal cancer", "Chest pain", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Winick?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "Anaphylaxis", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Raymond Carver?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Pneumothorax", "Renal failure", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Hartford?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Childbirth", "Lymphoma", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of \u00c9mile Zola?", "answers": ["Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Hepatitis C", "Arthritis", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stephen Crane?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Tuberculosis", "Asthma", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Earl Hindman?", "answers": ["Pulmonary edema", "Lung cancer", "Tongue Cancer", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miss Tony?", "answers": ["Renal cell carcinoma", "Renal failure", "Anemia", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Emily Dickinson?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Influenza", "Bright's disease", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Willie Stargell?", "answers": ["Coronary artery disease", "Exhaustion", "Stroke", "Thrombus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edna St. Vincent Millay?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edna St. Vincent Millay?", "answers": ["Tongue Cancer", "Lobar pneumonia", "Poison", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leonard Chess?", "answers": ["Coronary artery disease", "Pernicious anemia", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vera-Ellen?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Drowning", "Epilepsy", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cory Monteith?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Edema", "Brain Cancer", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Orville Wright?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Aortic dissection", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Bright's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Allen Collins?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Exhaustion", "Pneumonia", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vernon Presley?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Aplastic anemia", "Leukemia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Morgan Fieri?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Drug overdose", "Pneumocystis pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sergio Franchi?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Liver cancer", "Bubonic plague", "Intestinal Obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ernest Tubb?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Lung cancer", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Morphine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gladys Presley?", "answers": ["Bubonic plague", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Trauma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mike Webster?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Thyroid cancer", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kellie Waymire?", "answers": ["Appendix cancer", "Epidemic typhus", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Wimber?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Thrombosis", "Cardiovascular disease", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pierre Le Moyne d'Iberville?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Cirrhosis", "Yellow fever", "Perforated ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wilbur Wright?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Typhoid fever", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miss Elizabeth?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Arsenic poisoning", "Arsenic poisoning", "Bronchopneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jorge Negrete?", "answers": ["Hepatitis", "Accidental Fire", "Respiratory disease", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Ruffin?", "answers": ["Celiac disease", "Stomach cancer", "Diarrhea", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mae West?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Diabetes mellitus", "Stroke", "Alcohol intoxication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alan Freed?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Motor neuron disease", "Stroke", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Pryor?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Bleeding", "Poisoning", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Pryor?", "answers": ["Head and neck cancer", "Asphyxia", "Anal cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wernher von Braun?", "answers": ["Meningitis", "Marfan syndrome", "Pancreatic cancer", "Aplastic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Norman Bethune?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Trauma", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Juliet Anderson?", "answers": ["Exhaustion", "Anaphylaxis", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Big Pun?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Malaria", "Myocardial infarction", "Colon Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jock Stein?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Uterine cancer", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mariska Veres?", "answers": ["Rheumatic fever", "Heart failure", "Dementia pugilistica", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rajkumar?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Surgery", "Aplastic anemia", "Dementia pugilistica"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Cagney?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Asphyxia", "Celiac disease", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Cagney?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Anorexia nervosa", "Meningitis", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miles Davis?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Coronary occlusion", "Brain tumor", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miles Davis?", "answers": ["Respiratory disease", "Stroke", "Renal Cancer", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miles Davis?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Respiratory failure", "Smallpox", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Errol Flynn?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Diarrhea", "Sepsis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Raymond Burr?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Kidney cancer", "Alcoholism", "Iatrogenesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Mitchum?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Smallpox", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Mitchum?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Smoke inhalation", "Congenital heart defect", "Head and neck cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ibn Saud?", "answers": ["Wound", "Myocardial infarction", "Nephritis", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David O'Brien?", "answers": ["Choking", "AIDS", "Nephritis", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Matthew Ansara?", "answers": ["Traumatic brain injury", "Drug overdose", "Tongue Cancer", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nyree Dawn Porter?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Skin cancer", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Carson?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Pneumothorax", "Mesothelioma", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Carson?", "answers": ["Fever", "Colorectal cancer", "Enteritis", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nellie Melba?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Coronary occlusion", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Dawson?", "answers": ["Uterine cancer", "Arsenic poisoning", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Bixby?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Parkinson's disease", "Cardiac arrest", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ulysses S. Grant?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Schistosomiasis", "Iatrogenesis", "Respiratory disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bertolt Brecht?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Smoke inhalation", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Blatnick?", "answers": ["Heart cancer", "Anorexia nervosa", "Meningitis", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Neil Armstrong?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Bone cancer", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Frawley?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Viral pneumonia", "Myocardial infarction", "Coronary thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nicholas Macioci?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Liver tumour", "Alcohol intoxication", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sam Walton?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Liver tumour", "Stomach cancer", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sam Walton?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Typhoid fever", "Coronary occlusion", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sam Walton?", "answers": ["Bubonic plague", "Melanoma", "Marfan syndrome", "Multiple myeloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eyedea?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Pneumonia", "Acute pancreatitis", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gerald Levert?", "answers": ["B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Myasthenia gravis", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gerald Levert?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Infectious disease", "Melanoma", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Matuszak?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Polycythemia", "Cardiovascular disease", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lea De Mae?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Kidney cancer", "Acute renal failure", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lea De Mae?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Cholera", "Syphilis", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Francis Greenway?", "answers": ["Polycythemia", "Typhoid fever", "Chronic renal failure", "Appendix cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gus Grissom?", "answers": ["Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Smoke inhalation", "Brain tumor", "Bronchopneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ed Gein?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Pancreatitis", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ed Gein?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Diverticulosis", "Testicular cancer", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ed McMahon?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Diverticulosis", "Bone cancer", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ingrid Jonker?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Choking", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Zac Foley?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Arthritis", "Drug overdose", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Holton?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Drug overdose", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy Castle?", "answers": ["Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Suffocation", "Lung cancer", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Madeline Kahn?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Pancreatic cancer", "Brain Cancer", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bill Bixby?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Prostate cancer", "Sleep apnea", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Muriel Siebert?", "answers": ["Bubonic plague", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Mesothelioma", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lena Zavaroni?", "answers": ["Endometrial cancer", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alexandra McHale?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Renal failure", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sherwood Anderson?", "answers": ["Nephritis", "Peritonitis", "Stroke", "Skin cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Basil Rathbone?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Pulmonary edema", "Myocardial infarction", "Multiple myeloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Klee?", "answers": ["Peritonitis", "Systemic scleroderma", "Liver disease", "Pernicious anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Adams?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Fournier gangrene", "Smallpox", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Adams?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Rheumatic fever", "Viral pneumonia", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Adams?", "answers": ["Burn", "Liver cancer", "Bone cancer", "Epidemic typhus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Diana Dors?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Encephalitis", "B-cell lymphoma", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robin Gibb?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Crohn's disease", "Huntington's disease", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robin Gibb?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Colorectal cancer", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robin Gibb?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Parkinson's disease", "Smallpox", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wayman Tisdale?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Morphine", "Accidental Fire", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Robeson?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Trauma", "Stroke", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris Rebello?", "answers": ["Shock", "Myocardial infarction", "Throat cancer", "Muscular dystrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anna Nicole Smith?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe South?", "answers": ["Kidney cancer", "Heart failure", "Pernicious anemia", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tina Watson?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Anemia", "Drowning", "Physical abuse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tina Watson?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Pancreatitis", "Bronchitis", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yves Klein?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Paraquat", "Multiple sclerosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Karen Steele?", "answers": ["Thrombus", "Liver tumour", "Cancer", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rene Bond?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Huntington's disease", "Cirrhosis", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry Fine?", "answers": ["Suffocation", "Stroke", "Choking", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roger Ebert?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Bacterial pneumonia", "Respiratory Infection", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Danny Thomas?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Hypothermia", "Heart failure", "Kidney cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nick Duncombe?", "answers": ["Intracranial aneurysm", "Starvation", "Meningitis", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Oppenheimer?", "answers": ["Cholangiocarcinoma", "Smallpox", "Throat cancer", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edith Wharton?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Stroke", "Bone cancer", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Amrish Puri?", "answers": ["Aplastic anemia", "Respiratory failure", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Skin cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ol' Dirty Bastard?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Drug overdose", "Epidemic typhus", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ol' Dirty Bastard?", "answers": ["Aspiration pneumonia", "Gallbladder cancer", "Heart failure", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Walter Reed?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Peritonitis", "Nephropathy", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dee Dee Belson?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Choking", "Cerebral edema", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris Adams?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Systemic scleroderma", "Ballistic trauma", "Pyaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of B. F. Skinner?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Surgery", "Leukemia", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Barbieri?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Liver failure", "Fever", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Calamity Jane?", "answers": ["Insulinoma", "Cerebral edema", "Pneumonia", "Hepatitis A"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Raphael?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Fever", "Uremia", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Walker?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Pneumonia", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joan Crawford?", "answers": ["Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Myocardial infarction", "Synovial sarcoma", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joan Crawford?", "answers": ["Renal cell carcinoma", "Pancreatic cancer", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charlotte Brosnan?", "answers": ["Smallpox", "Coronary artery disease", "Pneumothorax", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Dickens?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Physical abuse", "Pneumothorax"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Nirenberg?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Cirrhosis", "Pulmonary embolism", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Ablett?", "answers": ["Synovial sarcoma", "Infection", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Epidemic typhus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Ablett?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Colorectal cancer", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lee Marvin?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Myocardial infarction", "Meningitis", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Les Darcy?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Pneumonia", "Injury", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Les Darcy?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Sepsis", "Poison", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Francis Scott Key?", "answers": ["Pleurisy", "Injury", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Simon Monjack?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Thrombosis", "Dehydration", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Simon Monjack?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Anaphylaxis", "Liver cancer", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Kennedy?", "answers": ["Burn", "Brain Cancer", "Aortic aneurysm", "Starvation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Kennedy?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Post-polio syndrome", "Cancer", "Traumatic brain injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carrie Hamilton?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Lung cancer", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carrie Hamilton?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Stroke", "Dengue fever", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Morrow Lindbergh?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Nephropathy", "Stroke", "Rheumatic fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Morrow Lindbergh?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Tuberculosis", "Cerebral edema", "Seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Delaney?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Dysentery", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of L. Ron Hubbard?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Liver tumour", "Seizure", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ralph Greene?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Iatrogenesis", "Melanoma", "Liver tumour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ike Turner?", "answers": ["Traumatic brain injury", "Cancer of the larynx", "Drug overdose", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of F. Scott Fitzgerald?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Myocardial infarction", "Traumatic brain injury", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kevin Peter Hall?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Pleurisy", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kevin Peter Hall?", "answers": ["Alcoholism", "Alcohol intoxication", "AIDS", "Wound"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lupe Ontiveros?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Hypertension", "Testicular cancer", "Peritonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Germond?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Asphyxia", "Coronary occlusion", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Steinbrenner?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Cystic fibrosis", "Tuberculosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Randy Castillo?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Motor neuron disease", "Skin cancer", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eva Per\u00f3n?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Asphyxia", "Hypertensive heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eva Per\u00f3n?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Cancer", "Bone cancer", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Clarke Duncan?", "answers": ["Cardiomegaly", "Kawasaki disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Clarke Duncan?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Pleurisy", "AIDS", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ulrich M\u00fche?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Testicular cancer", "Bronchopneumonia", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brook Benton?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Meningitis", "Arsenic poisoning", "Bright's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Carroll?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Shock", "Cardiomyopathy", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ben Breedlove?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Hepatitis C", "Myocardial infarction", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Amjad Khan?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Heart failure", "Cystic fibrosis", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Seneca the Younger?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Aortic aneurysm", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nicolaus Copernicus?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Emphysema", "Epidemic typhus", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Josh Gibson?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Schistosomiasis", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Walter Matthau?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Alcoholism", "Myocardial infarction", "Seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Whiteley?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Blunt trauma", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ellen Corby?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Stroke", "Lymphoma", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ellen Corby?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Cardiovascular disease", "Starvation", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jason Collier?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Falling", "Cardiac arrest", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Neville?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "Tuberculosis", "Synovial sarcoma", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Lindbergh?", "answers": ["Blunt trauma", "Trauma", "Lymphoma", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buddy Hackett?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Diabetes mellitus", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Motor neuron disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Angela Devi?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Cystic fibrosis", "Cardiovascular disease", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Millington Synge?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Lymphoma", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Coronary thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leonardo Favio?", "answers": ["Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Lupus erythematosus", "Bright's disease", "Hepatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leonardo Favio?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marlon Brando?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Cardiovascular disease", "Physical abuse", "Kawasaki disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marlon Brando?", "answers": ["Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Alzheimer's disease", "Liver tumour", "Marfan syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marlon Brando?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Smoke inhalation", "Exhaustion", "Cholera"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Inman?", "answers": ["Hepatitis A", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Claude Debussy?", "answers": ["Infectious disease", "Falling", "Colorectal cancer", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Lemmon?", "answers": ["Infection", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Lemmon?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Aortic dissection", "Colon Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bernie Mac?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Pneumonia", "Hepatitis A", "Traumatic brain injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Howard Florey?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Smallpox", "Tetanus", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of McLean Stevenson?", "answers": ["Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Aplastic anemia", "Kidney Disease", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Fischer?", "answers": ["Cancer of the larynx", "Renal failure", "Skull fracture", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cecil Rhodes?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Arsenic poisoning", "Congenital heart defect", "Epidural hematoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aleksandr Pushkin?", "answers": ["Meningitis", "Cancer", "Ballistic trauma", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ferdinand Marcos?", "answers": ["Acute renal failure", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Esophageal cancer", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ferdinand Marcos?", "answers": ["Atherosclerosis", "Mesothelioma", "Brain damage", "Systemic lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ferdinand Marcos?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Aortic aneurysm", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Melanie Appleby?", "answers": ["Smoke inhalation", "Epidural hematoma", "Toxoplasmosis", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Melanie Appleby?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Arteriosclerosis", "Kidney Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Collins?", "answers": ["Kidney cancer", "Acute renal failure", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gaines Adams?", "answers": ["Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Pancreatic cancer", "Cor pulmonale"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Allan Sherman?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Emphysema", "Drowning", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aneta Corsaut?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Burn", "Septic shock", "Physical abuse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sathya Sai Baba?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Poison", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chuck Connors?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Drowning", "Embolism", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chuck Connors?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Perforated ulcer", "Pneumonia", "Acute renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vladimir Krutov?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Liver failure", "Cerebral edema", "Ischaemic heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Graham Murray?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Thrombus", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Hepatocellular carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Josh Ryan Evans?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Lupus erythematosus", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gene Pitney?", "answers": ["Paraquat", "Colorectal cancer", "Coronary occlusion", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rhonda Sing?", "answers": ["Pulmonary aspiration", "Aortic aneurysm", "Myocardial infarction", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rhonda Sing?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Enteritis", "Traumatic brain injury", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ivor Novello?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Cardiovascular disease", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Wisden?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Cancer", "Bacterial pneumonia", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Reed?", "answers": ["Congenital heart defect", "Celiac disease", "Infectious disease", "Cerebral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Reed?", "answers": ["Cancer of the larynx", "Influenza", "Encephalitis", "Epilepsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aristotle Onassis?", "answers": ["Cancer of the larynx", "Liver tumour", "Pneumonia", "Influenza"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barbara Billingsley?", "answers": ["Arsenic poisoning", "Poisoning", "Nephritis", "Polymyalgia rheumatica"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ben Chifley?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Coronary artery disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Napoleon III?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Stomach cancer", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tim Hardin?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Heart failure", "Anaphylaxis", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gregory Peck?", "answers": ["Mesothelioma", "Pneumonia", "Lung cancer", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gregory Peck?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "Bronchopneumonia", "Testicular cancer", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Culp?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Colon Cancer", "Bubonic plague", "Tetanus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dieter Dengler?", "answers": ["Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "B-cell lymphoma", "Muscular dystrophy", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Myocardial infarction", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ian Dury?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Wound", "Congenital heart defect", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Herb Edelman?", "answers": ["Coronary occlusion", "Cholera", "Mesothelioma", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edgar Allan Poe?", "answers": ["Cystic fibrosis", "Puerperal fever", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edgar Allan Poe?", "answers": ["Septic shock", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Typhoid fever", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Isaac Asimov?", "answers": ["Multiple myeloma", "AIDS", "Alcohol intoxication", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Isaac Asimov?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Diarrhea", "Spinal tumor", "Acute pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Isaac Asimov?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Aortic aneurysm", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Celia Cruz?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Motor neuron disease", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Celia Cruz?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Anaphylaxis", "Brain damage", "Head and neck cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eduard Khil?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Renal failure", "Motor neuron disease", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Albert Hofmann?", "answers": ["Viral pneumonia", "Myocardial infarction", "Anemia", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vitas Gerulaitis?", "answers": ["Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Enteritis", "Testicular cancer", "Cerebral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry H. Miller?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Diabetes mellitus", "Dementia", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bea Benaderet?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Dementia", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bea Benaderet?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Bladder cancer", "Hyperthermia", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ramesses II?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Tuberculosis", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ronnie Montrose?", "answers": ["Smallpox", "Prostate cancer", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Cholangiocarcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Reed?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Bacterial pneumonia", "Gangrene", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Reed?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Morphine", "Heart failure", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerry Nolan?", "answers": ["Smoke inhalation", "Muscular dystrophy", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Burl Ives?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Muscular dystrophy", "Bronchopneumonia", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dick York?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Cardiac surgery", "Emphysema", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Moli\u00e8re?", "answers": ["Aplastic anemia", "Bright's disease", "Pulmonary edema", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Moli\u00e8re?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Dysentery", "Childbirth", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stephen Covey?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Alzheimer's disease", "Injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rick Aviles?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Muscular dystrophy", "Pulmonary embolism", "Respiratory Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rick Aviles?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Heart cancer", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frankie Ruiz?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Embolism", "Multiple sclerosis", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brian Connolly?", "answers": ["Fever", "Gigantism", "Myocardial infarction", "Marfan syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brian Connolly?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Falling", "Colon Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brian Connolly?", "answers": ["Coronary artery disease", "Liver failure", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Polycythemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Minnie Pearl?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Stroke", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Myasthenia gravis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Carradine?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Encephalitis", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bing Crosby?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Epidural hematoma", "Hepatitis", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marcelo H. del Pilar?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Pancreatic cancer", "Tuberculosis", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Burgess Meredith?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Melanoma", "Typhoid fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Burgess Meredith?", "answers": ["Tongue Cancer", "Alzheimer's disease", "Perforated ulcer", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Burgess Meredith?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Encephalopathy", "Skin cancer", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Tamm?", "answers": ["Congenital heart defect", "Perforated ulcer", "Cancer", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Julius Carry?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Perforated ulcer", "Pancreatic cancer", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Terry Melcher?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "Skin cancer", "Septic shock", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John A. Roebling?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Tetanus", "Aortic aneurysm", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roger C. Carmel?", "answers": ["Head and neck cancer", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Cardiovascular disease", "Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ron Palillo?", "answers": ["Epilepsy", "Myocardial infarction", "Viral pneumonia", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Butterfield?", "answers": ["Viral pneumonia", "Schistosomiasis", "Nephritis", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Butterfield?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Dehydration", "Brain damage", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Shue?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Falling", "Melanoma", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nicholas R. Oleson?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Dementia pugilistica", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gerry Ryan?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Bright's disease", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Howard Rollins?", "answers": ["Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Drowning", "AIDS", "Cholera"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Howard Rollins?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Myasthenia gravis", "Renal failure", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pedro Zamora?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Rheumatic fever", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Margaret Brown?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Debility", "Burn", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Margaret Brown?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Brain tumor", "Pulmonary embolism", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marilyn Maxwell?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Myocardial infarction", "Crohn's disease", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Beck?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Pancreatitis", "Prostate cancer", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leonid Brezhnev?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Coronary thrombosis", "Hypertension", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenneth More?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Drowning", "Endometrial cancer", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of LeRoi Moore?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Injury", "Systemic scleroderma", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Byron MacGregor?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Pneumonia", "Syphilis", "Testicular cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alex Chilton?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Barbiturate", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Logie Baird?", "answers": ["Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Insulinoma", "Stroke", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Harrison?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Brain Cancer", "Bubonic plague", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Dekova?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Lobar pneumonia", "Bacterial pneumonia", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fred Rogers?", "answers": ["Meningitis", "Lymphoma", "Stomach cancer", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ren\u00e9 Laennec?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Respiratory failure", "Viral pneumonia", "Tongue Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eazy-E?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Renal Cancer", "AIDS", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Livingstone?", "answers": ["Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Acute renal failure", "Cardiovascular disease", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mike Reid?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Syphilis", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Colon Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eddie Guerrero?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Heart failure", "Smoke inhalation", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Oliver Cromwell?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Malaria", "Liver disease", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Cook?", "answers": ["Suffocation", "Bleeding", "Trauma", "Multiple myeloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Connell?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Myocardial infarction", "Head and neck cancer", "Muscular dystrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Loretta Young?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Ovarian cancer", "Falling", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edmund Sylvers?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Acute renal failure", "Pleurisy", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward G. Robinson?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Fournier gangrene", "Ballistic trauma", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yvette Wilson?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Arsenic poisoning", "Barbiturate overdose", "Cervical cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Raaj Kumar?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Cervical cancer", "Pancreatic cancer", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Burns?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Cardiac arrest", "Systemic scleroderma", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Max Robinson?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mao Zedong?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Motor neuron disease", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of \u00c9dith Piaf?", "answers": ["Infection", "Cancer", "Asphyxia", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Oscar Wilde?", "answers": ["Suffocation", "Meningitis", "Bubonic plague", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harold Washington?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Lobar pneumonia", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Robbins?", "answers": ["Falling", "Cancer", "Childbirth", "Thyroid cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pietro Mennea?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Synovial sarcoma", "Toxoplasmosis", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dusty Springfield?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Trichinosis", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Adlai Stevenson II?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Influenza", "Lobar pneumonia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Adlai Stevenson II?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Cardiovascular disease", "Smallpox", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sun Yat-sen?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Barbiturate", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Anaphylaxis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Dunn?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Influenza", "Cor pulmonale", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Louis Cyr?", "answers": ["Nephritis", "Liver cancer", "Cancer of the larynx", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Lundigan?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Tetanus", "Choking", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Lundigan?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Pulmonary edema", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy Rogers?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Dehydration", "Heart failure", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Benjamin Ruggiero?", "answers": ["Aortic dissection", "Yellow fever", "Toxoplasmosis", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Greg Kramer?", "answers": ["Ruptured Aneurysm", "Cerebral edema", "Cancer", "Kidney Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Karen Black?", "answers": ["Shock", "Pancreatitis", "Cancer", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stokely Carmichael?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Respiratory failure", "Syphilis", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buck Adams?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Heart failure", "Chronic renal failure", "Endometrial cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Bernard Shaw?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Renal failure", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Muscular dystrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Darryl Kile?", "answers": ["Aortic aneurysm", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Emphysema", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bruce Paltrow?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Motor neuron disease", "Bleeding", "Embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bruce Paltrow?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Anorexia nervosa", "Pneumonia", "Encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bruce Paltrow?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Pernicious anemia", "Oral cancer", "Insulinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bruce Paltrow?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Zhou Enlai?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Falling", "Cor pulmonale", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jay Bennett?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Drug overdose", "Morphine", "Hypertensive heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Art Donovan?", "answers": ["Cardiomegaly", "Cardiomegaly", "Barbiturate", "Respiratory disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of H. G. Wells?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Rheumatic fever", "Aortic aneurysm", "Liver tumour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Falcon Scott?", "answers": ["Coronary artery disease", "Starvation", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Judy Garland?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Thrombus", "Burn", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Judy Garland?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Renal failure", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Colleen Dewhurst?", "answers": ["Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Cancer of the larynx", "Cervical cancer", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Diana Sands?", "answers": ["Leiomyosarcoma", "Leukemia", "Coronary thrombosis", "Schistosomiasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jessica Savitch?", "answers": ["Edema", "Suffocation", "Drowning", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dred Scott?", "answers": ["Cardiomyopathy", "Tuberculosis", "Stroke", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Rubell?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Acute renal failure", "Physical abuse", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Geeta Dutt?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Cirrhosis", "Ovarian cancer", "Alcohol intoxication"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Maria Montez?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Myocardial infarction", "Head and neck cancer", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Maria Montez?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Spinal tumor", "Drowning", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Helen Morgan?", "answers": ["Tongue Cancer", "Cirrhosis", "Epidural hematoma", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wesley C. Skiles?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Smoke inhalation", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Everett Sloane?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Sepsis", "Coronary occlusion", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harry Caray?", "answers": ["Cor pulmonale", "Cervical cancer", "Cardiovascular disease", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leonhard Euler?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lady Randolph Churchill?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Traumatic brain injury", "Bleeding", "Hepatitis A"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lady Randolph Churchill?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Injury", "Surgery", "Typhoid fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rod Serling?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Surgery", "Myocardial infarction", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Moe Norman?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Testicular cancer", "Pneumothorax", "Ischaemic heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Janet Leigh?", "answers": ["Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Myocardial infarction", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Teddy Pendergrass?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Walter Payton?", "answers": ["Alcoholism", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Lobar pneumonia", "Liver tumour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robin Harris?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Alcoholism", "Myocardial infarction", "Smallpox"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve McNair?", "answers": ["Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Aortic aneurysm", "Kidney Disease", "Ballistic trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Terry Scott?", "answers": ["Epidemic typhus", "Cancer", "Brain tumor", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nelson Rockefeller?", "answers": ["Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Traumatic brain injury", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Teresa Graves?", "answers": ["Crohn's disease", "Barbiturate", "Anorexia nervosa", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Mulligan?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Testicular cancer", "Tetanus", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Bloom?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Testicular cancer", "Liver disease", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Manuel Quezon?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Tuberculosis", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Randolph Scott?", "answers": ["Respiratory disease", "Nephritis", "Pernicious anemia", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Randolph Scott?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Surgery", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ella Fitzgerald?", "answers": ["Hepatitis", "Diabetes mellitus", "Marfan syndrome", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David H. Hackworth?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Systemic scleroderma", "Perforated ulcer", "Bronchopneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David H. Hackworth?", "answers": ["Ruptured Aneurysm", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Smallpox", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Arthur Ashe?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "AIDS", "Pernicious anemia", "Septic shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chase Tatum?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Trauma", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pope Paul VI?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Acute renal failure", "Falling", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Stewart?", "answers": ["Pulmonary edema", "Celiac disease", "Cardiac arrest", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Stewart?", "answers": ["Acute renal failure", "Pulmonary embolism", "Respiratory arrest", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Stewart?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Injury", "Dysentery", "Bacterial pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of N. T. Rama Rao?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Respiratory failure", "Pleurisy", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of DONDI?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Diverticulosis", "Embolism", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eartha Kitt?", "answers": ["Coronary artery disease", "Colorectal cancer", "Endometrial cancer", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sylvia Likens?", "answers": ["Shock", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sylvia Likens?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Liver failure", "Internal bleeding", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sylvia Likens?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Anemia", "Bleeding", "Skin cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sylvia Likens?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Alzheimer's disease", "Trauma", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sylvia Likens?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Bright's disease", "Malnutrition", "Dementia with Lewy bodies"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Arthur Conan Doyle?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Liver cancer", "Liver failure", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Addie?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Cancer of the larynx", "Acute pancreatitis", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Reggie Roby?", "answers": ["Infection", "Myocardial infarction", "Pyaemia", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dan Blocker?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Pulmonary embolism", "Atherosclerosis", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nora Ephron?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Hepatitis", "Hepatitis A", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nora Ephron?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Respiratory disease", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Ischaemic heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Perry Como?", "answers": ["Shock", "Pulmonary edema", "Edema", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lance Cade?", "answers": ["Anorexia nervosa", "Hepatitis C", "Heart failure", "Thrombus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lee J. Cobb?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Myocardial infarction", "Hepatitis A", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Linda Darnell?", "answers": ["Bubonic plague", "Motor neuron disease", "Smoke inhalation", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Traylor?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Pernicious anemia", "Toxoplasmosis", "Anal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerry Buss?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Esophageal cancer", "Cancer", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edith Bouvier Beale?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Myocardial infarction", "Iatrogenesis", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dizzy Gillespie?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Brain tumor", "Appendix cancer", "Hepatitis A"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christine Maggiore?", "answers": ["Post-polio syndrome", "Suffocation", "AIDS", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jill Dando?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "Encephalopathy", "Aplastic anemia", "Ballistic trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of E. Nesbit?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Lung cancer", "Aortic aneurysm", "Septic shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Billy Joe Daugherty?", "answers": ["Shock", "Lymphoma", "Perforated ulcer", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ryan Shay?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Colorectal cancer", "Dehydration", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ryan Shay?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Exhaustion", "Cirrhosis", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Burns?", "answers": ["Anorexia nervosa", "Cor pulmonale", "Brain tumor", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stephen A. Douglas?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "Childbirth", "Ovarian cancer", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Danton?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Infection", "Bright's disease", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Danton?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Esophageal cancer", "Injury", "Kidney Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Victor French?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Huntington's disease", "Arthritis", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Isaac Hayes?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Asthma", "Pulmonary embolism", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Etta James?", "answers": ["Multiple myeloma", "Alcoholism", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Etta James?", "answers": ["Bacterial pneumonia", "Alzheimer's disease", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Anal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Ehrlich?", "answers": ["Kidney Disease", "Breast cancer", "Stroke", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mabel Albertson?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Chest pain", "Huntington's disease", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cyrinda Foxe?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Dengue fever", "Brain tumor", "Brain Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of J.J. Jackson?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Myocardial infarction", "Diarrhea", "Fournier gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bess Houdini?", "answers": ["Rheumatic fever", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Myocardial infarction", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Connie Kreski?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Childbirth", "Lung cancer", "Polycythemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charlie Crowe?", "answers": ["Bright's disease", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeanne Cooper?", "answers": ["Encephalopathy", "Debility", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Allan Sekula?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Dengue fever", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Martina von Trapp?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Cancer", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Florence Griffith Joyner?", "answers": ["Choking", "Epilepsy", "Liver cancer", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Thomas H. Ince?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Heart failure", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Theodore Wilson?", "answers": ["Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Cyanide poisoning", "AIDS", "Influenza"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Theodore Wilson?", "answers": ["Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Stroke", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Gallbladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Denison?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "Cancer", "Perforated ulcer", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kirby Puckett?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Emphysema", "Testicular cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marie-France Pisier?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Prostate cancer", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sadako Sasaki?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Leukemia", "Smallpox", "Epidemic typhus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fred Astaire?", "answers": ["Pulmonary aspiration", "Breast cancer", "Pneumonia", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carson McCullers?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Epidural hematoma", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carson McCullers?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Crohn's disease", "Cirrhosis", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christiaan Barnard?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Cirrhosis", "Asthma", "Rheumatic fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Banner?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Synovial sarcoma", "Dengue fever", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sebastian Cabot?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Cyanide poisoning", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alexander III of Russia?", "answers": ["Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Myasthenia gravis", "Melanoma", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Piermario Morosini?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Myocardial infarction", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bert Convy?", "answers": ["Post-polio syndrome", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Brain tumor", "Uremia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of River Phoenix?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Heart failure", "Liver disease", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of River Phoenix?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Melanoma", "Cor pulmonale", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tiny Tim?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Congenital heart defect", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carl Sagan?", "answers": ["Gallbladder cancer", "Pneumonia", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gene Autry?", "answers": ["Alcoholism", "Respiratory Infection", "Arteriosclerosis", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ashleigh Aston Moore?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Hypothermia", "Surgery", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ashleigh Aston Moore?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Drug overdose", "Coronary artery disease", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rajesh Khanna?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Stomach cancer", "Cancer", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bert Lahr?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Bronchopneumonia", "Pneumonia", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Del Close?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Diabetes mellitus", "Synovial sarcoma", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Harris?", "answers": ["Leiomyosarcoma", "Malnutrition", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Kidney cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alejandro Rey?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Falling", "Surgery", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Hart?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Uremia", "Pyaemia", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Benny Hill?", "answers": ["Skin cancer", "Coronary thrombosis", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Uremia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ludwig van Beethoven?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Shock", "Liver failure", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eric Carr?", "answers": ["Heart cancer", "Synovial sarcoma", "Bronchopneumonia", "Gallbladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Amy Winehouse?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Cor pulmonale", "Alcohol intoxication", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Divine?", "answers": ["Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Cardiomegaly", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gerry Rafferty?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Liver disease", "Stomach cancer", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Totie Fields?", "answers": ["Injury", "Pulmonary embolism", "Alzheimer's disease", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Al Capone?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Stroke", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Al Capone?", "answers": ["Lupus erythematosus", "Pneumonia", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Hughes?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Poison", "Liver tumour", "Injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Hughes?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Kidney Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rory Gallagher?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Smallpox", "Epidemic typhus", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Keats?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Tuberculosis", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rajendra Kumar?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Encephalitis", "Cancer", "Septic shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sarah Vaughan?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Lung cancer", "Diabetes mellitus", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Satchel Paige?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Gangrene", "Thyroid cancer", "Embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rigo Tovar?", "answers": ["Alcoholism", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Diabetes mellitus", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Heraclitus?", "answers": ["Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Fournier gangrene", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul von Hindenburg?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Cyanide poisoning", "Lung cancer", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jos\u00e9 Lima?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Liver cancer", "Epidemic typhus", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Bravo?", "answers": ["Poison", "Bronchopneumonia", "Marfan syndrome", "Influenza"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Catherine Marshall?", "answers": ["Edema", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Heart failure", "Hepatitis A"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Wayne?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Stomach cancer", "Bleeding", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Sharkey?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Trauma", "AIDS", "Hypertensive heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Boris Karloff?", "answers": ["Polycythemia", "Arthritis", "Hepatitis A", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Boris Karloff?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Throat cancer", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carl Switzer?", "answers": ["Cor pulmonale", "Leukemia", "Thyroid cancer", "Ballistic trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Humphrey Bogart?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Acute pancreatitis", "Coronary artery disease", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Humphrey Bogart?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "AIDS", "Esophageal cancer", "Liver tumour"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Franklin Pierce?", "answers": ["Insulinoma", "Coronary artery disease", "Motor neuron disease", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Big Boss Man?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Cirrhosis", "Cancer of the larynx", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cary Grant?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Aneurysm", "Dementia", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Winston Churchill?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Poisoning", "B-cell lymphoma", "Thyroid cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joyce Brothers?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Cyanide poisoning", "Respiratory failure", "Epilepsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of He Pingping?", "answers": ["Paraquat", "Colon Cancer", "Heart failure", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of He Pingping?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Debility", "Peritonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Rooney?", "answers": ["Burn", "Bladder cancer", "Surgery", "Cervical cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Murali?", "answers": ["Pernicious anemia", "Myocardial infarction", "Multiple myeloma", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anthony Quinn?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Cardiomyopathy", "Aortic dissection", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anthony Quinn?", "answers": ["Bacterial pneumonia", "Pneumonia", "Sleep apnea", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vladimir Lenin?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Debility", "Wound"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nathaniel Bacon?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Dysentery", "Brain tumor", "Cyanide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wilhelm II?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Peritonitis", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Syreeta Wright?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Myocardial infarction", "Uterine cancer", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Syreeta Wright?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Trichinosis", "Aspiration pneumonia", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Syreeta Wright?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Encephalopathy", "Sepsis", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Booker T. Washington?", "answers": ["Arthritis", "Cancer of the larynx", "Trichinosis", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lennard Pearce?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Tongue Cancer", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Respiratory disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hart Crane?", "answers": ["B-cell lymphoma", "Drowning", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Marfan syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Al Lettieri?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Injury", "Smallpox"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Steele?", "answers": ["Appendix cancer", "Heart failure", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Garfield?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Influenza", "Cardiovascular disease", "Acute renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dinah Washington?", "answers": ["Wound", "Drug overdose", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Infectious disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Ross?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Lymphoma", "Pancreatitis", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George VI?", "answers": ["Choking", "Heart failure", "Lung cancer", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mitsuharu Misawa?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Parkinson's disease", "Encephalopathy", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frances Farmer?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Throat cancer", "Embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dennis Wilson?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Drowning", "Polycythemia", "Infectious disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Jewell?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Crohn's disease", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Jewell?", "answers": ["Coronary occlusion", "Schistosomiasis", "Cardiomyopathy", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pablo Picasso?", "answers": ["Lupus erythematosus", "Hepatitis", "Myocardial infarction", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harry Houdini?", "answers": ["Peritonitis", "Spinal tumor", "Pulmonary embolism", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Donna Michelle?", "answers": ["Tongue Cancer", "Trauma", "Asthma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Spencer?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Appendix cancer", "Iatrogenesis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brittany Murphy?", "answers": ["Paraquat", "Perforated ulcer", "Anemia", "Cholera"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brittany Murphy?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Surgery", "Surgery", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brittany Murphy?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Esophageal cancer", "Chest pain", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dan Hartman?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "AIDS", "Liver disease", "Dementia pugilistica"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yolanda King?", "answers": ["Cholangiocarcinoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Breast cancer", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aditya Vikram Birla?", "answers": ["Bacterial pneumonia", "Coronary thrombosis", "Prostate cancer", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Junior Samples?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Bubonic plague", "Alcoholism", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mikl\u00f3s Feh\u00e9r?", "answers": ["Skin cancer", "Diarrhea", "Pancreatitis", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mikl\u00f3s Feh\u00e9r?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Anaphylaxis", "Lung cancer", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Kelley?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Emphysema", "Influenza", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Kelley?", "answers": ["Kidney cancer", "Coronary occlusion", "Pancreatic cancer", "Cholera"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dale Evans?", "answers": ["Pleurisy", "Encephalitis", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bon Scott?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Fever", "Iatrogenesis", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Irving Thalberg?", "answers": ["Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Pneumonia", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Death of Lisa McPherson?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Acute pancreatitis", "Viral pneumonia", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Haley Paige?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Cyanide poisoning", "Drug overdose", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles de Gaulle?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Aneurysm", "Chest pain", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eric Morecambe?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Colorectal cancer", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ethan Allen?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Barbiturate", "Stroke", "Poison"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Suzanne Pleshette?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Respiratory failure", "Starvation", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hattie McDaniel?", "answers": ["Hepatitis A", "Pulmonary embolism", "Breast cancer", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bert Kaempfert?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Aortic aneurysm", "Trauma", "Hepatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andreas M\u00fcnzer?", "answers": ["Aspiration pneumonia", "Muscular dystrophy", "Gigantism", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Bosley?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Bronchopneumonia", "Aortic dissection", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Doc Watson?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Enteritis", "Bronchopneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rose Wilder Lane?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Diabetes mellitus", "Cyanide poisoning", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brad Delp?", "answers": ["Respiratory disease", "Alzheimer's disease", "Cervical cancer", "Carbon monoxide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Emily McLaughlin?", "answers": ["Suffocation", "Stomach cancer", "Cancer", "Poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vidal Sassoon?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Multiple sclerosis", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nadine Shamir?", "answers": ["Wound", "Malaria", "Marfan syndrome", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Erik Rhodes?", "answers": ["Respiratory disease", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Coronary artery disease", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pope John Paul I?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Polycythemia", "Paraquat", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Clara Bow?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Pyaemia", "Viral pneumonia", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jacques Demy?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "AIDS", "Epilepsy", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Noble Willingham?", "answers": ["Iatrogenesis", "Arsenic poisoning", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mark Hanna?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Stroke", "Typhoid fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tutankhamun?", "answers": ["Kidney Disease", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Malaria", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of DeForest Kelley?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Meningitis", "Trichinosis", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rachel?", "answers": ["Falling", "Childbirth", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brian Clough?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Stomach cancer", "Myasthenia gravis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mai Zetterling?", "answers": ["Falling", "Gallbladder cancer", "Hepatitis C", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harpo Marx?", "answers": ["Traumatic brain injury", "Cardiovascular disease", "Colorectal cancer", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Hatfield?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Puerperal fever", "Syphilis", "Cholera"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Hatfield?", "answers": ["Cystic fibrosis", "Respiratory disease", "Sleep apnea", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carl Williams?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Smallpox", "Diverticulosis", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tyrone Power?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Surgery", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johnnie Taylor?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Myocardial infarction", "Starvation", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lana Turner?", "answers": ["Pneumothorax", "Throat cancer", "Heart failure", "Motor neuron disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Glenn McQueen?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Melanoma", "Cancer", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Glenn McQueen?", "answers": ["Physical abuse", "Skin cancer", "Dementia pugilistica", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Art Porter?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Ovarian cancer", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Smith?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Myocardial infarction", "Gallbladder cancer", "Seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Davy Jones?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Cancer", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kim Walker?", "answers": ["Peritonitis", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Brain tumor", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nancy Kulp?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Cancer", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Hepatocellular carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Evan Tanner?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Tuberculosis", "Alzheimer's disease", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Madame de Pompadour?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Dementia", "Pulmonary embolism", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Franco Scoglio?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Appendix cancer", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of D. H. Lawrence?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Choking", "Tuberculosis", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ruby Starr?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Ovarian cancer", "Thyroid cancer", "Uremia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Nelson?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Colorectal cancer", "Fever", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Boyd Ed Graves?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Emphysema", "Cardiomegaly", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dan Fogelberg?", "answers": ["Debility", "Prostate cancer", "Cerebral edema", "Pneumocystis pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of \"George \"\"Gabby\"\" Hayes\"?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Parkinson's disease", "Thrombus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank McCourt?", "answers": ["Melanoma", "Thrombus", "Physical abuse", "Acute pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary of Teck?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Lung cancer", "Syphilis", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris Penn?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Head and neck cancer", "Cardiomyopathy", "Skin cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chris Penn?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buster Keaton?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Aspiration pneumonia", "Brain damage", "Polycythemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Denver Pyle?", "answers": ["Heart cancer", "Arteriosclerosis", "Trauma", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nathan Bedford Forrest?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Diabetes mellitus", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Aplastic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Fogerty?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Mesothelioma", "Bacterial pneumonia", "Aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Fogerty?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Tuberculosis", "Cardiomyopathy", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Howard Hughes?", "answers": ["Pulmonary edema", "Renal failure", "Cor pulmonale", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Atta Mills?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Stroke", "Post-polio syndrome", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Pettiet?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "Drug overdose", "Starvation", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Goodman?", "answers": ["Cor pulmonale", "Leukemia", "Respiratory failure", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Monkhouse?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Rheumatic fever", "Endometrial cancer", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buster Merryfield?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Pneumothorax", "Accidental Fire", "Syphilis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Hite?", "answers": ["Epilepsy", "Myocardial infarction", "Congenital heart defect", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Friedensreich Hundertwasser?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Cyanide poisoning", "Respiratory Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Curly Howard?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Testicular cancer", "Peritonitis", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Curly Howard?", "answers": ["Celiac disease", "Infectious disease", "Stroke", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Chopin?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Respiratory failure", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yasser Arafat?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Surgery", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hiroshi Yamauchi?", "answers": ["Injury", "Leukemia", "Pneumonia", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yves Saint Laurent?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "Lung cancer", "Cancer", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Cook?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Lung cancer", "Sleep apnea", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Cronin?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Puerperal fever", "Tongue Cancer", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nancy Benoit?", "answers": ["Pneumothorax", "Cirrhosis", "Cholera", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Truman Capote?", "answers": ["Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Aortic dissection", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fred Shero?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Burn", "Motor neuron disease", "Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rajeev Motwani?", "answers": ["Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Brain tumor", "Respiratory Infection", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anneliese Michel?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Dehydration", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anneliese Michel?", "answers": ["Malnutrition", "Respiratory Infection", "Malaria", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edwin Hubble?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Exhaustion", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of MickDeth?", "answers": ["Septic shock", "Respiratory failure", "Bleeding", "Anal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Wright?", "answers": ["Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Cancer", "Cardiac surgery", "Hypertensive heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dave O'Brien?", "answers": ["Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Lupus erythematosus", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles M. Schulz?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Diarrhea", "Burn", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles M. Schulz?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Throat cancer", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Ramsey?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Pancreatitis", "Uterine cancer", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Ramsey?", "answers": ["Smoke inhalation", "Hypertension", "Synovial sarcoma", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hirohito?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Myocardial infarction", "Congenital heart defect", "Lobar pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Jeter?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Accidental Fire", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Jeter?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Wound", "Lymphoma", "Pleurisy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Jeter?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Esophageal cancer", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eddie Rabbitt?", "answers": ["Huntington's disease", "Insulinoma", "Lung cancer", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gavrilo Princip?", "answers": ["Accidental Fire", "Cerebral edema", "Tuberculosis", "Encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony Doyle?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Marfan syndrome", "Polycythemia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John DeLorean?", "answers": ["Aspiration pneumonia", "Aplastic anemia", "Stroke", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Calvin Coolidge?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Myocardial infarction", "Poisoning", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miguel de Cervantes?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Edema", "Cyanide poisoning", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Rheumatic fever", "Pancreatic cancer", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Glenn Shadix?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Blunt trauma", "Multiple sclerosis", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jimmy Durante?", "answers": ["Cardiomegaly", "Brain Cancer", "Pneumonia", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pee Wee Reese?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Synovial sarcoma", "Liver tumour", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sergio Vega?", "answers": ["Intracranial aneurysm", "AIDS", "Stroke", "Ballistic trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barry Sheene?", "answers": ["Tongue Cancer", "Stomach cancer", "Suffocation", "Bright's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barry Sheene?", "answers": ["Melanoma", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Throat cancer", "Physical abuse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry Hagman?", "answers": ["Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Respiratory arrest", "Myasthenia gravis", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry Hagman?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Renal Cancer", "Leukemia", "Dementia pugilistica"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry Hagman?", "answers": ["Mesothelioma", "Respiratory failure", "Asthma", "Head and neck cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ra\u00fal Juli\u00e1?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Stroke", "Chronic renal failure", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ra\u00fal Juli\u00e1?", "answers": ["Nephritis", "Infectious disease", "Stomach cancer", "Head and neck cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cus D'Amato?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Bleeding", "Brain Cancer", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Warren Zevon?", "answers": ["Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Diabetes mellitus", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Martin Frobisher?", "answers": ["Infectious disease", "Wound", "Tetanus", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Maria Callas?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Pancreatitis", "Injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Philo Farnsworth?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Tongue Cancer", "Exhaustion", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Philo Farnsworth?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Pneumonia", "Spinal tumor", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Helen Martin?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Barbiturate", "Heart cancer", "Dementia with Lewy bodies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edsel Ford?", "answers": ["Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Insulinoma", "Chronic renal failure", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ann Richards?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Throat cancer", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Backus?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Epilepsy", "Brain damage", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Backus?", "answers": ["Cardiac surgery", "Bright's disease", "Pneumonia", "Poison"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lupe V\u00e9lez?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Drug overdose", "Epilepsy", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brad Davis?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "B-cell lymphoma", "AIDS", "Dementia with Lewy bodies"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brad Davis?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Leukemia", "Edema", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chester A. Arthur?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Stroke", "Kidney cancer", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Earl Anthony?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Drug overdose", "Cor pulmonale"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dennis Burkley?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Pancreatitis", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dana Plato?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Drug overdose", "Kawasaki disease", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of V\u00e9ra Clouzot?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Cholera", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward Jenner?", "answers": ["Polycythemia", "Stroke", "Esophageal cancer", "Wound"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vestal Goodman?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Internal bleeding", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miyuki Kanbe?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Heart failure", "Pneumothorax", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leigh Bowery?", "answers": ["Cholangiocarcinoma", "AIDS", "Syphilis", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Glenn Corbett?", "answers": ["Shock", "Aspiration pneumonia", "Lung cancer", "Bacterial pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Reinaldo Arenas?", "answers": ["Dengue fever", "Binge drinking", "Drug overdose", "Accidental Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Street?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Pulmonary embolism", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gr\u00e9gory Lemarchal?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "Trauma", "Influenza", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Romy Diaz?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Trichinosis", "Synovial sarcoma", "Tongue Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bebe Moore Campbell?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Lupus erythematosus", "Post-polio syndrome", "Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bebe Moore Campbell?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Cirrhosis", "Cancer", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Augusto Pinochet?", "answers": ["Epidemic typhus", "Parkinson's disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Augusto Pinochet?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Typhoid fever", "Cardiovascular disease", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Parks?", "answers": ["Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Cancer", "Liver failure", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ch\u00f6gyam Trungpa?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Fournier gangrene", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mathieu Montcourt?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Cancer of the larynx"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alex Haley?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Myocardial infarction", "Endometrial cancer", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eugen Sandow?", "answers": ["Lupus erythematosus", "Motor neuron disease", "Stroke", "Fournier gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Boyer?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Endometrial cancer", "Internal bleeding", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Beau Brummell?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Syphilis", "Edema", "Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Beau Brummell?", "answers": ["Craniocerebral Trauma", "Testicular cancer", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Infectious disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mark St. John?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Motor neuron disease", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe DiMaggio?", "answers": ["Thrombus", "Polycythemia", "Lung cancer", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eliyahu M. Goldratt?", "answers": ["Uterine cancer", "Cancer", "Tuberculosis", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Seth Bullock?", "answers": ["Bright's disease", "Seizure", "Cancer", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Moshood Kashimawo Olawale Abiola?", "answers": ["Fournier gangrene", "Suffocation", "Arthritis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Oliver N'Goma?", "answers": ["Aortic dissection", "Cirrhosis", "Huntington's disease", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carlo Gambino?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Myocardial infarction", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Minnie Riperton?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Arsenic poisoning", "Falling", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Minnie Riperton?", "answers": ["Epidemic typhus", "Anemia", "Cancer", "Muscular dystrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leonard Bernstein?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "Cholera", "Colorectal cancer", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Margot Fonteyn?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Fever", "Nephropathy", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of E. B. White?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Skin cancer", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert E. Lee?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Smallpox", "Pneumonia", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Karen Lancaume?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Uremia", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Respiratory disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Isabella Blow?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Pneumonia", "Brain tumor", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Isabella Blow?", "answers": ["Post-polio syndrome", "Colon Cancer", "Paraquat", "Endometrial cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Curtis Whitley?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Drug overdose", "Morphine", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harold Dow?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Asthma", "Cyanide poisoning", "Cerebral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nancy Dolman?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Alcohol intoxication", "Ovarian cancer", "Morphine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of J. Edgar Hoover?", "answers": ["Atherosclerosis", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Septic shock", "Binge drinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of J. Edgar Hoover?", "answers": ["Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Myocardial infarction", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Inger Stevens?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Edema", "Anaphylaxis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack London?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Aortic aneurysm", "Choking", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack London?", "answers": ["Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Injury", "Mesothelioma", "Uremia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Grete Waitz?", "answers": ["Pleurisy", "Barbiturate", "Cancer", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Russell Means?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Throat cancer", "Malaria", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Wadlow?", "answers": ["Skin cancer", "Infection", "Crohn's disease", "Smallpox"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of DJ Screw?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Drug overdose", "Cervical cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Adrian Rogers?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Leukemia", "Acute renal failure", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marvin Hamlisch?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Lobar pneumonia", "Physical abuse", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marvin Hamlisch?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Respiratory arrest", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marvin Hamlisch?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Encephalopathy", "Heart cancer", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Corazon Aquino?", "answers": ["Malnutrition", "Schistosomiasis", "Colorectal cancer", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Claudia Cohen?", "answers": ["Trichinosis", "Viral pneumonia", "Head and neck cancer", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lenny McLean?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Cancer of the larynx", "Peritonitis", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yutaka Ozaki?", "answers": ["Epidemic typhus", "Aplastic anemia", "Pulmonary edema", "Systemic lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Strasberg?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Heart failure", "Leukemia", "Trichinosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Strasberg?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Pneumothorax", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pope John XXIII?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Alzheimer's disease", "Cardiovascular disease", "Peritonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Earl Weaver?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Cardiac arrest", "Physical abuse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony Curtis?", "answers": ["Head and neck cancer", "Dengue fever", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sahara Davenport?", "answers": ["Cardiomegaly", "Heart failure", "Drug overdose", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Adelle Davis?", "answers": ["Post-polio syndrome", "Multiple myeloma", "Malnutrition", "Anal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Umaga?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Myocardial infarction", "Renal Cancer", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jane Austen?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Tuberculosis", "Endometrial cancer", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vicki Sue Robinson?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Huntington's disease", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Z.Z. Hill?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Bleeding", "Myocardial infarction", "Hepatocellular carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pernell Roberts?", "answers": ["Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Pancreatic cancer", "Anaphylaxis", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pernell Roberts?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Perforated ulcer", "Oral cancer", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roger Maris?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Coronary occlusion", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roger Maris?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Rheumatic fever", "Aspiration pneumonia", "Encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dennis Cole?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Liver disease", "Renal failure", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Keye Luke?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Hypertension", "Childbirth", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Donald Pleasence?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Encephalitis", "Ischaemic heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles IX of France?", "answers": ["Blunt trauma", "Esophageal cancer", "Tuberculosis", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Wagner?", "answers": ["Coronary occlusion", "Motor neuron disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harriet Tubman?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Injury", "Pneumonia", "Kidney cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Amerigo Vespucci?", "answers": ["Poison", "Synovial sarcoma", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Malaria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of L. Frank Baum?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Influenza", "Lupus erythematosus", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Morrie Schwartz?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Liver failure", "Motor neuron disease", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Elizabeth Bishop?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Pancreatitis", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Queen Victoria?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Falling", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Blythe?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Dementia", "Lung cancer", "Huntington's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Sanders?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Appendix cancer", "Drug overdose", "Typhoid fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Antinous?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Aspiration pneumonia", "Arsenic poisoning", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Floyd Patterson?", "answers": ["Exhaustion", "Alzheimer's disease", "Mesothelioma", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Floyd Patterson?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Schistosomiasis", "Bronchitis", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenneth MacDonald?", "answers": ["Malnutrition", "Coronary thrombosis", "Anaphylaxis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Adam Goldstein?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Esophageal cancer", "Drug overdose", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Ehrlichman?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Coronary thrombosis", "Peritonitis", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Herod the Great?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Perforated ulcer", "Mesothelioma", "Fournier gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Herod the Great?", "answers": ["Edema", "Lymphoma", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Katherine Joyce?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Paraquat", "Gangrene", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barbara Orbison?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Enteritis", "Prostate cancer", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenny Everett?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Brain tumor", "AIDS", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dennis Johnson?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Smoke inhalation", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pat Lampard?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Pneumonia", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Schistosomiasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nat King Cole?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Aplastic anemia", "Melanoma", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nina Simone?", "answers": ["Respiratory Infection", "Esophageal cancer", "Lymphoma", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nina Simone?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Morphine", "Cervical cancer", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Desi Arnaz?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Meningitis", "Pancreatic cancer", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Linda Lee Thomas?", "answers": ["Nephritis", "Liver tumour", "Emphysema", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frederick Douglass?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Colorectal cancer", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ricky Bell?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Acute renal failure", "Heart failure", "Syphilis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sam Bottoms?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Esophageal cancer", "Drug overdose", "Physical abuse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sam Bottoms?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Tuberculosis", "Renal Cancer", "Cerebral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sam Bottoms?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Post-polio syndrome", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve McQueen?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Childbirth", "Acute pancreatitis", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve McQueen?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Stroke", "Multiple sclerosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jason Rhoades?", "answers": ["Melanoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Binge drinking", "Pleurisy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robin Cook?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Dengue fever", "Barbiturate", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Woody Guthrie?", "answers": ["Huntington's disease", "Nephritis", "Bone cancer", "Testicular cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Van Cliburn?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Swenson?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Injury", "Alcohol intoxication", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Kennedy?", "answers": ["Bacterial pneumonia", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Internal bleeding", "Hypertensive heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenny Greene?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Edema", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andrew Breitbart?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Heart failure", "Thrombosis", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shoeless Joe Jackson?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "Bronchopneumonia", "Myocardial infarction", "Head and neck cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fred Berry?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Stroke", "AIDS", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brett Mycles?", "answers": ["Cardiomyopathy", "Cardiovascular disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Physical abuse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carl Anderson?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Endometrial cancer", "Leukemia", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jermaine Stewart?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Septic shock", "Encephalopathy", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dutch Schultz?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Peritonitis", "Thrombosis", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard D. Zanuck?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Malnutrition", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Len Bias?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jean Hagen?", "answers": ["Hepatitis C", "Bladder cancer", "Esophageal cancer", "Binge drinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mark R. Hughes?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Trichinosis", "Colon Cancer", "Anal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Sutton?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Bacterial pneumonia", "B-cell lymphoma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aaron Spelling?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Stroke", "Typhoid fever", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Doc Holliday?", "answers": ["Edema", "Tuberculosis", "Cirrhosis", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Bendix?", "answers": ["Asthma", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Lobar pneumonia", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marilyn Monroe?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Drug overdose", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marilyn Monroe?", "answers": ["Leiomyosarcoma", "Barbiturate overdose", "Pancreatitis", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edmund Hillary?", "answers": ["Peritonitis", "Anemia", "Blunt trauma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Hodiak?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Yellow fever", "Leukemia", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Greg Giraldo?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Encephalopathy", "Pulmonary edema", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mako Iwamatsu?", "answers": ["Synovial sarcoma", "Throat cancer", "Pyaemia", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mako Iwamatsu?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Brain damage", "Anaphylaxis", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lorraine Hansberry?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Accidental Fire", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ernie Baron?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Influenza", "Pneumothorax", "Hepatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lou Gish?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Tuberculosis", "Cancer", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johann Wolfgang von Goethe?", "answers": ["Respiratory Infection", "Appendix cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Typhoid fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Simpson?", "answers": ["Shock", "Kawasaki disease", "Epidural hematoma", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Simpson?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Alzheimer's disease", "Traumatic brain injury", "Kidney Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lyle Alzado?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Multiple sclerosis", "Stomach cancer", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lyle Alzado?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Bacterial pneumonia", "Brain tumor", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Drew Barrymore?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Cancer", "Toxoplasmosis", "Carbon monoxide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lal Bahadur Shastri?", "answers": ["Fever", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gene Krupa?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Nephritis", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dermot Morgan?", "answers": ["Atherosclerosis", "Kawasaki disease", "Skin cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Deng Xiaoping?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Multiple myeloma", "Binge drinking", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Wattis?", "answers": ["Hepatitis C", "Tuberculosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sherman Hemsley?", "answers": ["Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Multiple myeloma", "Renal Cancer", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Godfrey Cambridge?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Smoke inhalation", "Myocardial infarction", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hercules?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Cardiovascular disease", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Peritonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Olive Thomas?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Pyaemia", "Poison", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Olive Thomas?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Colon Cancer", "Nephritis", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Janet Munro?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Smallpox"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Janet Munro?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Skull fracture", "Cancer of the larynx", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wendie Jo Sperber?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Cor pulmonale", "Hepatitis", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michel Foucault?", "answers": ["Aspiration pneumonia", "AIDS", "Perforated ulcer", "Motor neuron disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Philbin?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Drowning", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Freddie Hubbard?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Throat cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Oliver Hardy?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sam Mills?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Bubonic plague", "Tuberculosis", "Colon Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brent Mydland?", "answers": ["Fever", "Drug overdose", "Seizure", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Will Geer?", "answers": ["Tetanus", "Meningitis", "Respiratory failure", "Glioblastoma multiforme"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy Kinnear?", "answers": ["Viral pneumonia", "Liver tumour", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Graves?", "answers": ["Cystic fibrosis", "Coronary occlusion", "Lung cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sheldon Brown?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Trauma", "Kidney cancer", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jay Reatard?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Skin cancer", "Cardiac surgery", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Baldwin?", "answers": ["Bacterial pneumonia", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Stroke", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anthony Perkins?", "answers": ["Dengue fever", "AIDS", "Aplastic anemia", "Cervical cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anthony Perkins?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Wound", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Matthew Hopkins?", "answers": ["Pernicious anemia", "Tuberculosis", "Bright's disease", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kim Jong-il?", "answers": ["Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Myocardial infarction", "Brain damage", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Franz Kafka?", "answers": ["Hepatitis C", "Head and neck cancer", "Tuberculosis", "Kidney cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lance Loud?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Arteriosclerosis", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Morphine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bill Owen?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Toxoplasmosis", "Fournier gangrene", "Intestinal Obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Helen Gilbert?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Pneumothorax", "Choking", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Washington?", "answers": ["Huntington's disease", "Pneumonia", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Fournier gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sophiya Haque?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Encephalopathy", "Bronchopneumonia", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sophiya Haque?", "answers": ["Melanoma", "Cancer", "Cystic fibrosis", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Phil Lynott?", "answers": ["Aspiration pneumonia", "Drug overdose", "Cardiac arrest", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Phil Lynott?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Pneumonia", "Toxoplasmosis", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rev. Timothy Wright?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Childbirth", "Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Clayton Moore?", "answers": ["Metastatic Melanoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mark Twain?", "answers": ["Choking", "Asphyxia", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kipp Hamilton?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Aneurysm", "Cardiac surgery", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Simpson Kirkpatrick?", "answers": ["Post-polio syndrome", "Cancer", "Ballistic trauma", "Viral pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wally Cox?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Huntington's disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Bacterial pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kurt Vonnegut?", "answers": ["Traumatic brain injury", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Lobar pneumonia", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stanley Kubrick?", "answers": ["Tetanus", "Oral cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Thyroid cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Townes Van Zandt?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Myocardial infarction", "Diabetes mellitus", "Marfan syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Biggs?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Bone cancer", "Alcoholism", "Embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Fixx?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Coronary occlusion", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ernie Davis?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Melanoma", "Leukemia", "Lupus erythematosus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Derrick Thomas?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Puerperal fever", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vic Tayback?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Encephalopathy", "Myocardial infarction", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Moe Howard?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Cerebral edema", "Epidemic typhus", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dave Thomas?", "answers": ["Nephritis", "Gallbladder cancer", "Liver tumour", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Davey Boy Smith?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Myocardial infarction", "Epilepsy", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lev Vygotsky?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Tuberculosis", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dixie Carter?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Bright's disease", "Endometrial cancer", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nutan?", "answers": ["Cystic fibrosis", "Pulmonary embolism", "Cancer", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stan Laurel?", "answers": ["Cardiac surgery", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Myocardial infarction", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Omar Suleiman?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Post-polio syndrome", "Myocardial infarction", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anissa Jones?", "answers": ["Pneumothorax", "Diverticulosis", "Aplastic anemia", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Darren Robinson?", "answers": ["Coronary thrombosis", "Nephropathy", "Myocardial infarction", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Gilbert?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Enteritis", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pat Roach?", "answers": ["Uterine cancer", "Throat cancer", "Injury", "Coronary thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kevyn Aucoin?", "answers": ["Paraquat", "Aortic dissection", "Drug overdose", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Whitney Young?", "answers": ["Craniocerebral Trauma", "Kawasaki disease", "Drowning", "Hepatocellular carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Travers?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Lymphoma", "Cardiac arrest", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stu Ungar?", "answers": ["Cystic fibrosis", "Drug overdose", "Skull fracture", "Cholera"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Slovo?", "answers": ["Melanoma", "Debility", "Leukemia", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of D. James Kennedy?", "answers": ["Kidney Disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Congenital heart defect", "Cholera"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jean Seberg?", "answers": ["Respiratory disease", "Thyroid cancer", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shana Dowdeswell?", "answers": ["Post-polio syndrome", "Cardiomegaly", "Perforated ulcer", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George M. Cohan?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Spinal tumor", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Porter Wagoner?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Polycythemia", "Lung cancer", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Arnold Lobel?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "AIDS", "Injury", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Coleman?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Hepatitis A", "Epidural hematoma", "Respiratory disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Coleman?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Kidney Disease", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Burt Lancaster?", "answers": ["Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rob Pilatus?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Acute renal failure", "Typhoid fever", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Oscar Levant?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Multiple myeloma", "Multiple sclerosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dave McArtney?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Aortic aneurysm", "Poison", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Isabelle Caro?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Celiac disease", "Cor pulmonale", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christian Brando?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Pneumonia", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Patrick Troughton?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Influenza", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Finch?", "answers": ["Arsenic poisoning", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Myocardial infarction", "Encephalitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ed Parker?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Thrombosis", "Liver cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anna Wood?", "answers": ["Mesothelioma", "Celiac disease", "Drug overdose", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shelly Novack?", "answers": ["Cardiomyopathy", "Pneumonia", "Uremia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ron Santo?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Melanoma", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Big Mama Thornton?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Iatrogenesis", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roscoe Arbuckle?", "answers": ["Poison", "Motor neuron disease", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don S. Davis?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Myocardial infarction", "Liver failure", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Isabel Sanford?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Epilepsy", "Cyanide poisoning", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Steinbeck?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Lung cancer", "Kidney cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Brown?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Pneumothorax", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Brown?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Uremia", "Cardiovascular disease", "Epidural hematoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Floyd?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Kidney Disease", "Peritonitis", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dash Snow?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Brain Cancer", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Harmon?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Myocardial infarction", "Anaphylaxis", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vince Guaraldi?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Aortic aneurysm", "Stroke", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Diana Vreeland?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Myocardial infarction", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Arfa Karim?", "answers": ["Pneumothorax", "Anorexia nervosa", "Seizure", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Arfa Karim?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Cancer", "Pyaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Fosse?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Thyroid cancer", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Max Baer?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Myocardial infarction", "Alcoholism", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dennis Potter?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Marfan syndrome", "Cancer", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dennis Potter?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Brain tumor", "Pancreatic cancer", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Arthur Williams?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Colorectal cancer", "Influenza", "Renal Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of E. Pierce Marshall?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Alzheimer's disease", "Schistosomiasis", "Infectious disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sunny Johnson?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Liver tumour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Judith Barsi?", "answers": ["Cardiac surgery", "Ballistic trauma", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Theodora?", "answers": ["Fever", "Mesothelioma", "Cancer", "Cerebral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brion James?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Lobar pneumonia", "Cervical cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bill Evans?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Multiple myeloma", "Myasthenia gravis", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bill Evans?", "answers": ["Peritonitis", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Malnutrition", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Terry Gordy?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Hypertension", "Myocardial infarction", "Blunt trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cazuza?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "AIDS", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Syphilis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cazuza?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Blunt trauma", "Lung cancer", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jules Verne?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Gangrene", "Morphine", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Grant?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Cor pulmonale"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Luther Vandross?", "answers": ["Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Thrombus", "Myocardial infarction", "Acute pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ryan Davies?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Asthma", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Sabol?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Stroke", "Smoke inhalation", "Renal Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stephen Dunham?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Cirrhosis", "Accidental Fire", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerry Falwell?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Diarrhea", "Celiac disease", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerry Falwell?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Respiratory disease", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Henrietta Lacks?", "answers": ["Testicular cancer", "Morphine", "Cervical cancer", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sharat Sardana?", "answers": ["Infection", "Coronary thrombosis", "Schistosomiasis", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Albert Collins?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Stomach cancer", "Ballistic trauma", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Castillo?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Melanoma", "Physical abuse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tommy Rettig?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Myocardial infarction", "Liver disease", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pope John Paul II?", "answers": ["Mesothelioma", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pope John Paul II?", "answers": ["Wound", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Parkinson's disease", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Douglas MacArthur?", "answers": ["Testicular cancer", "Colorectal cancer", "Appendix cancer", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Hutton?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Multiple sclerosis", "Renal failure", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dwight D. Eisenhower?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Pancreatic cancer", "Viral pneumonia", "Bacterial pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ruhollah Khomeini?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Edema", "Multiple sclerosis", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of M. G. Ramachandran?", "answers": ["Cancer of the larynx", "Myasthenia gravis", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Peppard?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Atherosclerosis", "Embolism", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tina Chow?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Poisoning", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Manuel Roxas?", "answers": ["Aneurysm", "Polycythemia", "Binge drinking", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Allen?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Kawasaki disease", "AIDS", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lynne Thigpen?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Acute renal failure", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Merritt Butrick?", "answers": ["Tetanus", "Toxoplasmosis", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Anaphylaxis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Merritt Butrick?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Kawasaki disease", "Poison", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Franciscus?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "Meningitis", "Meningitis", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of H\u00e9ctor Lavoe?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "AIDS", "Bacterial pneumonia", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Mingus?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Gangrene", "Motor neuron disease", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ben Johnson?", "answers": ["Celiac disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Hypothermia", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Julie London?", "answers": ["Gallbladder cancer", "Congenital heart defect", "Stroke", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher George?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Bubonic plague", "Liver disease", "Bronchopneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Derek?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Trichinosis", "Arsenic poisoning", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Theodore Roosevelt?", "answers": ["Cholangiocarcinoma", "Pneumothorax", "Motor neuron disease", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marion Davies?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Stomach cancer", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Zora Neale Hurston?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Dengue fever", "Thyroid cancer", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Juliette Gordon Low?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Liver disease", "Cholera", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerry Paris?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Brain tumor", "Cerebral edema", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Taliferro?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Thrombosis", "Kidney Disease", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Mokaba?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "AIDS", "B-cell lymphoma", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jagdish Raj?", "answers": ["Melanoma", "Dementia", "Cardiac arrest", "Bronchopneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe C.?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Internal bleeding", "Celiac disease", "Kidney cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Will Sampson?", "answers": ["Malnutrition", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Enteritis", "Poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Will Sampson?", "answers": ["Wound", "Respiratory arrest", "Smoke inhalation", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bear Bryant?", "answers": ["Falling", "Dengue fever", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Catherine II of Russia?", "answers": ["Aortic dissection", "Pyaemia", "Paraquat", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Anton Wilson?", "answers": ["Binge drinking", "Cyanide poisoning", "Cardiac surgery", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Billy Preston?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Skin cancer", "Renal failure", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Woody Long?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Stroke", "Multiple sclerosis", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of O. Henry?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Respiratory Infection", "Cirrhosis", "Yellow fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Lutz?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Hepatitis C", "Cardiovascular disease", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Douglas Fairbanks?", "answers": ["Polycythemia", "Trichinosis", "Diarrhea", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Candace Pert?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Paraquat", "Cardiac arrest", "Traumatic brain injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bill Hicks?", "answers": ["Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Accidental Fire", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Puyi?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Renal Cancer", "Cardiomyopathy", "Motor neuron disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Puyi?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Aortic aneurysm", "Poisoning", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vito Russo?", "answers": ["Gallbladder cancer", "Brain Cancer", "AIDS", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen?", "answers": ["Cor pulmonale", "Epilepsy", "Congenital heart defect", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Sands?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Starvation", "Bronchopneumonia", "Skin cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jody Payne?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Bronchitis", "Tuberculosis", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Zachary Taylor?", "answers": ["Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Respiratory disease", "Kidney Disease", "Infectious disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Louis Pasteur?", "answers": ["Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Stroke", "Dengue fever", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jett Travolta?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Kidney cancer", "Throat cancer", "Seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jett Travolta?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Dehydration", "Kawasaki disease", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Grant McLennan?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Douglas Bader?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Pulmonary embolism", "Myocardial infarction", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Piet Mondrian?", "answers": ["Coronary artery disease", "Pneumonia", "Heart failure", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Allen Carr?", "answers": ["Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Lung cancer", "Asthma", "Yellow fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Helen Schucman?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Pancreatic cancer", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of GG Allin?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Infectious disease", "Synovial sarcoma", "Kawasaki disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nevin Spence?", "answers": ["Cancer of the larynx", "Insulinoma", "Poisoning", "Peritonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Amedeo Modigliani?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Anemia", "Cholera", "Colon Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Amedeo Modigliani?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Stroke", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stan Winston?", "answers": ["Multiple myeloma", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Dengue fever", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony Scott?", "answers": ["Fever", "Blunt trauma", "Cystic fibrosis", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Donna Summer?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Cancer", "Post-polio syndrome", "Yellow fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Donna Summer?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Atherosclerosis", "Rheumatic fever", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Norman Rockwell?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Polycythemia", "Lung cancer", "Starvation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Smita Patil?", "answers": ["Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Childbirth", "Cirrhosis", "Polycythemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Falk?", "answers": ["Debility", "Tongue Cancer", "Pneumonia", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Falk?", "answers": ["Mesothelioma", "Brain tumor", "Alzheimer's disease", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bruno Kirby?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Synovial sarcoma", "Trauma", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Tatum?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Heart failure", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Pleurisy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eli Whitney?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Prostate cancer", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fela Kuti?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "AIDS", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Alcohol intoxication"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chuck Hughes?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Coronary occlusion", "Diverticulosis", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Zara Cully?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Surgery", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Abebe Bikila?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Aplastic anemia", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joan Mir\u00f3?", "answers": ["Fever", "Cardiovascular disease", "Dehydration", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dorothy Kilgallen?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Myocardial infarction", "Physical abuse", "Endometrial cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Hipwell?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Head and neck cancer", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rita MacNeil?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Congenital heart defect", "Surgery", "Binge drinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Millar?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Coronary thrombosis", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Douglas Mawson?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Smallpox", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne d'Harnoncourt?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Embolism", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Howard Cosell?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Cardiovascular disease", "Thrombosis", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Isabella Beeton?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "Childbirth", "Coronary thrombosis", "Poison"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Isabella Beeton?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Puerperal fever", "Celiac disease", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ai Iijima?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Pneumonia", "Dengue fever", "Pyaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Norm Cash?", "answers": ["Testicular cancer", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Drowning", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bal Thackeray?", "answers": ["Shock", "Insulinoma", "Heart failure", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Lloyd George?", "answers": ["B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Aplastic anemia", "Cardiomyopathy", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Karac Pendragon Plant?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Chronic renal failure", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Deborah Raffin?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Tongue Cancer", "Gangrene", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rene Requiestas?", "answers": ["Coronary thrombosis", "Pancreatitis", "Uterine cancer", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Cochran?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Pulmonary edema", "Barbiturate", "Cyanide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Prince John of the United Kingdom?", "answers": ["Epilepsy", "Barbiturate overdose", "Epidemic typhus", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry McCormick?", "answers": ["Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Cancer", "Brain Cancer", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lincoln Hall?", "answers": ["Mesothelioma", "Perforated ulcer", "Pleurisy", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bridgette Andersen?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Bright's disease", "Drug overdose", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pete Postlethwaite?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Diabetes mellitus", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony Williams?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Hepatitis", "Myocardial infarction", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bingu wa Mutharika?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Epidemic typhus", "Gallbladder cancer", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Albert Einstein?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Fever", "Iatrogenesis", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ira Hayes?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Hypothermia", "Starvation", "Kawasaki disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mel Blanc?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Stroke", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mel Blanc?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Sleep apnea", "Poisoning", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mel Blanc?", "answers": ["Shock", "Physical abuse", "Chronic renal failure", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lani O'Grady?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Kidney cancer", "B-cell lymphoma", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Morris Ankrum?", "answers": ["Acute renal failure", "Trichinosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Reggie Lewis?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Geraldine McGee Rosenthal?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Drug overdose", "Brain Cancer", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nikola Tesla?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Tongue Cancer", "Coronary thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Antonin Artaud?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Head and neck cancer", "Seizure", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Colm Murray?", "answers": ["Falling", "Alcohol intoxication", "Cardiomegaly", "Motor neuron disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Big John Studd?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Synovial sarcoma", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Big John Studd?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Crohn's disease", "Epilepsy", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Driscoll?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Leukemia", "Anal cancer", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Driscoll?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Cardiovascular disease", "Childbirth", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of L\u00e9on Foucault?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Tuberculosis", "Multiple sclerosis", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Louis?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Rheumatic fever", "Encephalopathy", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Van Heflin?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Fever", "Alzheimer's disease", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miller Huggins?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Renal Cancer", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Pyaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Diamond?", "answers": ["Injury", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Throat cancer", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Freddy Fender?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Breast cancer", "Lung cancer", "Pyaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edie Sedgwick?", "answers": ["Coronary occlusion", "Barbiturate", "Physical abuse", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edie Sedgwick?", "answers": ["Renal Cancer", "Drug overdose", "Oral cancer", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Puff Johnson?", "answers": ["Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Embolism", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Cervical cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Brain tumor", "Hyperthermia", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lois DeBerry?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Peritonitis", "Chronic renal failure", "Intestinal Obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charlton Heston?", "answers": ["Accidental Fire", "Pneumonia", "Oral cancer", "Syphilis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wilhelm Grimm?", "answers": ["Pulmonary aspiration", "Dementia pugilistica", "Infection", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary Moore?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Synovial sarcoma", "Esophageal cancer", "Appendix cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William III of England?", "answers": ["Accidental Fire", "Crohn's disease", "Pneumonia", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Bronson?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Alzheimer's disease", "Thrombus", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Bronson?", "answers": ["Hepatitis", "Aneurysm", "Emphysema", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Princess Marina of Greece and Denmark?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Malnutrition", "Injury", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johannes Gutenberg?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Cardiomegaly", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Emily Bront\u00eb?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Tuberculosis", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leslie Carter?", "answers": ["Coronary artery disease", "Cirrhosis", "Heart failure", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Francesco Quinn?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Rheumatic fever", "Sepsis", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Griffith?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Wound", "Myocardial infarction", "Thyroid cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kathryn Joosten?", "answers": ["Crohn's disease", "Lung cancer", "Suffocation", "Anal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward Hardwicke?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Cancer", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Wellborn Root?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Gallbladder cancer", "Cerebral edema", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony Conigliaro?", "answers": ["Rheumatic fever", "Cardiovascular disease", "Thrombosis", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marvin Sease?", "answers": ["Gallbladder cancer", "Fever", "Poisoning", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ira Gershwin?", "answers": ["Tongue Cancer", "Cardiovascular disease", "Bleeding", "Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carol Wayne?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Cardiac arrest", "Heart cancer", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Patrick Swayze?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Colorectal cancer", "Throat cancer", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Forsythe?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Pneumonia", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Winfield?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Kidney cancer", "Injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Arthur Miller?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Heart failure", "Viral pneumonia", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Arthur Miller?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Malaria", "Cardiovascular disease", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Judy Holliday?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Heart cancer", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Pneumothorax"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sunil Dutt?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Suffocation", "Myocardial infarction", "Fournier gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vern Gosdin?", "answers": ["Blunt trauma", "Stroke", "Aplastic anemia", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ari Up?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Ovarian cancer", "Trauma", "Viral pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Daniel Jarque?", "answers": ["Intracranial aneurysm", "Muscular dystrophy", "Myocardial infarction", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brandon Tartikoff?", "answers": ["Septic shock", "Infection", "Lymphoma", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dobie Gray?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Injury", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Katrin Cartlidge?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Sepsis", "Hypertension", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Katrin Cartlidge?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Pneumonia", "Barbiturate", "Influenza"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Debarge?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "AIDS", "Toxoplasmosis", "Respiratory disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cristiano J\u00fanior?", "answers": ["Huntington's disease", "Uremia", "Myocardial infarction", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jean Harlow?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Synovial sarcoma", "AIDS", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack LaLanne?", "answers": ["Poison", "Pneumonia", "Liver disease", "Appendix cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack LaLanne?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Childbirth", "Arteriosclerosis", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anders Celsius?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Melanoma", "Cardiac arrest", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dorothy Dandridge?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Lung cancer", "Prostate cancer", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dorothy Dandridge?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Kidney Disease", "Perforated ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roald Dahl?", "answers": ["Congenital heart defect", "Blunt trauma", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dave Jennings?", "answers": ["Paraquat", "Sepsis", "Marfan syndrome", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Snyder?", "answers": ["Kidney cancer", "Leukemia", "Encephalitis", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Connelly?", "answers": ["Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Alzheimer's disease", "Lung cancer", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Norman Kirk?", "answers": ["Hepatitis", "Pyaemia", "Cardiovascular disease", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rosetta LeNoire?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Diabetes mellitus", "Head and neck cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Preston?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Acute pancreatitis", "Anorexia nervosa", "Rheumatic fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sir William Schwenck Gilbert?", "answers": ["Bubonic plague", "Myocardial infarction", "Fournier gangrene", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeffrey Hunter?", "answers": ["Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Aortic aneurysm", "Stroke", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeffrey Hunter?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Muscular dystrophy", "Poisoning", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shain Gandee?", "answers": ["Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Brain damage", "Brain Cancer", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marcus Garvey?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Cardiac arrest", "Cardiomegaly", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harold Hunter?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Drug overdose", "Binge drinking", "Kawasaki disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harold Hunter?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Bleeding", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pio of Pietrelcina?", "answers": ["Ruptured Aneurysm", "Myocardial infarction", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Lobar pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kate Wolf?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Thyroid cancer", "Arteriosclerosis", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Sexton?", "answers": ["Carbon monoxide poisoning", "AIDS", "Blunt trauma", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Palmer?", "answers": ["Hypertensive heart disease", "Alcoholism", "Myocardial infarction", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gerald Ford?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Binge drinking", "Cardiovascular disease", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Mapplethorpe?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Rheumatic fever", "AIDS", "Influenza"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bettie Page?", "answers": ["Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Burn", "Multiple myeloma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Kemp?", "answers": ["Insulinoma", "Bronchopneumonia", "Cancer", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Al Jolson?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Myocardial infarction", "Bronchopneumonia", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Moondyne Joe?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "B-cell lymphoma", "Myasthenia gravis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ken Caminiti?", "answers": ["Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Infectious disease", "Drug overdose", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ken Caminiti?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Brain damage", "Myocardial infarction", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Casablancas?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Melanoma", "Lobar pneumonia", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Tenta?", "answers": ["Aneurysm", "AIDS", "Bladder cancer", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Spike Milligan?", "answers": ["Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Renal failure", "Gallbladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johannes Brahms?", "answers": ["Wound", "Aplastic anemia", "Cancer", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rust Epique?", "answers": ["Congenital heart defect", "Coronary thrombosis", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kenneth Lay?", "answers": ["Kawasaki disease", "Diarrhea", "Myocardial infarction", "Schistosomiasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Darla Hood?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Heart failure", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Bright's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Darla Hood?", "answers": ["Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Hepatitis", "Respiratory arrest", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Akpor Pius Ewherido?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Arthritis", "Stroke", "Cor pulmonale"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Samuel Adams?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Dementia pugilistica", "Parkinson's disease", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Haile Selassie I?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Insulinoma", "Physical abuse", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Haile Selassie I?", "answers": ["Falling", "Respiratory failure", "Exhaustion", "Acral lentiginous melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Soo?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Hypertension", "Throat cancer", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chad Everett?", "answers": ["Insulinoma", "Lung cancer", "Marfan syndrome", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of E. E. Cummings?", "answers": ["Aneurysm", "Bleeding", "Morphine", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of E. E. Cummings?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Debility", "Mesothelioma", "Carbon monoxide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Fontaine?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Bright's disease", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brian Jones?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Hepatitis C", "Debility", "Infectious disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chaney Kley?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Testicular cancer", "Sleep apnea", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Gershwin?", "answers": ["Leiomyosarcoma", "Infection", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Benjamin Harrison?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Multiple sclerosis", "Ovarian cancer", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Griffith Jr.?", "answers": ["Pneumothorax", "Alcoholism", "Emphysema", "Aplastic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Infection", "Respiratory failure", "Lymphoma", "Multiple myeloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Houser?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Cystic fibrosis", "Nephritis", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Haskell?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Infectious disease", "Uterine cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard J. Corman?", "answers": ["Edema", "Alcohol intoxication", "Multiple myeloma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eiji Toyoda?", "answers": ["Acute renal failure", "Lung cancer", "Heart failure", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Sullivan?", "answers": ["Metastatic Melanoma", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Uterine cancer", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alex Higgins?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Puerperal fever", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Liver disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Murder of Lindsay Hawker?", "answers": ["B-cell lymphoma", "Asphyxia", "Throat cancer", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Lord?", "answers": ["Hepatitis C", "Kidney cancer", "Cardiovascular disease", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Surjit Bindrakhia?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Thrombosis", "Endometrial cancer", "Perforated ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bruce Chatwin?", "answers": ["Aortic dissection", "AIDS", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Koch?", "answers": ["Fournier gangrene", "Myocardial infarction", "Acute pancreatitis", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Prince Claus of the Netherlands?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Asthma", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Hodgkin's lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Julius Nyerere?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Dementia", "AIDS", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lizzie Borden?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Pneumonia", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ralph Earnhardt?", "answers": ["Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Aortic aneurysm", "Myocardial infarction", "Brain Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eleanor Powell?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Marfan syndrome", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Margaret Hamilton?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Fournier gangrene", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Henry Ford?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Trauma", "Traumatic brain injury", "Yellow fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robin Sachs?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Ovarian cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Appendix cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ken Kostick?", "answers": ["Thrombus", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Pancreatitis", "Liver disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard E Dauch?", "answers": ["Smallpox", "Cancer", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joanna Moore?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Emphysema", "Lung cancer", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Willi Ninja?", "answers": ["Synovial sarcoma", "Fournier gangrene", "Acute pancreatitis", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Willi Ninja?", "answers": ["Coronary occlusion", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Heart failure", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of P. Ramlee?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Emphysema", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sage Stallone?", "answers": ["Atherosclerosis", "Barbiturate overdose", "Colon Cancer", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sage Stallone?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Myocardial infarction", "Meningitis", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Castellano?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Ballistic trauma", "Dementia pugilistica", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lena Horne?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Bubonic plague", "Acute pancreatitis", "Lobar pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael James Heney?", "answers": ["Alcoholism", "Tuberculosis", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Yellow fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vladimir Garin?", "answers": ["Injury", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Toxoplasmosis", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dave DeBusschere?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Myocardial infarction", "Cystic fibrosis", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Randy Savage?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Liver tumour", "Arsenic poisoning", "Poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Danny Kaye?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Cyanide poisoning", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Hepatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Danny Kaye?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Myocardial infarction", "Anaphylaxis", "Aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Wirt Winchester?", "answers": ["Cardiac surgery", "Cholera", "Thrombosis", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Samantha Lewes?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Meningitis", "Physical abuse", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Santo?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Nephritis", "Myocardial infarction", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Django Reinhardt?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "AIDS", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nick Zoricic?", "answers": ["Craniocerebral Trauma", "Perforated ulcer", "Puerperal fever", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Jabara?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Bright's disease", "Prostate cancer", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tiberius?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Yellow fever", "Heart failure", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Martha Beall Mitchell?", "answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Multiple myeloma", "Appendix cancer", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Martha Beall Mitchell?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Edema", "Cancer", "Kawasaki disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ravi Shankar?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Cardiomegaly", "Encephalitis", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ravi Shankar?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Smoke inhalation", "Epilepsy", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Irons?", "answers": ["Dengue fever", "Myocardial infarction", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Motor neuron disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dylan Thomas?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Traumatic brain injury", "Pneumonia", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johnny Thunders?", "answers": ["Melanoma", "Pulmonary edema", "Drug overdose", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Noor Jehan?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Starvation", "Drowning", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Doug McClure?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Trauma", "Kidney cancer", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joan Sims?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Embolism", "Diverticulosis", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Armen Gilliam?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Myocardial infarction", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Bright's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Abdul Basit Abdus Samad?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Systemic scleroderma", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of J.J. Cale?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Barbiturate overdose", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rosalind Cash?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Tetanus", "Wound", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rico Yan?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Toxoplasmosis", "Colon Cancer", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sandra Dee?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Liver failure", "Pulmonary edema", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sandra Dee?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Dysentery", "Pneumonia", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Perry Ellis?", "answers": ["Cholangiocarcinoma", "Barbiturate", "Pulmonary aspiration", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Chandler?", "answers": ["Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Iatrogenesis", "Heart cancer", "Typhoid fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Chandler?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Renal failure", "Bleeding", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gene Siskel?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Trichinosis", "Tetanus", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eudora Welty?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Pneumonia", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yul Brynner?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Cardiomyopathy", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vincent Price?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Lung cancer", "Arthritis", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve James?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Chest pain", "Liver cancer", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Cancer", "Malaria", "Respiratory Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Stomach cancer", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sally Ride?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Pulmonary edema", "Pancreatic cancer", "Perforated ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gregory Hemingway?", "answers": ["Dementia pugilistica", "Peritonitis", "Hypertension", "Bright's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gregory Hemingway?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Appendix cancer", "Peritonitis", "Traumatic brain injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wassily Kandinsky?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Liver cancer", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Luciano Pavarotti?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Pancreatic cancer", "Anemia", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Ann Ganser?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Throat cancer", "Encephalitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dan Duryea?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Barbiturate overdose", "Gigantism", "Thyroid cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Knotts?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Asphyxia", "Trauma", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Meillon?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Brain tumor", "Liver disease", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gene Anthony Ray?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Perforated ulcer", "Stroke", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Niven?", "answers": ["Melanoma", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Motor neuron disease", "Pneumocystis pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buffalo Bill?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Gangrene", "Smoke inhalation", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Scott Newman?", "answers": ["Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Drug overdose", "Thrombus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kofi Awoonor?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Ballistic trauma", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alfredo Ferrari?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Blunt trauma", "Muscular dystrophy", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry Rickles?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Pneumonia", "Smoke inhalation", "Cyanide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Lanphier?", "answers": ["Asthma", "Stroke", "Binge drinking", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Maurice Oldham?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Parkinson's disease", "Edema", "Thrombus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bram Stoker?", "answers": ["Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Cholera", "Syphilis", "Septic shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Danny Joe Brown?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Cervical cancer", "Renal failure", "Smallpox"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Danny Joe Brown?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Choking", "Pyaemia", "Dementia with Lewy bodies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Natalie Wood?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Drowning", "Binge drinking", "Glioblastoma multiforme"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lucy Grealy?", "answers": ["Alcoholism", "Drug overdose", "Trauma", "Myasthenia gravis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paula Yates?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Drug overdose", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stephen J. Cannell?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Toxoplasmosis", "Lupus erythematosus", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Boz Burrell?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Hyperthermia", "Arthritis", "Hepatitis A"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Peterson?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Schistosomiasis", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Sauer?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Myocardial infarction", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lewis Grizzard?", "answers": ["Aortic dissection", "Accidental Fire", "Myocardial infarction", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rick James?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Stroke", "Prostate cancer", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rick James?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Appendix cancer", "Arthritis", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sergei Grinkov?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Respiratory disease", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Donald Neilson?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Mesothelioma", "Breast cancer", "Trichinosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stuart Cable?", "answers": ["Binge drinking", "Tuberculosis", "Anorexia nervosa", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brenda Fassie?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Dehydration", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Graham Chapman?", "answers": ["Renal Cancer", "Infection", "Appendix cancer", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Graham Chapman?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Aplastic anemia", "Cancer", "Iatrogenesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Graham Chapman?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Gigantism", "Spinal tumor", "Debility"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nicholas Colasanto?", "answers": ["Post-polio syndrome", "Myocardial infarction", "Falling", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Thor Heyerdahl?", "answers": ["Poison", "Brain tumor", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Louis Kahn?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Myocardial infarction", "Cholera", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eugene Allen?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Heart cancer", "Viral pneumonia", "Pernicious anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Donyale Luna?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Hepatitis C", "Drug overdose", "Myasthenia gravis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Spalding Gray?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Muscular dystrophy", "Iatrogenesis", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aldous Huxley?", "answers": ["Encephalopathy", "Skin cancer", "AIDS", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aldous Huxley?", "answers": ["Cancer of the larynx", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Diverticulosis", "Crohn's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Preston Tucker?", "answers": ["Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Chronic renal failure", "Leiomyosarcoma", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Preston Tucker?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Embolism", "Lung cancer", "Cerebral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Pastorelli?", "answers": ["Dengue fever", "Toxoplasmosis", "Hepatitis", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Igor Stravinsky?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Heart failure", "Cardiomegaly", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sukumari?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Aplastic anemia", "Cardiac arrest", "Pyaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roger Miller?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Blunt trauma", "Tetanus", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roger Miller?", "answers": ["B-cell lymphoma", "Chronic renal failure", "Liver tumour", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Smiley Burnette?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Cystic fibrosis", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Paraquat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Julie Vega?", "answers": ["Ischaemic heart disease", "Kidney cancer", "Melanoma", "Bronchopneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Julie Vega?", "answers": ["Arthritis", "Pernicious anemia", "Pancreatitis", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Julie Vega?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Pneumonia", "Dementia", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jackie Robinson?", "answers": ["Wound", "Multiple myeloma", "Myocardial infarction", "Epidural hematoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nicolette Larson?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Typhoid fever", "Cerebral edema", "Kawasaki disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sylvester?", "answers": ["Celiac disease", "AIDS", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jay Silverheels?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Epilepsy", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Healey?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Respiratory Infection", "Pancreatic cancer", "Gallbladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Grady?", "answers": ["Suffocation", "Bubonic plague", "Kidney cancer", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Enrico Fermi?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Acute renal failure", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hermann G\u00f6ring?", "answers": ["Poison", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul C\u00e9zanne?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Post-polio syndrome", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of MC Breed?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Renal failure", "Malnutrition", "Hodgkin's lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dominic Lucero?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Renal failure", "Lymphoma", "Colon Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dominic Lucero?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Shock", "Debility", "Influenza"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carole Landis?", "answers": ["Fever", "Drug overdose", "Cystic fibrosis", "Respiratory disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Walt Disney?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Myasthenia gravis", "Tuberculosis", "Appendix cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Cab Calloway?", "answers": ["Poison", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Stroke", "Pneumocystis pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sandy Dennis?", "answers": ["Gastrointestinal bleeding", "AIDS", "Skin cancer", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Vetter?", "answers": ["Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Uterine cancer", "Epidural hematoma", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Thomas Jefferson?", "answers": ["Craniocerebral Trauma", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Pneumonia", "Renal Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Dickinson?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Aortic aneurysm", "Barbiturate overdose", "Polycythemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Benjamin Guggenheim?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Drowning", "Hepatitis A", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Doohan?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Dementia", "Colorectal cancer", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Doohan?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Binge drinking", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Madge Sinclair?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Traumatic brain injury", "Schistosomiasis", "Hypertensive heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dev Anand?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Dehydration", "Liver failure", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dick Trickle?", "answers": ["Acute renal failure", "Arsenic poisoning", "Cardiomyopathy", "Ballistic trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richa Sharma?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Seizure", "Encephalopathy", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Boris Yeltsin?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Cardiovascular disease", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Boris Yeltsin?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Heart failure", "Nephropathy", "Respiratory disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anne Frank?", "answers": ["Appendix cancer", "Hypertension", "Epidemic typhus", "Binge drinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Kerouac?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Brain tumor", "Cirrhosis", "Lobar pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Herb Ritts?", "answers": ["Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Colon Cancer", "Alzheimer's disease", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jane Russell?", "answers": ["Liver failure", "Respiratory failure", "Alcohol intoxication", "Hepatocellular carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vivien Thomas?", "answers": ["Pneumothorax", "Pancreatic cancer", "Cyanide poisoning", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Russell Harty?", "answers": ["Hepatitis", "Systemic scleroderma", "Schistosomiasis", "Uremia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Stinson?", "answers": ["Respiratory disease", "Bright's disease", "Lupus erythematosus", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wilma Rudolph?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Lobar pneumonia", "Brain tumor", "Pyaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wilma Rudolph?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Bubonic plague", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Gallbladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mabel King?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Diabetes mellitus", "Multiple sclerosis", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mabel King?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Esophageal cancer", "Traumatic brain injury", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Montgomery Clift?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Colorectal cancer", "AIDS", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Freddie Mercury?", "answers": ["Aortic dissection", "AIDS", "Viral pneumonia", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Freddie Mercury?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Arthritis", "Dehydration", "Fournier gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Barbara Valentin?", "answers": ["Huntington's disease", "Stroke", "Malaria", "Tetanus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ann Sheridan?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Injury", "Esophageal cancer", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ann Sheridan?", "answers": ["Epidemic typhus", "Physical abuse", "Liver cancer", "Encephalitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Linda McCartney?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Breast cancer", "Cyanide poisoning", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lewis Miller?", "answers": ["Testicular cancer", "Nephropathy", "Cancer", "Traumatic brain injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lewis Miller?", "answers": ["Encephalopathy", "Infectious disease", "Heart cancer", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Slobodan Milo\u0161evi\u0107?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Myocardial infarction", "Cerebral edema", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jay Moriarty?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Kawasaki disease", "Encephalopathy", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of E. Lynn Harris?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Sleep apnea", "Cardiovascular disease", "Motor neuron disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of E. Lynn Harris?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Alcoholism", "Myocardial infarction", "Ballistic trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eric Fleming?", "answers": ["Hepatitis", "Pernicious anemia", "Drowning", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Juan Ponce de Le\u00f3n?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Poisoning", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Juan Ponce de Le\u00f3n?", "answers": ["Poison", "Anemia", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Elizabeth Taylor?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Lupus erythematosus", "Barbiturate", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ram Mohan Roy?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Meningitis", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mitch Mullany?", "answers": ["Meningitis", "Stroke", "Syphilis", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Corey Haim?", "answers": ["Infection", "Meningitis", "Pneumothorax", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Corey Haim?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Dehydration", "Traumatic brain injury", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nick Traina?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Trichinosis", "Ovarian cancer", "Accidental Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andrew MacNaughtan?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Starvation", "Epidemic typhus", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Menzies?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "Myocardial infarction", "Respiratory disease", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ottis Toole?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Pernicious anemia", "Cirrhosis", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sterling Hayden?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Prostate cancer", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yvette Vickers?", "answers": ["Metastatic Melanoma", "Lupus erythematosus", "Heart failure", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vince Lombardi?", "answers": ["Coronary occlusion", "Alzheimer's disease", "Colorectal cancer", "Appendix cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vince Lombardi?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Anemia", "Smallpox"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Wells?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Tuberculosis", "Cancer of the larynx", "Cerebral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Baba Amte?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Lung cancer", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sandy West?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Traumatic brain injury", "Insulinoma", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sandy West?", "answers": ["Edema", "Esophageal cancer", "Arsenic poisoning", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gordon MacRae?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Oral cancer", "Polymyalgia rheumatica"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gordon MacRae?", "answers": ["Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Pneumonia", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Karen Carpenter?", "answers": ["Uterine cancer", "Anorexia nervosa", "Embolism", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gerald Anthony?", "answers": ["Encephalitis", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Myocardial infarction", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Trevor Barker?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Lupus erythematosus", "Puerperal fever", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dolph Sweet?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Barbiturate", "Tongue Cancer", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Wayne?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Exhaustion", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Wayne?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Poison", "Polycythemia", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Wayne?", "answers": ["Cancer of the larynx", "Myocardial infarction", "Tongue Cancer", "Hypertensive heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Coltrane?", "answers": ["Pulmonary edema", "Rheumatic fever", "Liver tumour", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Titus?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Fever", "Stroke", "Epidemic typhus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charlie Christian?", "answers": ["Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Respiratory Infection", "Tuberculosis", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Slim Dusty?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Physical abuse", "Cancer of the larynx", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gilbert Roland?", "answers": ["Anorexia nervosa", "Rheumatic fever", "Post-polio syndrome", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ronnie James Dio?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Gigantism", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Moore?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Myasthenia gravis", "Atherosclerosis", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frankie Howerd?", "answers": ["Cardiomegaly", "Traumatic brain injury", "Poisoning", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Davis?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Myocardial infarction", "Tetanus", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Erik Bruhn?", "answers": ["Lupus erythematosus", "Lung cancer", "Infectious disease", "Ruptured Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Erik Bruhn?", "answers": ["Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Uremia", "Tetanus", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joey Bishop?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Nephritis", "Heart failure", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marie Dressler?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Cancer of the larynx", "Trauma", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Franz Schubert?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Ballistic trauma", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Franz Schubert?", "answers": ["Trichinosis", "Drug overdose", "Syphilis", "Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roddy McDowall?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Septic shock", "Dehydration", "Liver disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pat Summerall?", "answers": ["Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Cardiac arrest", "Brain tumor", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rosalia Lombardo?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Pneumonia", "Thrombosis", "Poison"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of M. F. Husain?", "answers": ["Burn", "Stroke", "Myocardial infarction", "Fournier gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Williams?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Uremia", "Malaria", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gustave Eiffel?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Respiratory disease", "Chest pain", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ward Bond?", "answers": ["Infectious disease", "Multiple sclerosis", "Cor pulmonale", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kim Manners?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Lung cancer", "Liver disease", "Seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sarah Charlesworth?", "answers": ["Fever", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Fever", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Alexander Schumann?", "answers": ["Nephritis", "Lymphoma", "B-cell lymphoma", "Syphilis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Alexander Schumann?", "answers": ["Exhaustion", "Hyperthermia", "Pneumonia", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Denholm Elliott?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Tuberculosis", "Liver disease", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Denholm Elliott?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Tetanus", "Huntington's disease", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anita Roddick?", "answers": ["B-cell lymphoma", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Thrombosis", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shobhan Babu?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Asthma", "Malaria", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Manzarek?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Cancer", "Asthma", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ray Manzarek?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Linus Pauling?", "answers": ["Iatrogenesis", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Cancer", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Linus Pauling?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Motor neuron disease", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christian Ben\u00edtez?", "answers": ["Choking", "Appendix cancer", "Heart failure", "Pneumocystis pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Glenn Ford?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Meningitis", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Laurence Olivier?", "answers": ["Meningitis", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Testicular cancer", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Laurence Olivier?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Renal failure", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Yellow fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vishnuvardhan?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Smoke inhalation", "Bright's disease", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Reeve?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Sepsis", "Epidural hematoma", "Myelodysplastic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Reeve?", "answers": ["Renal Cancer", "Exhaustion", "Cardiac arrest", "Multiple myeloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Reeve?", "answers": ["Chronic renal failure", "Epidural hematoma", "Appendix cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christopher Reeve?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Pancreatitis", "Cardiovascular disease", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Enrico Caruso?", "answers": ["Poison", "Childbirth", "Drowning", "Peritonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marky Cielo?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Bronchitis", "Colorectal cancer", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Casey Calvert?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "AIDS", "Cancer of the larynx", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Friedrich Nietzsche?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Pneumonia", "Schistosomiasis", "Anaphylaxis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alfred Hitchcock?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Yellow fever", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rock Hudson?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Infectious disease", "Mesothelioma", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerry Reed?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Uremia", "Appendix cancer", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anita O'Day?", "answers": ["Iatrogenesis", "Perforated ulcer", "Myocardial infarction", "Dementia with Lewy bodies"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anita O'Day?", "answers": ["Iatrogenesis", "Pneumonia", "Meningitis", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Elisabeth Sladen?", "answers": ["Celiac disease", "Head and neck cancer", "Cancer", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dan Dailey?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Ovarian cancer", "Anemia", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Crichton?", "answers": ["Kidney cancer", "Throat cancer", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Lobar pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Crichton?", "answers": ["Synovial sarcoma", "Cancer", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Zappa?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Rheumatic fever", "Drowning", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dana Hill?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Barbiturate overdose", "Hyperthermia", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dana Hill?", "answers": ["Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Diabetes mellitus", "Barbiturate", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Orwell?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Thyroid cancer", "Malnutrition", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gene Kelly?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Stroke", "Sepsis", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of MC Trouble?", "answers": ["Thrombus", "Dysentery", "Liver cancer", "Seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Debra Hill?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Heart failure", "Cancer", "Acral lentiginous melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Desiderius Erasmus?", "answers": ["Paraquat", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Anal cancer", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Erwin Schr\u00f6dinger?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Hepatitis A", "Tuberculosis", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Carlson?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Alcohol intoxication", "AIDS", "Celiac disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sikandar Sanam?", "answers": ["Pyaemia", "Liver cancer", "Pulmonary edema", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ryan White?", "answers": ["Synovial sarcoma", "Spinal tumor", "Pneumonia", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gary David Goldberg?", "answers": ["Kidney Disease", "Brain Cancer", "Brain damage", "Pleurisy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dick Powell?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Cardiovascular disease", "Lymphoma", "Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shannon Hoon?", "answers": ["Aortic aneurysm", "Accidental Fire", "Respiratory disease", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Daniel Gordon-Levitt?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Drug overdose", "Cervical cancer", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andrew Johnson?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Slim Pickens?", "answers": ["Multiple myeloma", "Nephritis", "Anemia", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ozzie Nelson?", "answers": ["Injury", "Alcoholism", "Cyanide poisoning", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ozzie Nelson?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Liver tumour", "Enteritis", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of LaVerne Andrews?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Post-polio syndrome", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Gipp?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Coronary artery disease", "Pneumonia", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Karen Blixen?", "answers": ["Burn", "Malnutrition", "Heart failure", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Hanneman?", "answers": ["Appendix cancer", "Dengue fever", "Liver failure", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Murali?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Polymyalgia rheumatica", "Multiple myeloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Laura Branigan?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Barbiturate overdose", "Septic shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charlotte Coleman?", "answers": ["Aortic aneurysm", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mike Bloomfield?", "answers": ["Perforated ulcer", "Drug overdose", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Haystacks Calhoun?", "answers": ["Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Diabetes mellitus", "Paraquat", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Forrest?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Cancer", "Aspiration pneumonia", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jacques Brel?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Liver tumour", "Lung cancer", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Betty Grable?", "answers": ["Respiratory disease", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Lung cancer", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Packer?", "answers": ["Cystic fibrosis", "Pneumonia", "Fever", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Packer?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Bright's disease", "Cystic fibrosis", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Francis Drake?", "answers": ["Aplastic anemia", "Dysentery", "Epidural hematoma", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Dassin?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Cardiomyopathy", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Napoleon Bonaparte?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Nephritis", "Epidemic typhus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Scotty Beckett?", "answers": ["Smoke inhalation", "Drug overdose", "Syphilis", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stephen F. Austin?", "answers": ["Kawasaki disease", "Influenza", "Influenza", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bertrand Russell?", "answers": ["Gallbladder cancer", "Influenza", "Bronchopneumonia", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gene Rayburn?", "answers": ["Accidental Fire", "Puerperal fever", "Gallbladder cancer", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Teresa Teng?", "answers": ["Kawasaki disease", "Infection", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Veronica Lake?", "answers": ["Pleurisy", "Hepatitis", "Cystic fibrosis", "Wound"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Veronica Lake?", "answers": ["Skin cancer", "Acute renal failure", "Trauma", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Veronica Lake?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Skin cancer", "Renal failure", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Spencer Tracy?", "answers": ["Congenital heart defect", "Insulinoma", "Cervical cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy Campanella?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Head and neck cancer", "Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dennis Weaver?", "answers": ["Physical abuse", "Diabetes mellitus", "Cancer", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aaron Burr?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hussein of Jordan?", "answers": ["Arthritis", "Colon Cancer", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vincent Schiavelli?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "Lung cancer", "Tongue Cancer", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lenny Bruce?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Hypertension", "Encephalopathy", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eduardo Palomo?", "answers": ["Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Leukemia", "Myocardial infarction", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Ann Bugg?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Hypothermia", "Tuberculosis", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Telly Savalas?", "answers": ["Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Renal Cancer", "Prostate cancer", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Telly Savalas?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Bladder cancer", "Sepsis", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Louis Armstrong?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Myocardial infarction", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lalit Suri?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Cardiovascular disease", "Cyanide poisoning", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tyrone Davis?", "answers": ["Spinal tumor", "Ballistic trauma", "Stroke", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alex Harvey?", "answers": ["Bright's disease", "Smallpox", "Myocardial infarction", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jean-Paul Sartre?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Nephropathy", "Pleurisy", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Patrick Henry?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Liver disease", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fred Gwynne?", "answers": ["Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "AIDS", "Pancreatic cancer", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mel Smith?", "answers": ["Aplastic anemia", "Myasthenia gravis", "Myocardial infarction", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ottavio Quattrocchi?", "answers": ["Infection", "Malnutrition", "Myocardial infarction", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ottavio Quattrocchi?", "answers": ["Synovial sarcoma", "Toxoplasmosis", "Stroke", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Cardiac arrest", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dom DeLuise?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Uremia", "Cirrhosis", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dom DeLuise?", "answers": ["Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Pulmonary aspiration", "Liver disease", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alan Whicker?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Barbiturate", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ava Gardner?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Aortic aneurysm", "Barbiturate", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Malcolm Marshall?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Puerperal fever", "Respiratory arrest", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Matthew Garber?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Epidural hematoma", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hattie Jacques?", "answers": ["Insulinoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Cardiac surgery", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anna Massey?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Cancer", "Injury", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marc Hunter?", "answers": ["Hypertensive heart disease", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Throat cancer", "Testicular cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bugs Moran?", "answers": ["Ruptured Aneurysm", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Enteritis", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Betty Shabazz?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Burn", "Injury", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hank the Angry Drunken Dwarf?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Cirrhosis", "Edema", "Post-polio syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eva Braun?", "answers": ["Choking", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Alcohol intoxication", "Cyanide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Henry David Thoreau?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Accidental Fire", "Embolism", "Brain Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ho Chi Minh?", "answers": ["Edema", "Heart failure", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lou Rawls?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Kawasaki disease", "Liver failure", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lou Rawls?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Pernicious anemia", "Smoke inhalation", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Newman?", "answers": ["Infectious disease", "Rheumatic fever", "Respiratory Infection", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Irene Ryan?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Stroke", "Barbiturate overdose", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Benedict?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Myocardial infarction", "Falling", "Peritonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Heath Ledger?", "answers": ["Heart cancer", "Drug overdose", "Arsenic poisoning", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nirmal Pandey?", "answers": ["Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Myocardial infarction", "Muscular dystrophy", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Duke?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Coronary thrombosis", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Duke?", "answers": ["Pleurisy", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome", "Aneurysm", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Faulkner?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Pleurisy", "Debility", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alan Turing?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Hepatitis C", "Nephritis", "Cyanide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of King Ludwig II of Bavaria?", "answers": ["Leiomyosarcoma", "Childbirth", "Drowning", "Starvation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Farentino?", "answers": ["Asthma", "Stroke", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tony Greig?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Cancer", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy Orbison?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Hypertension", "Diabetes mellitus", "Polycythemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marlene Dietrich?", "answers": ["Exhaustion", "Renal failure", "Sleep apnea", "Appendix cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Reggie White?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Colon Cancer", "Barbiturate", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Golda Meir?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Fournier gangrene", "Pleurisy", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of \"Ron \"\"Pigpen\"\" McKernan\"?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Head and neck cancer", "Drug overdose", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vasco da Gama?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Malaria", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Huntington's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bud Day?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Puerperal fever", "Binge drinking", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Caroline Knapp?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Insulinoma", "Malaria", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Caroline Knapp?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Cancer", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marcheline Bertrand?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Syphilis", "Gigantism", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Davis?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Starvation", "Multiple myeloma", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Davis?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Brain tumor", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Elizabeth Glaser?", "answers": ["Morphine", "AIDS", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Schistosomiasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kathryn Kuhlman?", "answers": ["Bubonic plague", "Cardiac surgery", "Colon Cancer", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kathryn Kuhlman?", "answers": ["Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Surgery", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Panozzo?", "answers": ["Acute renal failure", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Weng Weng?", "answers": ["Cardiomegaly", "Liver disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Kidney cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Reginald Lewis?", "answers": ["Meningitis", "Childbirth", "Trauma", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rory Markas?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Heart failure", "Morphine", "Kidney Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Farrah Fawcett?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Barbiturate overdose", "Smallpox", "Starvation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leonard Frey?", "answers": ["Asthma", "AIDS", "Head and neck cancer", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Betty MacDonald?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Cancer", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Multiple organ dysfunction syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frida Kahlo?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Hyperthermia", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Cancer of the larynx"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bernadette Soubirous?", "answers": ["Congenital heart defect", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Tuberculosis", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Benjamin Franklin?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Skin cancer", "Endometrial cancer", "Pleurisy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gregory Hines?", "answers": ["Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Head and neck cancer", "Dementia pugilistica", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gregory Hines?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Liver tumour", "Intestinal Obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Reeves?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Parkinson's disease", "Lymphoma", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Omar Henry?", "answers": ["Pernicious anemia", "Respiratory arrest", "Gallbladder cancer", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary McLeod Bethune?", "answers": ["Aspiration pneumonia", "Dehydration", "Physical abuse", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Billy Thorpe?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Liver tumour", "Myocardial infarction", "Hepatitis C"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buddy Rich?", "answers": ["Metastatic Melanoma", "Brain tumor", "Typhoid fever", "Wound"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buddy Rich?", "answers": ["Intracranial aneurysm", "Cardiovascular disease", "Alzheimer's disease", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Taylor?", "answers": ["Acute renal failure", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Coronary artery disease", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry Riley?", "answers": ["B-cell lymphoma", "Enteritis", "Renal failure", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Larry Riley?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Aneurysm", "Stroke", "B-cell lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wilson Rawls?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Cancer", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Pernicious anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joseph McCarthy?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Hepatitis", "Cancer", "Suffocation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Gerstle?", "answers": ["Cystic fibrosis", "Cancer", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ricardo Montalb\u00e1n?", "answers": ["Infection", "Celiac disease", "Kawasaki disease", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Agnes Moorehead?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Atherosclerosis", "Skull fracture", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Agnes Moorehead?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Uterine cancer", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Stynes?", "answers": ["Bacterial pneumonia", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Cancer", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ted Williams?", "answers": ["Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Congenital heart defect", "Chest pain", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of T. S. Eliot?", "answers": ["Head and neck cancer", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Emphysema", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Davie Cooper?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Tongue Cancer", "Puerperal fever", "Ballistic trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Landry?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Puerperal fever", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Catfish Hunter?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Motor neuron disease", "Pleurisy", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward R. Murrow?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Diverticulosis", "Lung cancer", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward R. Murrow?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Infectious disease", "Malaria", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Patrick Nagel?", "answers": ["Coronary thrombosis", "Gigantism", "Typhoid fever", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marco Pantani?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Drug overdose", "Hypertension", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marco Pantani?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Infection", "Cervical cancer", "Progressive supranuclear palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marco Pantani?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Cystic fibrosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Liver disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Timothy Leary?", "answers": ["Polycythemia", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Thrombosis", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Luke Kelly?", "answers": ["Spinal tumor", "Stroke", "Brain tumor", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jesse Marunde?", "answers": ["Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Thyroid cancer", "Aplastic anemia", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harold Holt?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Liver tumour", "Alcohol intoxication", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Irene Dunne?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Pulmonary edema", "Heart failure", "Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nazia Hassan?", "answers": ["Acute pancreatitis", "Lung cancer", "Aplastic anemia", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nell Carter?", "answers": ["Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Diabetes mellitus", "Hepatitis A", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nell Carter?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Choking", "Cardiovascular disease", "Rheumatic fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Scranton?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Little Willie John?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Gangrene", "Cholera", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Adolph Caesar?", "answers": ["Binge drinking", "Myocardial infarction", "Encephalopathy", "Binge drinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Whitman Mayo?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Brain damage", "Myocardial infarction", "Skin cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frederic Remington?", "answers": ["Burn", "Encephalopathy", "Peritonitis", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rick Rude?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Cholera", "Cardiovascular disease", "Embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of J. T. Walsh?", "answers": ["Anal cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Loulou de la Falaise?", "answers": ["Encephalopathy", "Bronchitis", "Myasthenia gravis", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Bukowski?", "answers": ["Smallpox", "Smoke inhalation", "Stomach cancer", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tammy Wynette?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Liver disease", "Bubonic plague", "Thrombus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Norman Vincent Peale?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Thrombus", "Mesothelioma", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brian Epstein?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Drug overdose", "Thrombus", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hank Gathers?", "answers": ["Rheumatic fever", "Cardiac arrest", "Hyperthermia", "Epilepsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hank Gathers?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Cholera", "Edema", "Barbiturate overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of F\u00e9lix Faure?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Respiratory Infection", "Myocardial infarction", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harry Agganis?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Melanoma", "Oral cancer", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johnny Paycheck?", "answers": ["Epilepsy", "Mesothelioma", "Respiratory arrest", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johnny Paycheck?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Aneurysm", "Epilepsy", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rosal\u00eda Mera?", "answers": ["Appendix cancer", "Myasthenia gravis", "Influenza", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Hug?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Hepatitis", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Milton William Cooper?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Exhaustion", "Accidental Fire", "Ballistic trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ernie Wise?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Congenital heart defect", "Enteritis", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ernie Wise?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Intracranial aneurysm", "Suffocation", "Acute pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pol Pot?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Respiratory arrest", "Myocardial infarction", "Acute renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Martin Van Buren?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Hepatitis", "Cardiovascular disease", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Martin Van Buren?", "answers": ["Myasthenia gravis", "Asthma", "Pancreatic cancer", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Toren Smith?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Drug overdose", "Syphilis", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeff Porcaro?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Hepatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Colby?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Nephritis", "Drowning", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eve Arden?", "answers": ["Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Cancer", "Malaria", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eve Arden?", "answers": ["Cholera", "Bacterial pneumonia", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Cardiovascular disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eve Arden?", "answers": ["Aspiration pneumonia", "Injury", "Drowning", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kerry Packer?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Arteriosclerosis", "Encephalopathy", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Barrymore?", "answers": ["Encephalopathy", "Emphysema", "Cirrhosis", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Barrymore?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Malaria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Wallace?", "answers": ["Crohn's disease", "Thrombus", "Meningitis", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andrew Jackson?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Lobar pneumonia", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Stomach cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Louis XV of France?", "answers": ["Myasthenia gravis", "Smallpox", "Syphilis", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Slim Whitman?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Thrombosis", "Heart failure", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dan Wheldon?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Diarrhea", "Head and neck cancer", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eliot Ness?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Insulinoma", "Cor pulmonale", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Virginia Mayo?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Colorectal cancer", "Hepatitis", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Virginia Mayo?", "answers": ["Aspiration pneumonia", "Liver cancer", "Infectious disease", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Virginia Mayo?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Anaphylaxis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Laurence Harvey?", "answers": ["B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Stomach cancer", "Puerperal fever", "Thyroid cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Josef Mengele?", "answers": ["Epidural hematoma", "Drowning", "Anal cancer", "Rheumatic fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bernadette Nolan?", "answers": ["Falling", "Paraquat", "Breast cancer", "Alcohol intoxication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Curtis Mayfield?", "answers": ["Head and neck cancer", "Colon Cancer", "Appendix cancer", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Lynch?", "answers": ["Hepatitis A", "Alcohol intoxication", "Myocardial infarction", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sam Loeb?", "answers": ["Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Iatrogenesis", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James I of England?", "answers": ["Crohn's disease", "Stroke", "Systemic scleroderma", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andy Whitfield?", "answers": ["Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Nephritis", "Cystic fibrosis", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Typhoid Mary?", "answers": ["Nephritis", "Pneumonia", "Enteritis", "Endometrial cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Zelda Rubinstein?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Yellow fever", "Renal failure", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Zelda Rubinstein?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Respiratory failure", "Anorexia nervosa", "Enteritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Maynard Ferguson?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Tongue Cancer", "Asphyxia", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joseph Valachi?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Pulmonary edema", "Hepatitis A", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Herbert M. Allison?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Dehydration", "Myocardial infarction", "Binge drinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Murray Hamilton?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Brain tumor", "Cardiomyopathy", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Denny Doherty?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Poisoning", "Renal Cancer", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roger Voudouris?", "answers": ["Hepatitis", "Wound", "Muscular dystrophy", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ma Rainey?", "answers": ["Heart cancer", "Myocardial infarction", "Coronary occlusion", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Doug Sahm?", "answers": ["Ovarian cancer", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Myocardial infarction", "Aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter the Great?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Falling", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Josephine Baker?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Hyperthermia", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kwame Nkrumah?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Trauma", "Skin cancer", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kwame Nkrumah?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Exhaustion", "Cancer", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Jones?", "answers": ["Respiratory failure", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Choking", "Cyanide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pocahontas?", "answers": ["Smallpox", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Hypothermia", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pocahontas?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Brain damage", "Multiple myeloma", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pocahontas?", "answers": ["Asthma", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Prostate cancer", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yip Man?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Throat cancer", "Synovial sarcoma", "Multiple myeloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Yip Man?", "answers": ["Head and neck cancer", "Bone cancer", "Malaria", "Endometrial cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lou Costello?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Endometrial cancer", "Lobar pneumonia", "Poison"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart?", "answers": ["Respiratory disease", "Liver failure", "Bronchitis", "Rheumatic fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Vivien Leigh?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Tuberculosis", "Renal Cancer", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nancy Marchand?", "answers": ["Bacterial pneumonia", "Pyaemia", "Lung cancer", "Septic shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nancy Marchand?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Lupus erythematosus", "Hepatitis", "Myelodysplastic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nandi?", "answers": ["Smoke inhalation", "Poisoning", "Barbiturate overdose", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Franz Liszt?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Bronchopneumonia", "Encephalopathy", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alice Pearce?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Sepsis", "Ovarian cancer", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Talbot?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Traumatic brain injury", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Atkins?", "answers": ["Esophageal cancer", "Cancer", "Chest pain", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Atkins?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Hypertension", "Anaphylaxis", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Red Skelton?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Hepatitis C", "Glioblastoma multiforme", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jeremy Beadle?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Schistosomiasis", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nargis?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Drug overdose", "Pneumothorax", "Pancreatic cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Lynde?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Cholera", "Myocardial infarction", "Pulmonary embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Anaphylaxis", "Brain damage", "Myasthenia gravis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johann Sebastian Bach?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Stroke", "Chronic renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Paul Demayo?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Drug overdose", "Brain tumor", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Cassavetes?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Uremia", "Renal Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Troy Donahue?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Insulinoma", "Brain damage", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lhasa de Sela?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Ballistic trauma", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robin Bush?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Liver disease", "Leukemia", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mark Sandman?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Injury", "Debility", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johnny Ramone?", "answers": ["Cholangiocarcinoma", "Bone cancer", "Cancer", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johnny Ramone?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Hepatitis", "Uterine cancer", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alan Wilson?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Cor pulmonale", "Drug overdose", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alan Wilson?", "answers": ["Cor pulmonale", "Gangrene", "Barbiturate", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ian Fleming?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Myocardial infarction", "Fournier gangrene", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sonny Liston?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Pneumothorax", "Diabetes mellitus", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Hopper?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Pneumonia", "Progressive supranuclear palsy", "Esophageal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Hopper?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Uterine cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Merv Griffin?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Prostate cancer", "Epidural hematoma", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Max Weber?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Multiple sclerosis", "Spinal tumor", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Moms Mabley?", "answers": ["Viral pneumonia", "Enteritis", "Fever", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joe Paterno?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Sleep apnea", "Cyanide poisoning", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward Winter?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Pneumonia", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Munden?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Cardiac arrest", "Pneumothorax", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jon-Erik Hexum?", "answers": ["Traumatic brain injury", "Pancreatitis", "Hepatitis C", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andr\u00e9 the Giant?", "answers": ["Gigantism", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andr\u00e9 the Giant?", "answers": ["Epidemic typhus", "Trauma", "Thyroid cancer", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andr\u00e9 the Giant?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Aneurysm", "Myocardial infarction", "Polycythemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Erroll Garner?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Bladder cancer", "Cardiomegaly", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edd Gould?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Cystic fibrosis", "Starvation", "Respiratory disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward Said?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Falling", "Suffocation", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward Said?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Epilepsy", "Fournier gangrene", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jonathan Larson?", "answers": ["Kawasaki disease", "Aortic dissection", "Respiratory Infection", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jonathan Larson?", "answers": ["Aspiration pneumonia", "Coronary thrombosis", "Marfan syndrome", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rich Cronin?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Heart cancer", "Leukemia", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Julie Harris?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Manute Bol?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Acral lentiginous melanoma", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Philipp\u00e9 Wynne?", "answers": ["Aplastic anemia", "Post-polio syndrome", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Steve Walsh?", "answers": ["Trichinosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Liver failure", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harry H. Corbett?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Injury", "Appendix cancer", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jules L\u00e9otard?", "answers": ["Coronary occlusion", "Arsenic poisoning", "Brain tumor", "Infectious disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jules L\u00e9otard?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Smallpox", "Parkinson's disease", "Pneumocystis pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Boxcar Willie?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Ovarian cancer", "Iatrogenesis", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Duke Ellington?", "answers": ["Muscular dystrophy", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Thyroid cancer", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Duke Ellington?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Cystic fibrosis", "Yellow fever", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Grace Darling?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Nephropathy", "Sepsis", "Dengue fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Waterfield?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Perforated ulcer", "Respiratory failure", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of C. Wright Mills?", "answers": ["Pernicious anemia", "Myocardial infarction", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Myocardial infarction", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Respiratory disease", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Exhaustion", "Dementia pugilistica", "Coronary artery disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Franco Moschino?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Trauma", "Colon Cancer", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Annette Funicello?", "answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Infection", "Meningeal Tuberculosis", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Reinhard Heydrich?", "answers": ["Infection", "Septic shock", "Respiratory failure", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Stewart?", "answers": ["Testicular cancer", "Stroke", "Leukemia", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dada Kondke?", "answers": ["Encephalopathy", "Colon Cancer", "Morphine", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Lennon?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Falling", "Ballistic trauma", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gloria Foster?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Bladder cancer", "Renal Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ptolemy XIII Theos Philopator?", "answers": ["Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Drowning", "Hypertension", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Kamen?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Hyperthermia", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Moses Gunn?", "answers": ["Asthma", "Choking", "Diarrhea", "Carbon monoxide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richie Havens?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Uremia", "Pulmonary embolism", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Formby?", "answers": ["Traumatic brain injury", "Myocardial infarction", "Lung cancer", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bill Walsh?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Bright's disease", "Appendix cancer", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Theresa Merritt?", "answers": ["Glioblastoma multiforme", "B-cell lymphoma", "Skin cancer", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Emile Griffith?", "answers": ["Aortic dissection", "Iatrogenesis", "Dementia pugilistica", "Thyroid cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Emile Griffith?", "answers": ["Shock", "Renal failure", "Lung cancer", "Bacterial pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Fitzgerald?", "answers": ["Aortic aneurysm", "Asthma", "Cancer", "Kidney cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Fitzgerald?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Syphilis", "Burn", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Ozanam?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Starvation", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John McCrae?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Stroke", "Binge drinking", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buddy Miles?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Hepatitis C", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Pneumocystis pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gwen Watford?", "answers": ["Tongue Cancer", "Cystic fibrosis", "Cancer", "Systemic scleroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Johnny Weissmuller?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Pneumonia", "Pulmonary edema", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Teresa of \u00c1vila?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Coronary occlusion", "Trichinosis", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Clifford Antone?", "answers": ["Edema", "Congenital heart defect", "Cirrhosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Anthony Peck?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Cancer", "Pernicious anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Abdel Halim Hafez?", "answers": ["Coronary thrombosis", "Schistosomiasis", "Alcoholism", "Wound"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Abdel Halim Hafez?", "answers": ["Debility", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Renal failure", "Yellow fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Meena Kumari?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Traumatic brain injury", "Cirrhosis", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Christy Brown?", "answers": ["Choking", "Congenital heart defect", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Buster Crabbe?", "answers": ["Viral pneumonia", "Dementia", "Hepatitis C", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Badja Djola?", "answers": ["Congenital heart defect", "Myocardial infarction", "Liver cancer", "Aortic aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tom Cheek?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Sleep apnea", "Brain tumor", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gino Hernandez?", "answers": ["Leiomyosarcoma", "Drug overdose", "Gigantism", "Anorexia nervosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Juana Maria?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Smallpox", "Cardiac surgery", "Ballistic trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Zig Ziglar?", "answers": ["Ballistic trauma", "Pneumonia", "Cardiomegaly", "Brain Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carmen Miranda?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Bronchopneumonia", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Amanda Blake?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Alzheimer's disease", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gia Scala?", "answers": ["Lobar pneumonia", "Encephalopathy", "Drug overdose", "Alzheimer's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Stonewall Jackson?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Internal bleeding", "Pneumonia", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Syd Barrett?", "answers": ["Respiratory Infection", "Cancer", "Pulmonary edema", "Emphysema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Syd Barrett?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Burn", "Encephalopathy", "Smoke inhalation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Dodson?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Multiple sclerosis", "Acute renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mike Von Erich?", "answers": ["Exhaustion", "Atherosclerosis", "Marfan syndrome", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dutch Savage?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Chronic myelogenous leukemia", "Stroke", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ansel Adams?", "answers": ["Systemic scleroderma", "Cardiovascular disease", "Falling", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Don Drysdale?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Throat cancer", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bernie Winters?", "answers": ["Stomach cancer", "Thyroid cancer", "Thyroid cancer", "Bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fyodor Dostoyevsky?", "answers": ["Liver cancer", "Epilepsy", "Renal failure", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fyodor Dostoyevsky?", "answers": ["Pulmonary edema", "Colon Cancer", "Emphysema", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Maria Schneider?", "answers": ["Multiple myeloma", "Suffocation", "Cancer", "Head and neck cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gordon Jackson?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Bone cancer", "Craniocerebral Trauma", "Celiac disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gordon Jackson?", "answers": ["Cerebral thrombosis", "Cancer", "AIDS", "Cholangiocarcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Julia Child?", "answers": ["Bronchopneumonia", "Aplastic anemia", "Renal failure", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Beard?", "answers": ["Embolism", "Paraquat", "Cancer", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Feynman?", "answers": ["Renal cell carcinoma", "Cancer", "Anorexia nervosa", "Poison"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wade Dom\u00ednguez?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Cardiac surgery", "Respiratory failure", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nicholas Clay?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Liver cancer", "Huntington's disease", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Billie Holiday?", "answers": ["Fournier gangrene", "Trichinosis", "Cirrhosis", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jiddu Krishnamurti?", "answers": ["Cardiomyopathy", "Parkinson's disease", "Pancreatic cancer", "Congenital heart defect"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lorenzo Odone?", "answers": ["Marfan syndrome", "Aspiration pneumonia", "Spinal tumor", "Arsenic poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Terry McQueen?", "answers": ["Morphine", "Polycythemia", "Asthma", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lorne Greene?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Diverticulosis", "Chronic renal failure", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Acute pancreatitis", "Acral lentiginous melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Nixon?", "answers": ["Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Head and neck cancer", "Cerebral edema", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Nixon?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Heart cancer", "Acral lentiginous melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Nikita Khrushchev?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Cholangiocarcinoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Cholera"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Ramirez?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Diverticulosis", "Liver failure", "Pneumocystis pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Ramirez?", "answers": ["B-cell lymphoma", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Melanoma", "Thyroid cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Langston Hughes?", "answers": ["Prostate cancer", "Alzheimer's disease", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Gangrene"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Keith Moon?", "answers": ["Falling", "Alcohol intoxication", "Tongue Cancer", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Terry Lester?", "answers": ["Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Myocardial infarction", "Chest pain", "Pleurisy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Orville Redenbacher?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Gangrene", "Drowning", "Respiratory Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Orville Redenbacher?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Multiple sclerosis", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kit Carson?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Kidney cancer", "Cardiomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Kardashian?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Respiratory disease", "Ischaemic heart disease", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Kardashian?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Coronary occlusion", "Multiple sclerosis", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Kardashian?", "answers": ["Malaria", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Esophageal cancer", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Thomas D\u00f6rflein?", "answers": ["Uterine cancer", "Septic shock", "Myocardial infarction", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Waheed Murad?", "answers": ["Ruptured Aneurysm", "Respiratory Infection", "Childbirth", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gail Russell?", "answers": ["Celiac disease", "Myocardial infarction", "Barbiturate", "Dementia pugilistica"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gail Russell?", "answers": ["Pulmonary aspiration", "Bladder cancer", "Cirrhosis", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Merlin Olsen?", "answers": ["Injury", "Physical abuse", "Mesothelioma", "Bladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Grandpa Jones?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Poison", "Systemic scleroderma", "Hepatocellular carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Aziz Shavershian?", "answers": ["Typhoid fever", "Celiac disease", "Head and neck cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gil Hodges?", "answers": ["Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Heart cancer", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carl Wilson?", "answers": ["Yellow fever", "Lung cancer", "Liver cancer", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carl Wilson?", "answers": ["Oral cancer", "Brain tumor", "Cervical cancer", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ida Lupino?", "answers": ["Parkinson's disease", "Stroke", "Muscular dystrophy", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Michael Staniforth?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Internal bleeding", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Wright?", "answers": ["Paraquat", "Encephalopathy", "Aortic aneurysm", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mark Foo?", "answers": ["Physical abuse", "Drowning", "Puerperal fever", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Corwin Hawkins?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Fever", "Exhaustion", "Wound"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lloyd Avery II?", "answers": ["Aspiration pneumonia", "Physical abuse", "Embolism", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Serge Gainsbourg?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Morphine", "Anaphylaxis", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy L. Dennis?", "answers": ["Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Encephalopathy", "Liver disease", "Endometrial cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Evel Knievel?", "answers": ["Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis", "Chronic renal failure", "Melanoma", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Francisco Franco?", "answers": ["Throat cancer", "Colon Cancer", "Gangrene", "Parkinson's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Breck?", "answers": ["Traumatic brain injury", "Insulinoma", "Malnutrition", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dayananda Saraswati?", "answers": ["Pernicious anemia", "Poison", "Aplastic anemia", "Pleurisy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dick Sargent?", "answers": ["Puerperal fever", "Prostate cancer", "Leukemia", "Traumatic brain injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ivan Pavlov?", "answers": ["Septic shock", "Post-polio syndrome", "Pneumonia", "Malaria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Felix Mendelssohn-Bartholdy?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Poisoning", "Stroke", "Peritonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dave Niehaus?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Anaphylaxis", "Lupus erythematosus", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Uttam Kumar?", "answers": ["Synovial sarcoma", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Alzheimer's disease", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jon Pertwee?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Myocardial infarction", "Tuberculosis", "Trichinosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Alvin Ailey?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "AIDS", "Aspiration pneumonia", "Cystic fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ramona Bell?", "answers": ["Asthma", "Diarrhea", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Skip Prosser?", "answers": ["Arsenic poisoning", "Yellow fever", "Myocardial infarction", "Oral cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Kidd Kraddick?", "answers": ["Coronary artery disease", "Cardiac arrest", "Cardiovascular disease", "Acral lentiginous melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hank Williams?", "answers": ["Shock", "Drug overdose", "Appendix cancer", "Barbiturate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marich Man Singh Shrestha?", "answers": ["Ruptured Aneurysm", "Lung cancer", "Polycythemia", "Aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward VI of England?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Peritonitis", "Embolism", "Pernicious anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bob Hope?", "answers": ["Asthma", "Post-polio syndrome", "Pneumonia", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pina Bausch?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Choking", "Starvation", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of \"James \"\"Grizzly\"\" Adams\"?", "answers": ["Toxoplasmosis", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Meningitis", "Starvation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Randolph Hearst?", "answers": ["Fournier gangrene", "Myocardial infarction", "Exhaustion", "Binge drinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Boyle?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Smoke inhalation", "Schistosomiasis", "Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Boyle?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Cardiovascular disease", "Epidural hematoma", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Boyle?", "answers": ["Sepsis", "Cerebral edema", "Multiple myeloma", "Bright's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Peter Boyle?", "answers": ["Barbiturate", "Cancer", "Metastatic Melanoma", "Diverticulosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Myfanwy Talog?", "answers": ["Poisoning", "Breast cancer", "Kawasaki disease", "Bone cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Millard Fillmore?", "answers": ["Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Stroke", "Multiple sclerosis", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Von Erich?", "answers": ["Epidemic typhus", "Smallpox", "Poison", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Von Erich?", "answers": ["Starvation", "Drug overdose", "Kawasaki disease", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Von Erich?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Pancreatitis", "Carbon monoxide poisoning", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Milton Berle?", "answers": ["Liver disease", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Skull fracture", "Colorectal cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mary Antonia Wayne LaCava?", "answers": ["Lung cancer", "Infection", "Multiple sclerosis", "Infectious disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rachel Carson?", "answers": ["Viral pneumonia", "Drug overdose", "Chronic renal failure", "Breast cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Laura Canales?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Paraquat", "Wound", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Luana Patten?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Respiratory failure", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Scott Joplin?", "answers": ["Thyroid cancer", "Pancreatitis", "Dementia", "Huntington's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fannie Lou Hamer?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Aplastic anemia", "Bone cancer", "Metastatic Melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hans Holbein the Younger?", "answers": ["Uterine cancer", "Cyanide poisoning", "Tetanus", "Bubonic plague"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sheridan Morley?", "answers": ["Pulmonary embolism", "Hyperthermia", "Cardiovascular disease", "Mesothelioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerry Quarry?", "answers": ["Dengue fever", "Cardiac arrest", "Asthma", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Catherine Parr?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Atherosclerosis", "Encephalopathy", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bobby Leach?", "answers": ["Liver tumour", "Bladder cancer", "Gangrene", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Gregory Scarpa?", "answers": ["Arteriosclerosis", "Choking", "AIDS", "Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Claude Monet?", "answers": ["AIDS", "Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Lung cancer", "Puerperal fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George S. Patton?", "answers": ["Injury", "Seizure", "Dehydration", "Poison"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy Walford?", "answers": ["Motor neuron disease", "Cyanide poisoning", "Binge drinking", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Roy Walford?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Lung cancer", "Renal cell carcinoma", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bernadette San Pedro Bayot?", "answers": ["Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "AIDS", "Intracranial aneurysm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Malcolm Campbell?", "answers": ["Injury", "Poisoning", "Stroke", "Sepsis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Doug Henning?", "answers": ["Gangrene", "Diabetes mellitus", "Liver cancer", "Typhoid fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marcel Proust?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Dysentery", "Renal failure", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Warren G. Harding?", "answers": ["Diverticulosis", "Nephritis", "Myocardial infarction", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dirk Bogarde?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Myocardial infarction", "Trichinosis", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hoyt Axton?", "answers": ["Uterine cancer", "Rheumatic fever", "Infectious disease", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wallace Beery?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Gastrointestinal bleeding", "Bright's disease", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Joyce Jameson?", "answers": ["Tetanus", "Hepatitis A", "Arteriosclerosis", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Robert Young?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Respiratory failure", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Cholangiocarcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Henry Harrison?", "answers": ["Craniocerebral Trauma", "Pneumonia", "Parkinson's disease", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of William Henry Harrison?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Bone cancer", "Sepsis", "Endometrial cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ricky Wilson?", "answers": ["Atherosclerosis", "Childbirth", "Fever", "AIDS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sujatha?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Liver cancer", "Accidental Fire", "Leiomyosarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ish Kabibble?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Trichinosis", "Respiratory failure", "Gigantism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles de Batz-Castelmore d'Artagnan?", "answers": ["Gallbladder cancer", "Ballistic trauma", "Fever", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Krissy Taylor?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Cirrhosis", "Cardiovascular disease", "Alcohol intoxication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Krissy Taylor?", "answers": ["Syphilis", "Malaria", "Heart failure", "Embolism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Krissy Taylor?", "answers": ["Binge drinking", "Asthma", "Huntington's disease", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Margaret Sanger?", "answers": ["Falling", "Heart failure", "Arsenic poisoning", "Aplastic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eric Douglas?", "answers": ["Aneurysm", "Diarrhea", "Seizure", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mickey Mantle?", "answers": ["Schistosomiasis", "Liver tumour", "Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy", "Respiratory failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Klaus Kinski?", "answers": ["Meningitis", "Myocardial infarction", "Kidney cancer", "Craniocerebral Trauma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Clarence Clemons?", "answers": ["Cyanide poisoning", "Stroke", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Meningeal Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Warren Oates?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Peritonitis", "Infection", "Alcohol intoxication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hank Thompson?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Epilepsy", "Lung cancer", "Kidney Disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Mark McManus?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Heart cancer", "Pneumonia", "Binge drinking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Manjula Vijayakumar?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Puerperal fever", "Liver tumour", "Lobar pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eldridge Cleaver?", "answers": ["Pleurisy", "Diarrhea", "Multiple myeloma", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jill Clayburgh?", "answers": ["AIDS", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Tuberculosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jill Clayburgh?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Leukemia", "Respiratory Infection", "Gallbladder cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Marian Anderson?", "answers": ["Hepatitis", "Heart failure", "Uterine cancer", "Huntington's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Simple Kapadia?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Esophageal cancer", "Trichinosis", "Skull fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Guy McDonough?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Head and neck cancer", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brenda Marshall?", "answers": ["Infection", "Throat cancer", "Huntington's disease", "Liver cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of David Dukes?", "answers": ["Pancreatic cancer", "Renal failure", "Hepatitis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Arjumand Banu?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Hepatitis", "Childbirth", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jenny Tomasin?", "answers": ["Appendix cancer", "Gangrene", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Throat cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Feroze Gandhi?", "answers": ["Asphyxia", "Sepsis", "Seizure", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Derek Boogaard?", "answers": ["Bright's disease", "Exhaustion", "Seizure", "Drug overdose"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Derek Boogaard?", "answers": ["Alcohol intoxication", "Trauma", "Bronchopneumonia", "Hepatitis A"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lucky Luciano?", "answers": ["Non-Hodgkin lymphoma", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Myocardial infarction", "Morphine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Savitri Devi?", "answers": ["Renal Cancer", "Tetanus", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Savitri Devi?", "answers": ["Myasthenia gravis", "Gangrene", "Cancer of the larynx", "Coronary thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Natasha Richardson?", "answers": ["Bacterial pneumonia", "Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis", "Respiratory Infection", "Epidural hematoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Natasha Richardson?", "answers": ["Tongue Cancer", "Traumatic brain injury", "Morphine", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lynne Frederick?", "answers": ["Iatrogenesis", "Fever", "Alcoholism", "Huntington's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edmund Barton?", "answers": ["Barbiturate overdose", "Accidental Fire", "Kidney cancer", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sledge Hammer?", "answers": ["Breast cancer", "Cardiac arrest", "Poisoning", "Renal cell carcinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lawrence Kohlberg?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Drowning", "Diarrhea", "Atherosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Brigham Young?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Peritonitis", "Accidental Fire", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hari Rhodes?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Hodgkin's lymphoma", "Myocardial infarction", "Liver disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Silvana Gallardo?", "answers": ["Bone cancer", "Asthma", "Throat cancer", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Scatman John?", "answers": ["Aortic aneurysm", "Renal failure", "Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Lung cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Andre Young Jr.?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Hepatitis C", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Eric Turner?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Barbiturate", "Colorectal cancer", "Insulinoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lee Remick?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Smallpox", "Kidney cancer", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lee Remick?", "answers": ["Hepatocellular carcinoma", "Embolism", "Choking", "Testicular cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lee Remick?", "answers": ["Renal cell carcinoma", "Craniodiaphyseal dysplasia", "Coronary artery disease", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Lee Remick?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Liver tumour", "Dementia", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Count Basie?", "answers": ["Hepatitis C", "Heart failure", "Pancreatic cancer", "Myelodysplastic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fred Dibnah?", "answers": ["Bubonic plague", "Ballistic trauma", "Peritonitis", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Fred Dibnah?", "answers": ["Fever", "Marfan syndrome", "Appendix cancer", "Prostate cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jimmie Rodgers?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Diabetes mellitus", "Cirrhosis", "Poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Dick Shawn?", "answers": ["Accidental Fire", "Exhaustion", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Miguel Calero?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Testicular cancer", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Cerebral thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Wende Wagner?", "answers": ["Cancer", "Cardiomegaly", "Wound", "Carbon monoxide poisoning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ross Martin?", "answers": ["Arthritis", "Malnutrition", "Myocardial infarction", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of James Strong?", "answers": ["Respiratory disease", "Alcoholism", "Gangrene", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Florence Ballard?", "answers": ["Cardiovascular disease", "Septic shock", "Lung cancer", "Accidental Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Le\u00f4nidas da Silva?", "answers": ["Hepatitis A", "Alzheimer's disease", "Debility", "Acral lentiginous melanoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harold Lloyd?", "answers": ["Hepatitis", "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Prostate cancer", "Aspiration pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jerry Garcia?", "answers": ["Colon Cancer", "Respiratory failure", "Myocardial infarction", "Multiple sclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Camu Tao?", "answers": ["Bright's disease", "Syphilis", "Lung cancer", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Best?", "answers": ["Tongue Cancer", "Skull fracture", "Infectious disease", "Toxoplasmosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Best?", "answers": ["Emphysema", "Kidney Disease", "Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Alcoholism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Best?", "answers": ["Post-polio syndrome", "Surgery", "Infant respiratory distress syndrome", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Pete Maravich?", "answers": ["Nephropathy", "Myasthenia gravis", "Respiratory arrest", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jimmie Foxx?", "answers": ["Leukemia", "Ovarian cancer", "Starvation", "Choking"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tammi Terrell?", "answers": ["Heart cancer", "Poisoning", "Stroke", "Brain tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jim Varney?", "answers": ["Lymphoma", "Dementia with Lewy bodies", "Lung cancer", "Aortic dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Donna Reed?", "answers": ["Bronchitis", "Infection", "Pancreatic cancer", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Elmore Leonard?", "answers": ["Smoke inhalation", "Trichinosis", "Stroke", "Endometrial cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rosalind Franklin?", "answers": ["Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Appendix cancer", "Hypertension", "Ovarian cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rosalind Franklin?", "answers": ["Abdominal aortic aneurysm", "Ruptured Aneurysm", "Cancer", "Muscular dystrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Susan Butcher?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Poisoning", "Leukemia", "Arteriosclerosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rahul Dev Burman?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Binge drinking", "Respiratory arrest", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Quincy Adams?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Cyanide poisoning", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Francis Magalona?", "answers": ["Ruptured Aneurysm", "Anal cancer", "Edema", "Leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Bill Shankly?", "answers": ["Influenza", "Myocardial infarction", "Cardiac arrest", "Huntington's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Leah Betts?", "answers": ["Drug overdose", "Childbirth", "Myelodysplastic syndrome", "Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Max Cantor?", "answers": ["Atypical teratoid rhabdoid tumor", "Drug overdose", "Fournier gangrene", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ren\u00e9 Descartes?", "answers": ["Rheumatic fever", "Rheumatic fever", "Cerebral thrombosis", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Carl Perkins?", "answers": ["Skull fracture", "Suffocation", "Throat cancer", "Non-Hodgkin lymphoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Tommy Cooper?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Liver disease", "Myocardial infarction", "B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Shelley Winters?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Syphilis", "Renal failure", "Hypertensive heart disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Boone?", "answers": ["Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease", "Throat cancer", "Lupus erythematosus", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Richard Boone?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Pneumonia", "Cardiomegaly", "Coronary occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Rio Diaz?", "answers": ["Melanoma", "Encephalopathy", "Synovial sarcoma", "Colon Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harold Wilson?", "answers": ["Alzheimer's disease", "Ovarian cancer", "Paraquat", "Nephropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Harold Wilson?", "answers": ["Colorectal cancer", "Aortic aneurysm", "B-cell lymphoma", "Asphyxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Charles Colson?", "answers": ["Nephritis", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Fournier gangrene", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Noel Redding?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Edema", "Arthritis", "Bright's disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Umm Kulthum?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "AIDS", "Sepsis", "Epidural hematoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Umm Kulthum?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Nephritis", "Fever", "Pulmonary aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Chuck Brown?", "answers": ["Enteritis", "Melanoma", "Pneumonia", "Synovial sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Ken Norton?", "answers": ["Brain tumor", "Tetanus", "Throat cancer", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sulla?", "answers": ["Tetanus", "Cirrhosis", "Trauma", "Nephritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Sulla?", "answers": ["Alcoholism", "Brain tumor", "Aplastic anemia", "Cardiomyopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Donald Bradman?", "answers": ["Arsenic poisoning", "Hypertensive heart disease", "Pneumonia", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Jack Webb?", "answers": ["Trauma", "Myocardial infarction", "Enteritis", "Tongue Cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Skeeter Davis?", "answers": ["Burn", "Pneumocystis pneumonia", "Breast cancer", "Liver failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of John Phillips?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Cardiovascular disease", "Polymyalgia rheumatica"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of J Dilla?", "answers": ["Arsenic poisoning", "Systemic lupus erythematosus", "Ballistic trauma", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Edward Albert?", "answers": ["Cerebral edema", "Lobar pneumonia", "Lung cancer", "Gastrointestinal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Maria Montessori?", "answers": ["Bladder cancer", "Pneumothorax", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Iatrogenesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What was the cause of death of George Formby?", "answers": ["Encephalitis", "Physical abuse", "Peritonitis", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What was the cause of death of Hank Snow?", "answers": ["B-cell lymphoma", "Heart failure", "Dementia", "Heart cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}